<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PXZHANG</title>
    <description>这里是 @PXZHANG张培歆 的个人网站</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 18:48:57 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 18:48:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (IJCAI)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reasoning about Consensus when Opinions Diffuse through Majority Dynamics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincenzo Auletta, University of Salerno&lt;br /&gt;Diodato Ferraioli, University of Salerno&lt;br /&gt;Gianluigi Greco, University of Calabria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SentiGAN: Generating Sentimental Texts via Mixture Adversarial Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ke Wang &amp;amp; Xiaojun Wan, Peking University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Conjunctive Queries to Instance Queries in Ontology-Mediated Querying&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristina Feier, University of Bremen&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Lutz, University of Bremen&lt;br /&gt;Frank Wolte, University of Liverpool&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What game are we playing? End-to-end learning in normal and extensive form games&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chun Kai Ling, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Fei Fang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;J. Zico Kolter, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Commonsense Knowledge Aware Conversation Generation with Graph Attention&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hao Zhou, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Tom Young, Beijing Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Minlie Huang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Haizhou Zhao, Sogou Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Jingfang Xu, Sogou Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoyan Zhu, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;R-SVM+: Robust Learning with Privileged Information&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xue Li, Wuhan University&lt;br /&gt;Bo Du, Wuhan University&lt;br /&gt;Chang Xu, University of Sydney&lt;br /&gt;Yipeng Zhang, Wuhan University&lt;br /&gt;Lefei Zhang, Wuhan University&lt;br /&gt;Dacheng Tao, University of Sydney&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Degeneracy Framework for Graph Similarity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giannis Nikolentzos, École Polytechnique&lt;br /&gt;Polykarpos Meladianos, Athens University of Economics and Business&lt;br /&gt;Stratis Limnios, École Polytechnique&lt;br /&gt;Michalis Vazirgiannis, École Polytechnique&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foundations of Declarative Data Analysis Using Limit Datalog Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Kaminski, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Bernardo Cuenca Grau, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Egor V. Kostylev, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Boris Motik, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Ian Horrocks, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hierarchical Finite State Controllers for Generalized Planning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Javier Segovia, Universitat Pompeu Fabra&lt;br /&gt;Sergio Jiménez, Universitat Pompeu Fabra&lt;br /&gt;Anders Jonsson, Universitat Pompeu Fabra&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Active Learning for Posterior Estimation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kirthevasan Kandasamy, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Schneider, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Barnabas Poczos, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recursive Decomposition for Nonconvex Optimization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abram L. Friesen &amp;amp; Pedro Domingos, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Optimization in High Dimensions via Random Embeddings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ziyu Wang, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Masrour Zoghi, University of Amsterdam&lt;br /&gt;Frank Hutter, Freiberg University&lt;br /&gt;David Matheson, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Nando de Freitas, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Flexibility and Decoupling in the Simple Temporal Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michel Wilson, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Tomas Klos, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Cees Witteveen, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bob Huisman, Delft University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unweighted Coalitional Manipulation Under the Borda Rule is NP-Hard&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nadja Betzler, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Rolf Niedermeier, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard J. Woeginger, Technische Universität Eindhoven&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nested Rollout Policy Adaptation for Monte Carlo Tree Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher D. Rosin, Parity Computing&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Decidability of Connectedness Constraints in 2D and 3D Euclidean Spaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Roman Kontchakov, Birkbeck College London&lt;br /&gt;Yavor Nenov, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Ian Pratt-Hartmann, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Michael Zakharyaschev, Birkbeck College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consequence-Driven Reasoning for Horn SHIQ Ontologies&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yevgeny Kazakov, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Conditional Preference Networks with Queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Frederic Koriche, Université Montpellier II&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Zanuttini, Université de Caen Basse-Normandie&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automated Heart Wall Motion Abnormality Detection From Ultrasound Images using Bayesian Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maleeha Qazi, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Glenn Fung, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Sriram Krishnan, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Romer Rosales, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Harald Steck, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;R. Bharat Rao, Siemens Medical Solutions&lt;br /&gt;Don Polderman, Erasmus University Medical Center&lt;br /&gt;Dhanalakshmi Chandrasekaran, No Affiliation&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building Structure into Local Search for SAT&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Duc Nghia Pham, Griffith University&lt;br /&gt;John Thornton, Griffith University&lt;br /&gt;Abdul Sattar, Griffith University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Performance Analysis of Online Anticipatory Algorithms for Large Multistage Stochastic Integer Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Luc Mercier &amp;amp; Pascal Van Hentenryck, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Coordination Classifiers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuhong Guo, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Russell Greiner, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Dale Schuurmans, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Solving Checkers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jonathan Schaeffer, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Yngvi Bjornsson, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Neil Burch, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Akihiro Kishimoto, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Martin Muller, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Robert Lake, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Paul Lu, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Steve Sutphen, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Probabilistic Model of Redundancy in Information Extraction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Doug Downey, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Oren Etzioni, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Soderland, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximating Game-Theoretic Optimal Strategies for Full-scale Poker&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Darse Billings, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Neil Burch, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Davidson, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Robert Holte, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Schaeffer, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Terence Schauenberg, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Duane Szafron, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thin Junction Tree Filters for Simultaneous Localization and Mapping&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark A. Paskin, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Complexity Results for Structure-Based Causality&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Eiter &amp;amp; Thomas Lukasiewicz, Vienna University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning in Natural Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Roth, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Distributed Case-Based Reasoning Application for Engineering Sales Support&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ian Watson, University of Salford&lt;br /&gt;Dan Gardingen, Western Air&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object Identification in a Bayesian Context&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Timothy Huang &amp;amp; Stuart Russell, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Translingual Information Retrieval: A Comparative Evaluation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jaime G. Carbonell, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Yiming Yang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Robert E. Frederking, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ralf D. Brown, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Yibing Geng, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Danny Lee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Applications of the Situation Calculus to Formalizing Control and Strategic Information: The Prolog Cut Operator&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fangzhen Lin, The Hongkong University of Science and Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/11/best-paper-awards-IJCAI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/11/best-paper-awards-IJCAI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (ICSE)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Large-Scale Analysis of Framework-Specific Exceptions in Android Apps&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lingling Fan, East China Normal University&lt;br /&gt;Ting Su, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Sen Chen, East China Normal University&lt;br /&gt;Guozhu Meng, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Yang Liu, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Lihua Xu, East China Normal University&lt;br /&gt;Geguang Pu, East China Normal University&lt;br /&gt;Zhendong Su, University of California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Generalized Data Structure Synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Calvin Loncaric, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Emina Torlak, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Static Automated Program Repair for Heap Properties&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rijnard van Tonder &amp;amp; Claire Le Goues, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards Optimal Concolic Testing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xinyu Wang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Jun Sun, Singapore University of Technology and Design&lt;br /&gt;Zhenbang Chen, National University of Defense Technology&lt;br /&gt;Peixin Zhang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Jingyi Wang, Singapore University of Technology and Design&lt;br /&gt;Yun Lin, National University of Singapore&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spatio-Temporal Context Reduction: A Pointer-Analysis-Based Static Approach for Detecting Use-After-Free Vulnerabilities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hua Yan, University of New South Wales&lt;br /&gt;Yulei Sui, University of Technology Sydney&lt;br /&gt;Shiping Chen, CSIRO&lt;br /&gt;Jingling Xue, University of New South Wales&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Identifying Design Problems in the Source Code: A Grounded Theory&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Leonardo Sousa, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Anderson Oliveira, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Willian Oizumi, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Simone Barbosa, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Garcia, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Jaejoon Lee, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Marcos Kalinowski, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Rafael de Mello, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Baldoino Fonseca, UFAL&lt;br /&gt;Roberto Oliveira, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Lucena, PUC-Rio&lt;br /&gt;Rodrigo Paes, PUC-Rio&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Traceability in the Wild: Automatically Augmenting Incomplete Trace links&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Rath, Technical University Ilmenau&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Rendall, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Jin L. C. Guo, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;Jane Cleland-Huang, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Mäder, Technical University Ilmenau&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automated Localization for Unreproducible Builds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhilei Ren, Dalian University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;He Jiang, Dalian University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jifeng Xuan, Wuhan University&lt;br /&gt;Zijiang Yang, Western Michigan University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Decoding the representation of code in the brain: An fMRI study of code review and expertise&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benjamin Floyd, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;Tyler Santander, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;Westley Weimer, University of Virginia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Code Defenders: Crowdsourcing Effective Tests and Subtle Mutants with a Mutation Testing Game&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;José Miguel Rojas, The University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Thomas D. White, The University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin S. Clegg, The University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Gordon Fraser, The University of Sheffield&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Clone Refactoring with Lambda Expressions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nikolaos Tsantalis, Concordia University&lt;br /&gt;Davood Mazinanian, Concordia University&lt;br /&gt;Shahriar Rostami, Concordia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimizing Test Placement for Module-Level Regression Testing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;August Shi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Suresh Thummalapenta, Microsoft Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Shuvendu K. Lahiri, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Nikolaj Bjorner, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jacek Czerwonka, Microsoft Corporation&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Grounded Theory of Agile Transitions in Practice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rashina Hoda, The University of Auckland&lt;br /&gt;James Noble Victoria, University of Wellington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Challenges for Static Analysis of Java Reflection-Literature Review and Empirical Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Davy Landman, Centrum Wiskunde &amp;amp; Informatica&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Serebrenik, Centrum Wiskunde &amp;amp; Informatica&lt;br /&gt;Jurgen J. Vinju, Centrum Wiskunde &amp;amp; Informatica&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feedback-Directed Instrumentation for Deployed JavaScript Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Magnus Madsen, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Frank Tip, Samsung Research&lt;br /&gt;Esben Andreasen, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Anders Møller, Aarhus University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Word Embeddings to Document Similarities for Improved Information Retrieval in Software Engineering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xin Ye, Ohio University Athens&lt;br /&gt;Hui Shen, Ohio University Athens&lt;br /&gt;Xiao Ma, Ohio University Athens&lt;br /&gt;Razvan Bunescu, Ohio University Athens&lt;br /&gt;Chang Liu, Ohio University Athens&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Techniques We Create, the Tools We Build, and Their Misalignments: A Study of KLEE&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric F. Rizzi, Grammatech&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Elbaum, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Matthew B. Dwyer, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Work Practices and Challenges in Pull-Based Development: The Contributor’s Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georgios Gousios, Radboud University Nijmegen&lt;br /&gt;Margaret-Anne Storey, University of Victoria&lt;br /&gt;Alberto Bacchelli, Delft University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Termination-Checking for LLVM Peephole Optimizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Menendez &amp;amp; Santosh Nagarakatte, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Guiding Dynamic Symbolic Execution toward Unverified Program Executions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maria Christakis, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Peter Müller, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Valentin Wüstholz, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Large-Scale Trace Checking Using MapReduce&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcello M. Bersani, Politecnico di Milano&lt;br /&gt;Domenico Bianculli, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Carlo Ghezzi, Politecnico di Milano&lt;br /&gt;Srđan Krstić, Politecnico di Milano&lt;br /&gt;Pierluigi San Pietro, Politecnico di Milano&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;VDTest: An Automated Framework to Support Testing for Virtual Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tingting Yu, University of Kentucky&lt;br /&gt;Xiao Qu, ABB Corporate Research&lt;br /&gt;Myra B. Cohen, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Energy Profiles of Java Collections Classes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Samir Hasan, Auburn University&lt;br /&gt;Zachary King, Auburn University&lt;br /&gt;Munawar Hafiz, Auburn University&lt;br /&gt;Mohammed Sayagh, Polytechnique Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Bram Adams, Polytechnique Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Abram Hindle, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alloy*: A General-Purpose Higher-Order Relational Constraint Solver&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aleksandar Milicevic, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joseph P. Near, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Eunsuk Kang, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jackson, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Much Up-Front? A Grounded theory of Agile Architecture&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Waterman, Specialised Architecture Services Ltd&lt;br /&gt;James Noble, Victoria University of Wellington&lt;br /&gt;George Allan, Victoria University of Wellington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Views on Internal and External Validity in Empirical Software Engineering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Janet Siegmund, University of Passau&lt;br /&gt;Norbert Siegmund, University of Passau&lt;br /&gt;Sven Apel, University of Passau&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Why Good Developers Write Bad Code: An Observational Case Study of the Impacts of Organizational Factors on Software Quality&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mathieu Lavallée &amp;amp; Pierre N. Robillard, Polytechnique Montréal&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;When and Why Your Code Starts to Smell Bad&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michele Tufano, College of William and Mary&lt;br /&gt;Fabio Palomba, University of Salerno&lt;br /&gt;Gabriele Bavota, Free University of Bozen-Bolzano&lt;br /&gt;Rocco Oliveto, University of Molise&lt;br /&gt;Massimiliano Di Penta, University of Sannio&lt;br /&gt;Andrea De Lucia, University of Salerno&lt;br /&gt;Denys Poshyvanyk, College of William and Mary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CARAMEL: Detecting and Fixing Performance Problems That Have Non-Intrusive Fixes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adrian Nistor, Chapman University&lt;br /&gt;Po-Chun Chang, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Cosmin Radoi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Shan Lu, University of Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Characterizing and Detecting Performance Bugs for Smartphone Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yepang Liu, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Chang Xu, Nanjing University&lt;br /&gt;Shing-Chi Cheung, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Automated Source Code Summarization via an Eye-Tracking Study of Programmers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paige Rodeghero, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Collin McMillan, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Paul W. McBurney, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Nigel Bosch, University of Notre Dame&lt;br /&gt;Sidney D’Mello, University of Notre Dame&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding JavaScript Event-Based Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Saba Alimadadi, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Sheldon Sequeira, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Ali Mesbah, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karthik Pattabiraman, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Coverage Is Not Strongly Correlated with Test Suite Effectiveness&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laura Inozemtseva &amp;amp; Reid Holmes, University of Waterloo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cowboys, Ankle Sprains, and Keepers of Quality: How Is Video Game Development Different from Software Development&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emerson Murphy-Hill, North Carolina State University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Nachiappan Nagappan, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trading Robustness for Maintainability: An Empirical Study of Evolving C# Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nélio Cacho, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Thiago César, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Filipe, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Eliezio Soares, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Arthur Cassio, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Rafael Souza, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Israel Garcia, Federal University of Rio Grande do Norte&lt;br /&gt;Eiji Adachi Barbosa, Pontifical Catholic University of Rio de Janeiro&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Garcia, Pontifical Catholic University of Rio de Janeiro&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unit Test Virtualization with VMVM&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jonathan Bell &amp;amp; Gail Kaiser, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enhancing Symbolic Execution with Veritesting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thanassis Avgerinos, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alexandre Rebert, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Sang Kil Cha, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;David Brumley, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Study and Toolkit for Asynchronous Programming in C#&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semih Okur, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;David L. Hartveld, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Danny Dig, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Arie van Deursen, Delft University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dual Ecological Measures of Focus in Software Development&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daryl Posnett, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Raissa D’Souza, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Premkumar Devanbu, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Vladimir Filkov, University of California Davis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Clone Detection and Visualization in Spreadsheets&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Felienne Hermans, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ben Sedee, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Martin Pinzger, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Arie van Deursen, Delft University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;UML in Practice	Marian Petre, Open University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic patch generation learned from human-written patches&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dongsun Kim, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jaechang Nam, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jaewoo Song, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Sunghun Kim, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assisting Developers of Big Data Analytics Applications When Deploying on Hadoop Clouds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weiyi Shang, Queen’s University&lt;br /&gt;Zhen Ming Jiang, Queen’s University&lt;br /&gt;Hadi Hemmati, Queen’s University&lt;br /&gt;Bram Adams, Polytechnique Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Ahmed E. Hassan, Queen’s University&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Martin, Queen’s University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Interaction-Based Test-Suite Minimization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dale Blue, IBM&lt;br /&gt;Itai Segall, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Rachel Tzoref-Brill, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Aviad Zlotnick, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Integer Overflow in C/C++&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Will Dietz, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Peng Li, University of Utah&lt;br /&gt;John Regehr, University of Utah&lt;br /&gt;Vikram Adve, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Dynamic Analysis to Discover Polynomial and Array Invariants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ThanhVu Nguyen, University of New Mexico&lt;br /&gt;Deepak Kapur, University of New Mexico&lt;br /&gt;Westley Weimer, University of New Mexico&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie Forrest, University of New Mexico&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amplifying Tests to Validate Exception Handling Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pingyu Zhang &amp;amp; Sebastian Elbaum, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Partial Models: Towards Modeling and Reasoning with Uncertainty&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michalis Famelis, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Rick Salay, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Marsha Chechik, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Do Professional Developers Comprehend Software?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tobias Roehm, Technische Universität München&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Tiarks, University of Bremen&lt;br /&gt;Rainer Koschke, University of Bremen&lt;br /&gt;Walid Maalej, Technische Universität München&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Tactic-Centric Approach for Automating Traceability of Quality Concerns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mehdi Mirakhorli, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Yonghee Shin, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Jane Cleland-Huang, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Murat Cinar, DePaul University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automated Detection of Client-State Manipulation Vulnerabilities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anders Møller &amp;amp; Mathias Schwarz, Aarhus University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verifying Multi-threaded Software using SMT-based Context-Bounded Model Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lucas Cordeiro &amp;amp; Bernd Fischer, University of Southampton&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Configuring Global Software Teams: A Multi-Company Analysis of Project Productivity, Quality, and Profits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Narayan Ramasubbu, Singapore Management University&lt;br /&gt;Marcelo Cataldo, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Rajesh Krishna Balan, Singapore Management University&lt;br /&gt;James D. Herbsleb, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Programs, tests, and oracles: the foundations of testing revisited&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matt Staats, University of Minnesota&lt;br /&gt;Michael W. Whalen, University of Minnesota&lt;br /&gt;Mats P.E. Heimdahl, University of Minnesota&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On-demand Feature Recommendations Derived from Mining Public Product Descriptions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Horatiu Dumitru, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Marek Gibiec, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Negar Hariri, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Jane Cleland-Huang, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Bamshad Mobasher, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Castro-Herrera, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Mehdi Mirakhorli, DePaul University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Run-Time Efficient Probabilistic Model Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Antonio Filieri, Politecnico di Milano&lt;br /&gt;Carlo Ghezzi, Politecnico di Milano&lt;br /&gt;Giordano Tamburrelli, Politecnico di Milano&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Machine Learning Approach for Tracing Regulatory Codes to Product Specific Requirements&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jane Cleland-Huang, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Adam Czauderna, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;John Emenecker, DePaul University&lt;br /&gt;Marek Gibiec, DePaul University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Collaborative Reliability Prediction of Service-Oriented Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zibin Zheng &amp;amp; Michael R. Lyu, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Cut-off Approach for Bounded Verification of Parameterized Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Qiusong Yang &amp;amp; Mingshu Li, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Test Generation through Programming in UDITA&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Milos Gligoric, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Tihomir Gvero, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Vilas Jagannath, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Sarfraz Khurshid, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Viktor Kuncak, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Degree-of-Knowledge Model to Capture Source Code Familiarity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Fritz, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Jingwen Ou, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Gail C. Murphy, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Emerson Murphy-Hill, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How We Refactor, and How We Know It&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emerson Murphy-Hill, Portland State University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Parnin, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andrew P. Black, Portland State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effective Static Deadlock Detection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mayur Naik, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Chang-Seo Park, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Gay, Intel Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Invariant-Based Automatic Testing of AJAX User Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ali Mesbah &amp;amp; Arie van Deursen, Delft University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Does Distributed Development Affect Software Quality? An Empirical Case Study of Windows Vista&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Bird, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Nachiappan Nagappan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Premkumar Devanbu, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Harald Gall, University of Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Brendan Murphy, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically finding patches using genetic programming&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Westley Weimer, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;ThanhVu Nguyen, University of New Mexico&lt;br /&gt;Claire Le Goues, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie Forrest, University of New Mexico&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Precise memory leak detection for java software using container profiling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Guoqing Xu &amp;amp; Atanas Rountev, Ohio State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Debugging reinvented: asking and answering why and why not questions about program behavior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew J. Ko &amp;amp; Brad A. Myers, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recommending adaptive changes for framework evolution&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barthélémy Dagenais &amp;amp; Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting Accurate and Actionable Static Analysis Warnings: An Experimental Approach&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joseph Ruthruff, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;John Penix, Google&lt;br /&gt;J. David Morgenthaler, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Elbaum, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Gregg Rothermel, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The effect of program and model structure on mc/dc test adequacy coverage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ajitha Rajan, University of Minnesota&lt;br /&gt;Michael W. Whalen, Rockwell Collins&lt;br /&gt;Mats P.E. Heimdahl, University of Minnesota&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Refactoring for Parameterizing Java Classes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adam Kiezun, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Frank Tip, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Robert M. Fuhrer, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tracking Code Clones in Evolving Software&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ekwa Duala-Ekoko &amp;amp; Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matching and Merging of Statecharts Specifications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shiva Nejati, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Mehrdad Sabetzadeh, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Marsha Chechik, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Steve Easterbrook, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Pamela Zave, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting Faults from Cached History&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sunghun Kim, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;E. James Whitehead Jr., University of California Santa Cruz&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Zeller, Saarland University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Model-Based Development of Dynamically Adaptive Software&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ji Zhang &amp;amp; Betty H.C. Cheng, Michigan State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Who Should Fix This Bug?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Anvik, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Lyndon Hiew, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Gail C. Murphy, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eliciting Design Requirements for Maintenance-Oriented IDEs: A Detailed Study of Corrective and Perfective Maintenance Tasks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Ko, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Htet Htet Aung, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Brad Myers, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Is Mutation an Appropriate Tool for Testing Experiments?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Andrews, University of Western Ontario&lt;br /&gt;Lionel Briand, Carleton University&lt;br /&gt;Yvan Labiche, Carleton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Structural Context to Recommend Source Code Examples&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reid Holmes &amp;amp; Gail Murphy, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Structure Repair Using Goal-Directed Reasoning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brian Demsky &amp;amp; Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SNIAFL: Towards a Static Non-Interactive Approach to Feature Location&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wei Zhao, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Lu Zhang, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Yin Liu, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Jiasu Sun, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Fuqing Yang, Peking University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Extending the REpresentational State Transfer (REST) Architectural Style for Decentralized Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rohit Khare &amp;amp; Richard N. Taylor, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Empirical Study of Software Reuse vs. Defect-Density and Stability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Parastoo Mohagheghi, Ericsson&lt;br /&gt;Reidar Conradi, Norwegian University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ole M. Killi, Norwegian University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Henrik Schwarz, Norwegian University of Science and Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Tool for Writing and Debugging Algebraic Specifications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Johannes Henkel &amp;amp; Amer Diwan, University of Colorado&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Static Checking of Dynamically Generated Queries in Database Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carl Gould, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Zhendong Su, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Premkumar Devanbu, University of California Davis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Precise Dynamic Slicing Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiangyu Zhang, University of Arizona&lt;br /&gt;Rajiv Gupta, University of Arizona&lt;br /&gt;Youtao Zhang, University of Arizona&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modular Verification of Software Components in C&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sagar Chaki, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Edmund Clarke, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Groce, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Somesh Jha, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Helmut Veith, Technische Universität Wien&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/11/best-paper-awards-ICSE/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/11/best-paper-awards-ICSE/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Software Engineering</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (MOBICOM)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SkyCore: Moving Core to the Edge for Untethered and Reliable UAV-based LTE Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mehrdad Moradi, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Karthikeyan Sundaresan, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Chai, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Sampath Rangarajan, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Z. Morley Mao, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;WEBee: Physical-Layer Cross-Technology Communication via Emulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhijun Li &amp;amp; Tian He, University of Minnesota&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CAreDroid: Adaptation Framework for Android ContextAware Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Salma Elmalaki, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Lucas Wanner, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Mani Srivastava, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tagoram: Real-Time Tracking of Mobile RFID Tags to High Precision Using COTS Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lei Yang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yekui Chen, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Xiang-Yang Li, Illinois Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Chaowei Xiao, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Mo Li, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Yunhao Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Whole-Home Gesture Recognition Using Wireless Signals&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Qifan Pu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Sidhant Gupta, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shwetak Patel, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Distinguishing Users with Capacitative Touch Communication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tam Vu, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Akash Baid, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Simon Gao, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Marco Gruteser, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Richard Howard, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Janne Lindqvist, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Predag Spasojevic, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Walling, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Driver Phone Use Leveraging Car Speakers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jie Yang, Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Simon Sdhom, Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Gayathri Chandrasekaran, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Tam Vu, Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hongbo Liu, Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nicolae Cecan, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Yingying Chen, Stevens Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Marco Gruteser, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Richard P. Martin, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;E-MiLi: Energy-Minimizing Idle Listening in Wireless Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xinyu Zhang &amp;amp; Kang G. Shin, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The κ factor: inferring protocol performance using inter-link reception correlation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kannan Srinivasan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mayank Jain, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jung Il Choi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Tahir Azim, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Edward S. Kim, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Philip Levis, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Bhaskar Krishnamachari, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CENTAUR: Realizing the Full Potential of Centralized WLANs through a Hybrid Data Path&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vivek Shrivastava, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Nabeel Ahmed, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Shravan Rayanchu, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Suman Banerjee, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Srinivasan Keshav, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Konstantina Papagiannaki, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Arunesh Mishra, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessment of Urban-Scale Wireless Networks with a Small Number of Measurements&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joshua Robinson, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Ram Swaminathan, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Edward W. Knightly, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-MOBICOM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-MOBICOM/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Mobile</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (KDD)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adversarial Attacks on Neural Networks for Graph Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Zügner, Technical University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Amir Akbarnejad, Technical University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Stephan Günnemann, Technical University of Munich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Accelerating Innovation Through Analogy Mining&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Hope, Hebrew University of Jerusalem&lt;br /&gt;Joel Chan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Aniket Kittur, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Dafna Shahaf, Hebrew University of Jerusalem&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FRAUDAR: Bounding Graph Fraud in the Face of Camouflage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryan Hooi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hyun Ah Song, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Beutel, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Neil Shah, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Kijung Shin, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Christos Faloutsos, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Algorithms for Public-Private Social Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Flavio Chierichetti, Sapienza University of Rome&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Epasto, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Kumar, Google&lt;br /&gt;Silvio Lattanzi, Google&lt;br /&gt;Vahab Mirrokni, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reducing the Sampling Complexity of Topic Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aaron Li, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Amr Ahmed, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sujith Ravi, Google&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Smola, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Simple and Deterministic Matrix Sketching&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edo Liberty, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Searching and Mining Trillions of Time Series Subsequences under Dynamic Time Warping&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thanawin Rakthanmanon, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Bilson Campana, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Abdullah Mueen, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Gustavo Batista, University of São Paulo&lt;br /&gt;Brandon Westover, Brigham and Women’s Hospital&lt;br /&gt;Qiang Zhu, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Jesin Zakaria, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Eamonn Keogh, University of California Riverside&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Leakage in Data Mining: Formulation, Detection, and Avoidance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shachar Kaufman, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Saharon Rosset, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Claudia Perlich, Media6Degrees&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Large linear classification when data cannot fit in memory&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hsiang-Fu Yu, National Taiwan University&lt;br /&gt;Cho-Jui Hsieh, National Taiwan University&lt;br /&gt;Kai-Wei Chang, National Taiwan University&lt;br /&gt;Chih-Jen Lin, National Taiwan University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Connecting the dots between news articles&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dafna Shahaf &amp;amp; Carlos Guestrin, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Collaborative Filtering with Temporal Dynamics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yehuda Koren, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fastanova: an efficient algorithm for genome-wide association study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiang Zhang, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Fei Zou, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Wei Wang, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predictive discrete latent factor models for large scale dyadic data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deepak Agarwal &amp;amp; Srujana Merugu, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Training linear SVMs in linear time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thorsten Joachims, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graphs over time: densification laws, shrinking diameters and possible explanations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jure Leskovec, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Christos Faloutsos, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A probabilistic framework for semi-supervised clustering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sugato Basu, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Mikhail Bilenko, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Raymond J. Mooney, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maximizing the spread of influence through a social network&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Kempe, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Éva Tardos, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pattern discovery in sequences under a Markov assumption&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Darya Chudova &amp;amp; Padhraic Smyth, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Robust space transformations for distance-based operations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edwin M. Knorr, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Raymond T. Ng, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Ruben H. Zamar, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hancock: a language for extracting signatures from data streams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Corinna Cortes, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen Fisher, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Daryl Pregibon, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Anne Rogers, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MetaCost: a general method for making classifiers cost-sensitive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pedro Domingos, Universidade Técnica de Lisboa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Occam’s Two Razors: The Sharp and the Blunt&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pedro Domingos, Universidade Técnica de Lisboa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Analysis and Visualization of Classifier Performance: Comparison under Imprecise Class and Cost Distributions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foster Provost &amp;amp; Tom Fawcett, NYNEX Science and Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-KDD/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-KDD/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Data Mining</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (INFOCOM)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;WiFED: WiFi Friendly Energy Delivery with Distributed Beamforming&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhramoy Mohanti, Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;Elif Bozkaya, Istanbul Technical University&lt;br /&gt;M. Yousof Naderi, Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;Berk Canberk, Istanbul Technical University&lt;br /&gt;Kaushik Chowdhury, Northeastern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Ethereum via Graph Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ting Chen, University of Electronic Science and Technology of China&lt;br /&gt;Yuxiao Zhu, Guangdong University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Zihao Li, University of Electronic Science and Technology of China&lt;br /&gt;Jiachi Chen, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoqi Li, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Xiapu Luo, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaodong Lin, Wilfrid Laurier University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaosong Zhang, University of Electronic Science and Technology of China&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimizing Age of Information in Wireless Networks with Throughput Constraints&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Igor Kadota, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Abhishek Sinha, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Eytan Modiano, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;One Step at a Time: Optimizing SDN Upgrades in ISP Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Konstantinos Poularakis, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;George Iosifidis, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Georgios Smaragdakis, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Leandros Tassiulas, Yale University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Heavy-Ball: A New Approach to Tame Delay and Convergence in Wireless Network Optimization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jia Liu, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Atilla Eryilmaz, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Ness B. Shroff, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Serena Bentley, Air Force Research Laboratory&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Power of Slightly More than One Sample in Randomized Load Balancing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lei Ying, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;R. Srikant, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Xiaohan Kang, Arizona State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joint Static and Dynamic Traffic Scheduling in Data Center Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zizhong Cao, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;br /&gt;M. Kodialam, Bell Labs&lt;br /&gt;T. V. Lakshman, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Performance Evaluation and Asymptotics for Content Delivery Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Virag Shah &amp;amp; Gustavo de Veciana, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Steady-State of Cache Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elisha J. Rosensweig, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Daniel S. Menasche, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Jim Kurose, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-resource allocation: Fairness-efficiency tradeoffs in a unifying framework&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carlee Joe-Wong, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Soumya Sen, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Tian Lan, George Washington University&lt;br /&gt;Mung Chiang, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic right-sizing for power-proportional data centers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minghong Lin, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Adam Wierman, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Lachlan Andrew, Swinburne University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Eno Thereska, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Feasibility and Efficacy of Protection Routing in IP Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kin-Wah Kwong, University of Pennsylvania&lt;br /&gt;Lixin Gao, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Roch Guérin, University of Pennsylvania&lt;br /&gt;Zhi-Li Zhang, University of Minnesota&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Queuing Network Models for Multi-Channel P2P Live Streaming Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Di Wu, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;br /&gt;Yong Liu, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;br /&gt;Keith W. Ross, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Feasibility of the Link Abstraction in (Rural) Mesh Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dattatraya Gokhal, Indian Navy&lt;br /&gt;Sayandeep Sen, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Kameswari Chebrolu, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bhaskaran Rama, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Theoretical Results on Base Station Movement Problem for Sensor Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yi Shi &amp;amp; Y. Thomas Hou, Virginia Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding the Capacity Region of the Greedy Maximal Scheduling Algorithm in Multi-hop Wireless Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Changhee Joo, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaojun Lin, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Ness B. Shroff, Ohio State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Disruption free topology reconfiguration in OSPF networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pierre Francois, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;br /&gt;Mike Shand, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Olicier Bonaventure, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Delay and Capacity Trade-offs in Mobile Ad Hoc Networks: A Global Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gaurav Sharma, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Mazumdar, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Ness Shroff, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Perfect Simulation and Stationarity of a Class of Mobility Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jean-Yves Le Boude, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Milan Vojnović, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Throughput-Delay Trade-Off in Wireless Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abbas El Gamal, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;James Mammen, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Balaji Prabhakar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Devavrat Shah, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;User-Level Performance of Channel-Aware Scheduling Algorithms in Wireless Data Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sem Borst, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Priority Service and Max-Min Fairness&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Marbach, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mobility increases the capacity of ad-hoc wireless networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthias Grossglauser, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;David Tse, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Chaotic Nature of TCP Congestion Control&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;András Veres, Ericsson&lt;br /&gt;Miklós Boda, Ericsson Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bandwidth Sharing: Objectives and Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laurent Massoulié, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;James Robert, France Telecom&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effective Bandwidths in Wireless Networks with Multiuser Receivers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Tse, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Hanly, University of Melbourne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An algorithm for multicast tree generation in networks with asymmetric links&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ram Ramanathan, BBN Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-INFOCOM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/10/best-paper-awards-INFOCOM/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Networking</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (PLDI)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Program synthesis using conflict-driven learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yu Feng, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Ruben Martins, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Osbert Bastani, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Isil Dillig, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The semantics of transactions and weak memory in x86, Power, ARM, and C++&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nathan Chong, ARM&lt;br /&gt;Tyler Sorensen, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;John Wickerson, Imperial College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A data-driven CHC solver&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;He Zhu, Galois&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Magill, Galois&lt;br /&gt;Suresh Jagannathan, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Low Overhead Dynamic Binary Translation on ARM&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanieu D’Antras, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Cosmin Gorgovan, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Jim Garside, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Mikel Luján, University of Manchester&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Repairing sequential consistency in C/C++11&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ori Lahav, MPI-SWS&lt;br /&gt;Viktor Vafeiadis, MPI-SWS&lt;br /&gt;Jeehoon Kang, Seoul National University&lt;br /&gt;Chung-Kil Hur, Seoul National University&lt;br /&gt;Derek Dreyer, MPI-SWS&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bringing the web up to speed with WebAssembly&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andreas Haas, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Rossberg, Google&lt;br /&gt;Derek L. Schuff, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ben L. Titzer, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michael Holman, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Dan Gohman, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;Luke Wagner, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;Alon Zakai, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;JF Bastien, Apple&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compiling without continuations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Luke Maurer, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Paul Downen, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Zena M. Ariola, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peyton Jones, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the limits of program-specific garbage collection performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicholas Jacek, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Meng-Chieh Chiu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Marlin, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Eliot Moss, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Into the Depths of C: Elaborating the De Facto Standards&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kayvan Memarian, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Justus Matthiesen, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;James Lingard, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Kyndylan Nienhuis, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;David Chisnall, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Robert N. M. Watson, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Peter Sewell, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Transactional Data Structure Libraries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alexander Spiegelman, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Guy Golan-Gueta, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Idit Keidar, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Types from data: Making structured data first-class citizens in F#&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tomas Petricek, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Gustavo Guerra, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Don Syme, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Provably Correct Peephole Optimizations with Alive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nuno P. Lopes, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;David Menendez, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Santosh Nagarakatte, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;John Regehr, University of Utah&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diagnosing Type Errors with Class&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Danfeng Zhang, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Dimitrios Vytiniotis, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peyton-Jones, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Improving Accuracy for Floating Point Expressions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pavel Panchekha, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Alex Sanchez-Stern, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James R. Wilcox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Zachary Tatlock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving JavaScript Performance by Deconstructing the Type System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wonsun Ahn, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Jiho Choi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Shull, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;María Garzarín, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Josep Torrellas, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compiler validation via equivalence modulo inputs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vu Le, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Mehrdad Afshari, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Zhendong Su, University of California Davis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Abstraction Refinement for Program Analyses in Datalog&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xin Zhang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Mangal, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Radu Grigore, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Mayur Naik, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hongseok Yang, Oxford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Static Analysis for Probabilistic Programs: Inferring Whole Program Properties from Finitely Many Path&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sriram Sankaranarayanan, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Aleksandar Chakarov, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Sumit Gulwani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A General Constraint-centric Scheduling Framework for Spatial Architectures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tony Nowatzki, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Sartin-Tarm, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo De Carli, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Karthikeyan Sankaralingam, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Cristian Estan, Broadcom&lt;br /&gt;Behnam Robatmili, Qualcomm Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reconciling Exhaustive Pattern Matching with Objects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chinawat Isradisaikul &amp;amp; Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CLAP: Recording Local Executions to Reproduce Concurrency Failures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeff Huang, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Charles Zhang, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Julian Dolby, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Concurrent Data Representation Synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Hawkins, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen Fisher, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Mooly Sagiv, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Representation Synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Hawkins, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen Fisher, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Mooly Sagiv, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Safe to the Last Instruction: Automated Verification of a Type-Safe Operating System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jean Yang, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Chris Hawblitzel, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Binary Analysis for Measurement and Attribution of Program Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nathan Tallent, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;John Mellor-Crummey, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Fagan, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fault-tolerant Typed Assembly Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Frances Perry, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Lester Mackey, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;George A. Reis, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Jay Ligatti, University of South Florida&lt;br /&gt;David I. August, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;David Walker, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Ant and the Grasshopper: Fast and Accurate Pointer Analysis for Millions of Lines of Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ben Hardekopf &amp;amp; Calvin Lin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Pool Allocation: Improving Performance by Controlling Data Structure Layout in the Heap&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Lattner &amp;amp; Vikram Adve, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Programming by Sketching for Bit-Streaming Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Armando Solar-Lezama, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Rodric Rabbah, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rastislav Bodik, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kemal Ebcioğlu, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cloning-Based Context-Sensitive Pointer Alias Analysis Using Binary Decision Diagrams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Whaley &amp;amp; Monica S. Lam, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Proving the Correctness of Compiler Optimizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sorin Lerner, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Todd Millstein, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Craig Chambers, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamo: a transparent dynamic optimization system&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vasanth Bala, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Duesterwald, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Sanjeev Banerjia, InCert&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Whole program paths&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James R. Larus, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-PLDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-PLDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Programming Languages</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (OSDI)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;REPT: Reverse Debugging of Failures in Deployed Software&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weidong Cui, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xinyang Ge, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Baris Kasikci, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ben Niu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Upamanyu Sharma, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ruoyu Wang, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Insu Yun, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Orca: Differential Bug Localization in Large-Scale Services&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjita Bhagwan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rahul Kumar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Chandra Sekhar Maddila, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Adithya Abraham Philip, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;LegoOS: A Disseminated, Distributed OS for Hardware Resource Disaggregation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yizhou Shan, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yutong Huang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yilun Chen, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yiying Zhang, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryoan: A Distributed Sandbox for Untrusted Computation on Secret Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tyler Hunt, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Zhiting Zhu, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Yuanzhong Xu, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peter, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Emmett Witchel, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Push-Button Verification of File Systems via Crash Refinement&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Helgi Sigurbjarnarson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Bornholt, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Emina Torlak, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Xi Wang, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Early Detection of Configuration Errors to Reduce Failure Damage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tianyin Xu, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Xinxin Jin, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Peng Huang, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Yuanyuan Zhou, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shan Lu, University of Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Long Jin, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Pasupathy, NetApp&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shielding Applications from an Untrusted Cloud with Haven&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Baumann, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Marcus Peinado, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Galen Hunt, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IX: A Protected Dataplane Operating System for High Throughput and Low Latency&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adam Belay, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;George Prekas, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Ana Klimovic, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Samuel Grossman, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christos Kozyrakis, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Edouard Bugnion, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Arrakis: The Operating System is the Control Plane&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Simon Peter, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jialin Li, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Irene Zhang, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dan Ports, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Doug Woos, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Roscoe, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spanner: Google’s Globally-Distributed Database&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James C. Corbett, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michael Epstein, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fikes, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Frost, Google&lt;br /&gt;JJ Furman, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Ghemawat, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrey Gubarev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Heiser, Google&lt;br /&gt;Peter Hochschild, Google&lt;br /&gt;Wilson Hsieh, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Kanthak, Google&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Kogan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Hongyi Li, Google&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Lloyd, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sergey Melnik, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Mwaura, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Nagle, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sean Quinlan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Rajesh Rao, Google&lt;br /&gt;Lindsay Rolig, Google&lt;br /&gt;Yasushi Saito, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michal Szymaniak, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Taylor, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ruth Wang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Dale Woodford, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient System-Enforced Deterministic Parallelism&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amittai Aviram, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Shu-Chun Weng, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Sen Hu, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Ford, Yale University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Turtles Project: Design and Implementation of Nested Virtualization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Muli Ben-Yehuda, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Day, IBM&lt;br /&gt;Zvi Dubitzky, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Factor, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Nadav Har’El, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Abel Gordon, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Liguori, IBM&lt;br /&gt;Orit Wasserman, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ben-Ami Yassour, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;KLEE: Unassisted and Automatic Generation of High-Coverage Tests for Complex Systems Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristian Cadar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Dunbar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Difference Engine: Harnessing Memory Redundancy in Virtual Machines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diwaker Gupta, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Sangmin Lee, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Vrable, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Stefan Savage, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Alex C. Snoeren, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;George Varghese, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey M. Voelker, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DryadLINQ: A System for General-Purpose Distributed Data-Parallel Computing Using a High-Level Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuan Yu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Isard, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Dennis Fetterly, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mihai Budiu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Úlfar Erlingsson, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Pradeep Kumar Gunda, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Currey, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bigtable: A Distributed Storage System for Structured Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fay Chang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Ghemawat, Google&lt;br /&gt;Wilson C. Hsieh, Google&lt;br /&gt;Deborah A. Wallach, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mike Burrows, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tushar Chandra, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fikes, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robert E. Gruber, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rethink the Sync&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edmund B. Nightingale, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Kaushik Veeraraghavan, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Peter M. Chen, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jason Flinn, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Model Checking to Find Serious File System Errors	Junfeng Yang, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul Twohey, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Madanlal Musuvathi, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recovering Device Drivers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael M. Swift, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Muthukaruppan Annamalai, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brian N. Bershad, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry M. Levy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Memory Resource Management in VMware ESX Server&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carl A. Waldspurger, VMware&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Checking System Rules Using System-Specific, Programmer-Written Compiler Extensions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Chelf, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Andy Chou, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Seth Hallem, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IO-Lite: A Unified I/O Buffering and Caching System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vivek S. Pai, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Druschel, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Willy Zwaenepoel, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Compiler-Inserted I/O Prefetching for Out-of-Core Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Todd C. Mowry, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Angela K. Demke, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Orran Krieger, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Safe Kernel Extensions Without Run-Time Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;George C. Necula &amp;amp; Peter Lee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-OSDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-OSDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Operating Systems</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (NSDI)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;NetChain: Scale-Free Sub-RTT Coordination&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xin Jin, Johns Hopkins University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaozhou Li, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Haoyu Zhang, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Nate Foster, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Jeongkeun Lee, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Robert Soulé, Università della Svizzera italiana&lt;br /&gt;Changhoon Kim, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;mOS: A Reusable Networking Stack for Flow Monitoring Middleboxes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Muhammad Asim Jamshed, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;YoungGyoun Moon, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Donghwi Kim, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Dongsu Han, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;KyoungSoo Park, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Passive Wi-Fi: Bringing Low Power to Wi-Fi Transmissions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryce Kellogg, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua R. Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Queues Don’t Matter When You Can JUMP Them!&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew P. Grosvenor, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Malte Schwarzkopf, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Ionel Gog, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Robert N. M. Watson, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Andrew W. Moore, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Steven Hand, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Jon Crowcroft, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Distributed Systems Using Approximate Synchrony in Data Center Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan R. K. Ports, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jialin Li, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Naveen Kr. Sharma, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Design and Implementation of Open vSwitch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ben Pfaff, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Justin Pettit, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Teemu Koponen, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Ethan J. Jackson, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Andy Zhou, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jarno Rajahalme, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jesse Gross, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Alex Wang, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Stringer, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Pravin Shelar, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Keith Amidon, Awake Networks&lt;br /&gt;Martín Casado, VMware&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Software Dataplane Verification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mihai Dobrescu &amp;amp; Katerina Argyraki, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Embassies: Radically Refactoring the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jon Howell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Parno, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;John R. Douceur, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Fault-Tolerant Engineered Network&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Halperin, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Resilient Distributed Datasets: A Fault-Tolerant Abstraction for In-Memory Cluster Computing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matei Zaharia, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Mosharaf Chowdhury, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Tathagata Das, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ankur Dave, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Justin Ma, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Murphy McCauley, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Michael J. Franklin, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design, Implementation and Evaluation of Congestion Control for Multipath TCP&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Damon Wischik, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Costin Raiciu, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Adam Greenhalgh, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Mark Handley, University College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ServerSwitch: A Programmable and High Performance Platform for Data Center Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Guohan Lu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Chuanxiong Guo, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yulong Li, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Zhiqiang Zhou, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Tong Yuan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haitao Wu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yongqiang Xiong, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rui Gao, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yongguang Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reverse traceroute&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan Katz-Bassett, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Harsha V. Madhyastha, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Vijay Kumar Adhikari, University of Minnesota&lt;br /&gt;Colin Scott, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Justine Sherry, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Peter van Wesep, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sora: High Performance Software Radio Using General Purpose Multi-core Processors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kun Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jiansong Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Ji Fang, Beijing Jiaotong University&lt;br /&gt;He Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yusheng Ye, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Shen Wang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yongguang Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haitao Wu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Wei Wang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey M. Voelker, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;TrInc: Small Trusted Hardware for Large Distributed Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dave Levin, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;John R. Douceur, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jacob R. Lorch, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Moscibroda, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Remus: High Availability via Asynchronous Virtual Machine Replication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brendan Cully, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey Lefebvre, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Dutch Meyer, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Mike Feeley, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Norm Hutchinson, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Warfield, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consensus Routing: The Internet as a Distributed System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John P. John, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Ethan Katz-Bassett, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arun Venkataramani, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Life, Death, and the Critical Transition: Finding Liveness Bugs in Systems Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charles Killian, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;James W. Anderson, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Ranjit Jhala, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Experience with an Object Reputation System for Peer-to-Peer Filesharing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin Walsh &amp;amp; Emin Gün Sirer, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Replay Debugging for Distributed Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dennis Geels, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Gautam Altekar, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting BGP Configuration Faults with Static Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nick Feamster &amp;amp; Hari Balakrishnan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trickle: A Self-Regulating Algorithm for Code Propagation and Maintenance in Wireless Sensor Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Philip Levis, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Neil Patel, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Culler, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-NSDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-NSDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Networking</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (SIGCOMM)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Inferring Persistent Interdomain Congestion&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Saksham Agarwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Shijin Rajakrishnan, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Akshay Narayan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rachit Agarwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;David Shmoys, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Re-architecting datacenter networks and stacks for low latency and high performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Handley, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Costin Raiciu, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Alexandru Agache, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Andrei Voinescu, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Moore, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Gianni Antichi, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Marcin Wójcik, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Language-directed hardware design for network performance monitoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Srinivas Narayana, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Anirudh Sivaraman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Vikram Nathan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Prateesh Goyal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Venkat Arun, IIT Guwahati&lt;br /&gt;Mohammad Alizadeh, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Vimalkumar Jeyakumar, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Changhoon Kim, Barefoot Networks&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eliminating Channel Feedback in Next-Generation Cellular Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deepak Vasisht, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Swarun Kumar, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hariharan Rahul, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Inter-Technology Backscatter: Towards Internet Connectivity for Implanted Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vikram Iyer, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Bryce Kellogg, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Don’t Mind the Gap: Bridging Network-wide Objectives and Device-level Configurations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryan Beckett, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Ratul Mahajan, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Todd Millstein, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Jitendra Padhye, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;David Walker, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Central Control Over Distributed Routing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefano Vissicchio, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Tilmans, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;br /&gt;Laurent Vanbever, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Rexford, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Balancing Accountability and Privacy in the Network&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Naylor, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Matthew K. Mukerjee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Steenkiste, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CONGA: Distributed Congestion-Aware Load Balancing for Datacenters&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohammad Alizadeh, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Tom Edsall, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Sarang Dharmapurikar, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Ramanan Vaidyanathan, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Chu, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Andy Fingerhut, Google&lt;br /&gt;Terry Lam, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Francis Matus, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Rong Pan, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Navindra Yadav, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;George Varghese, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ambient Backscatter: Wireless Communication Out of Thin Air&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Parks, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David Wetherall, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua R. Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-Resource Fair Queueing for Packet Processing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ali Ghodsi, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Vyas Sekar, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Matei Zaharia, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;They Can Hear Your Heartbeats: Non-Invasive Security for Implanted Medical Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Haitham Hassanieh, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Ransford, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Fu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Error Estimating Coding: Feasibility and Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Binbin Chen, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Ziling Chou, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Yuda Zhao, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Haifeng Yu, National University of Singapore&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;White Space Networking with Wi-Fi like Connectivity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paramvir Bahl, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Ranveer Chandra, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Moscibroda, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rohan Murty, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Matt Welsh, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ZigZag Decoding: Combating Hidden Terminals in Wireless Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota &amp;amp; Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-SIGCOMM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-SIGCOMM/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Networking</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (S&amp;P)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DEEPSEC: Deciding Equivalence Properties in Security Protocols – Theory and Practice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Cheval, Inria&lt;br /&gt;Steve Kremer, Inria&lt;br /&gt;Itsaka Rakotonirina, Inria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Enforcing the Digital Immunity of a Large Humanitarian Organization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stevens Le Blond, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Alejandro Cuevas, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Juan Ramón Troncoso-Pastoriza, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Philipp Jovanovic, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Ford, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Pierre Hubaux, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verified Models and Reference Implementations for the TLS 1.3 Standard Candidate&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Karthikeyan Bhargavan, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Blanchet, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Nadim Kobeissi, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A2: Analog Malicious Hardware&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiyuan Yang, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Hicks, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Qing Dong, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Todd Austin, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Dennis Sylvester, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Riposte: An Anonymous Messaging System Handling Millions of Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Henry Corrigan-Gibbs, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Boneh, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;David Mazières, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Messy State of the Union: Taming the Composite State Machines of TLS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benjamin Beurdouche, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Karthikeyan Bhargavan, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Antoine Delignat-Lavaud, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Cédric Fournet, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Markulf Kohlweiss, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alfredo Pironti, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Pierre-Yves Strub, IMDEA&lt;br /&gt;Jean Karim Zinzindohoue, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Secure Multiparty Computations on BitCoin&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcin Andrychowicz, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Stefan Dziembowski, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Malinowski, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Łukasz Mazurek, University of Warsaw&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bootstrapping Privacy Compliance in Big Data Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shayak Sen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Saikat Guha, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Anupam Datta, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Sriram K. Rajamani, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Janice Tsai, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jeannette M. Wing, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pinocchio: Nearly Practical Verifiable Computation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryan Parno, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Craig Gentry, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Howell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mariana Raykova, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Don’t Trust Satellite Phones: A Security Analysis of Two Satphone Standards&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benedikt Driessen, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Ralf Hund, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Willems, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Christof Paar, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Thorsten Holz, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Phonotactic Reconstruction of Encrypted VoIP Conversations: Hookt on fon-iks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew M. White, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Austin Matthews, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Snow, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Fabian Monrose, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SCiFI - A System for Secure Face Identification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Margarita Osadchy, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Benny Pinkas, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Ayman Jarrous, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Boaz Moskovich, University of Haifa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Native Client: A Sandbox for Portable, Untrusted x86 Native Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bennet Yee, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Sehr, Google&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Dardyk, Google&lt;br /&gt;Bradley Chen, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robert Muth, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tavis Ormandy, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiki Okasaka, Google&lt;br /&gt;Neha Narula, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Fullagar, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pacemakers and Implantable Cardiac Defibrillators: Software Radio Attacks and Zero-Power Defenses&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Halperin, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas S. Heydt-Benjamin, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Ransford, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Shane S. Clark, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benessa Defend, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Will Morgan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Fu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Tadayoshi Kohno, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;William H. Maisel, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-S&P/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-S&P/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Security and Privacy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
