<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PXZHANG</title>
    <description>这里是 @PXZHANG张培歆 的个人网站</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 22:25:30 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 22:25:30 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1998-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HighLife: Higher-arity Fact Harvesting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patrick Ernst, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;br /&gt;Amy Siu, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard Weikum, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Social Networks Under Stress&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Romero, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Brian Uzzi, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HypTrails: A Bayesian Approach for Comparing Hypotheses About Human Trails on the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Philipp Singer, GESIS - Leibniz Institute for the Social Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Denis Helic, Graz University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Hotho, University of Würzburg&lt;br /&gt;Markus Strohmaier, GESIS - Leibniz Institute for the Social Sciences&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Estimation for High Similarities using Odd Sketches&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Mitzenmacher, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Rasmus Pagh, IT University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Ninh Pham, IT University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;No Country for Old Members: User Lifecycle and Linguistic Change in Online Communities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristian Danescu-Niculescu-Mizil, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Robert West, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Jurafsky, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jure Leskovec, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Potts, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Counting Beyond a Yottabyte, or how SPARQL 1.1 Property Paths will Prevent Adoption of the Standard&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcelo Arenas, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Sebastián Conca, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Jorge Pérez, Universidad de Chile&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards a theory model for product search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beibei Li, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Anindya Ghose, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Panagiotis G. Ipeirotis, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Factorizing personalized Markov chains for next-basket recommendation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steffen Rendle, Osaka University&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Freudenthaler, University of Hildesheim&lt;br /&gt;Lars Schmidt-Thieme, University of Hildesheim&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hybrid keyword search auctions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ashish Goel, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kamesh Munagala, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IRLbot: Scaling to 6 billion pages and beyond&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hsin-Tsang Lee, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Derek Leonard, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoming Wang, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Dmitri Loguinov, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wherefore art thou r3579x?: anonymized social networks, hidden patterns, and structural steganography&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lars Backstrom, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Cynthia Dwork, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Random Sampling from a Search Engine’s Index&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ziv Bar-Yossef &amp;amp; Maxim Gurevich, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Three-level caching for efficient query processing in large Web search engines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiaohui Long &amp;amp; Torsten Suel, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic detection of fragments in dynamically generated web pages&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lakshmish Ramaswamy, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Arun Iyengar, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ling Liu, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Fred Douglis, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scaling personalized web search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Glen Jeh &amp;amp; Jennifer Widom, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SemTag and seeker: bootstrapping the semantic web via automated semantic annotation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Dill, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Nadav Eiron, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;David Gibson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Gruhl, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;R. Guha, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Anant Jhingran, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Tapas Kanungo, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sridhar Rajagopalan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Tomkins, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;John A. Tomlin, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Jason Y. Zien, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abstracting application-level web security&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Scott &amp;amp; Richard Sharp, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Engineering Server Driven Consistency for Large Scale Dynamic Web Services&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian Yin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo Alvisi, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Mike Dahlin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Arun Iyengar, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graph Structure in the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei Broder, AltaVista&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Kumar, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Farzin Maghoul, AltaVista&lt;br /&gt;Prabhakar Raghavan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sridhar Rajagopalan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Raymie Stata, Compaq Systems Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Tomkins, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Janet Wiener, Compaq Systems Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Focused Crawling: A New Approach to Topic-Specific Web Resource Discovery&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Soumen Chakrabarti, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Martin van den Berg, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;br /&gt;Byron Dom, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Interactive Multimedia Jukebox (IMJ): a new paradigm for the on-demand delivery of audio/video&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin C. Almeroth, University of California Santa Barbara&lt;br /&gt;Mostafa H. Ammar, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-WWW/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-WWW/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>World Wide Web</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1999-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Delayed Impact of Fair Machine Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lydia T. Liu, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Dean, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Esther Rolf, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Max Simchowitz, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Moritz Hardt, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Obfuscated Gradients Give a False Sense of Security: Circumventing Defenses to Adversarial Examples&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anish Athalye, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Carlini, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Wagner, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Black-box Predictions via Influence Functions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pang Wei Koh &amp;amp; Percy Liang, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ensuring Rapid Mixing and Low Bias for Asynchronous Gibbs Sampling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher De Sa, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Re, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kunle Olukotun, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Pixel Recurrent Neural Networks&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Van den Oord, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nal Kalchbrenner, Google&lt;br /&gt;Koray Kavukcuoglu, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dueling Network Architectures for Deep Reinforcement Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ziyu Wang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tom Schaul, Google&lt;br /&gt;Matteo Hessel, Google&lt;br /&gt;Hado van Hasselt, Google&lt;br /&gt;Marc Lanctot, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nando de Freitas, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Nearly-Linear Time Framework for Graph-Structured Sparsity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chinmay Hegde, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Piotr Indyk, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ludwig Schmid, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal and Adaptive Algorithms for Online Boosting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alina Beygelzimer, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Satyen Kale, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Haipeng Luo, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding the Limiting Factors of Topic Modeling via Posterior Contraction Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian Tang, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Zhaoshi Meng, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;XuanLong Nguyen, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Qiaozhu Mei, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ming Zhang, Peking University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vanishing Component Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Roi Livni, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;br /&gt;David Lehavi, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Sagi Schein, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Hila Nachlieli, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Shai Shalev Shwartz, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;br /&gt;Amir Globerson, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Semidifferential-based Submodular Function Optimization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rishabh Iyer, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Stefanie Jegelka, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Bilmes, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Posterior Sampling via Stochastic Gradient Fisher Scoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sungjin Ahn, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Anoop Korattikara, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Max Welling, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computational Rationalization: The Inverse Equilibrium Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin Waugh, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Brian Ziebart, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Drew Bagnell, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hilbert Space Embeddings of Hidden Markov Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Le Song, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Byron Boots, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Sajid M. Siddiqi, Google&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey Gordon, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Smola, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Structure preserving embedding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Blake Shaw &amp;amp; Tony Jebara, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SVM Optimization: Inverse Dependence on Training Set Size&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shai Shalev-Shwartz &amp;amp; Nathan Srebro, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Information-theoretic metric learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jason V. Davis, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Brian Kulis, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Prateek Jain, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Suvrit Sra, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Inderjit S. Dhillon, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trading convexity for scalability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ronan Collobert, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Fabian Sinz, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Jason Weston, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Léon Bottou, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A support vector method for multivariate performance measures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thorsten Joachims, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Least-Squares Temporal Difference Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin A. Boyan, NASA Ames Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICML/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICML/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Machine Learning</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1998-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mask R-CNN&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Georgia Gkioxari, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Piotr Dollar, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Ross Girshick, Facebook AI Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deep Neural Decision Forests&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Kontschieder, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Madalina Fiterau, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Antonio Criminisi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Samuel Rota Bulò, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Large Scale Image Categorization to Entry-Level Categories&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vicente Ordonez, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Jia Deng, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Yejin Choi, Stony Brook University&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Berg, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Tamara Berg, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Relative Attributes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Devi Parikh, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Kristen Grauman, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discriminative models for multi-class object layout&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chaitanya Desai, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Deva Ramanan, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Charless Fowlkes, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Population Shape Regression From Random Design Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bradley Davis, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;P. Thomas Fletcher, University of Utah&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Bullitt, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Sarang Joshi, University of Utah&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Globally Optimal Estimates for Geometric Reconstruction Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fredrik Kahl, Lund University&lt;br /&gt;Didier Henrion, LAAS-CNRS&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Pedestrians using Patterns of Motion and Appearance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul Viola, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael J. Jones, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Snow, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Image Parsing: Unifying Segmentation, Detection and Recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhuowen Tu, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Xiangrong Chen, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Alan L. Yuille, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Song-Chun Zhu, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Image-based Rendering using Image-based Priors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Yonatan Wexler, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Probabilistic Tracking with Exemplars in a Metric Space&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kentaro Toyama &amp;amp; Andrew Blake, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Space of All Stereo Images&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steven Seitz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Euclidean Reconstruction and Reprojection up to Subgroups&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yi Ma, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Stefano Soatto, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Jana Kosecka, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Sastry, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Theory of Shape by Space Carving&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kiriakos Kutulakos, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Steven Seitz, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Self-Calibration and Metric Reconstruction in spite of Varying and Unknown Internal Camera Parameters&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marc Pollefeys, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Reinhard Koch, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Luc Van Gool, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Problem of Degeneracy in Structure and Motion Recovery from Uncalibrated Image Sequences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Phil Torr, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICCV/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICCV/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Computer Vision</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2002-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adversarial Symbolic Execution for Detecting Concurrency-Related Cache Timing Leaks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shengjian (Daniel) Guo, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Meng Wu, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Chao Wang, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Empirical Study on Crash Recovery Bugs in Large-Scale Distributed Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yu Gao, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Wensheng Dou, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Feng Qin, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Chushu Gao, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Dong Wang, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Jun Wei, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Ruirui Huang, Alibaba Group&lt;br /&gt;Li Zhou, Alibaba Group&lt;br /&gt;Yongming Wu, Alibaba Group&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Race Detection on Compressed Traces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dileep Kini, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Umang Mathur, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Mahesh Viswanathan, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oreo: Detection of Clones in the Twilight Zone&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vaibhav Saini, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Farima Farmahinifarahani, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Yadong Lu, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Baldi, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Crista Lopes, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Impact of Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Practice: An Empirical Study at the Ecosystem Scale&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James C. Davis, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Christy A. Coghlan, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Francisco Servant, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Dongyoon Lee, Virginia Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Do Android Taint Analysis Tools Keep Their Promises?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Felix Pauck, Paderborn University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Bodden, Paderborn University&lt;br /&gt;Heike Wehrheim, Paderborn University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Power of “Why” and “Why Not”: Enriching Scenario Exploration with Provenance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tim Nelson, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Natasha Danas, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel J. Dougherty, Worcester Polytechnic Institute&lt;br /&gt;Shriram Krishnamurthi, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cooperative Kernels: GPU Multitasking for Blocking Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tyler Sorensen, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Hugues Evrard, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Alastair F. Donaldson, Imperial College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Misunderstandings in Source Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Gopstein, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Jake Iannacone, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Yu Yan, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Lois DeLong, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Yanyan Zhuang, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Martin K.-C. Yeh, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Justin Cappos, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trade-Offs in Continuous Integration: Assurance, Security, and Flexibility&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Hilton, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Nelson, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Tunnell, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Danny Dig, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discovering Relational Specifications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Calvin Smith, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Gabriel Ferns, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Aws Albarghouthi, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Diagnosing and Repairing Error Handling Bugs in C&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuchi Tian &amp;amp; Baishakhi Ray, University of Virginia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fairness Testing: Testing Software for Discrimination&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sainyam Galhotra, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Yuriy Brun, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Meliou, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foraging and Navigations Fundamentally: Developers’ Predictions of Value and Cost&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Piorkowski, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Austin Z. Henley, University of Memphis&lt;br /&gt;Tahmid Nabi, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Scott D. Fleming, University of Memphis&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Scaffidi, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Margaret Burnett, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-Representational Security Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eunsuk Kang, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Aleksandar Milicevic, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jackson, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Factors Influencing Code Review Processes in Industry&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tobias Baum, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Olga Liskin, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Kai Niklas, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Kurt Schneider, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;API Code Recommendation Using Statistical Learning from Fine-grained Changes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anh Tuan Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Hilton, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Mihai Codoban, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Hoan Anh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Lily Mast, University of Evansville&lt;br /&gt;Eli Rademacher, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Tien N. Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Danny Dig, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proteus: Computing Disjunctive Loop Summary via Path Dependency Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiaofei Xie, Tianjin University&lt;br /&gt;Bihuan Chen, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Yang Liu, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Wei Le, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaohong Li, Tianjin University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Why We Refactor? Confessions of GitHub Contributors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Danilo Silva, Federal University of Minas Gerais&lt;br /&gt;Nikolaos Tsantalis, Concordia University&lt;br /&gt;Marco Tulio Valente, Federal University of Minas Gerais&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Sensitive Data Disclosure via Bi-directional Text Correlation Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jianjun Huang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Xiangyu Zhang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Lin Tan, University of Waterloo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimizing energy consumption of GUIs in Android apps: a multi-objective approach&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mario Linares-Vásquez, College of William and Mary&lt;br /&gt;Gabriele Bavota, Free University of Bolzano&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Eduardo Bernal Cárdenas, College of William and Mary&lt;br /&gt;Rocco Oliveto, University of Molise&lt;br /&gt;Massimiliano Di Penta, University of Sannio&lt;br /&gt;Denys Poshyvanyk, College of William and Mary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Practitioners Perceive the Relevance of Software Engineering Research&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Lo, Singapore Management University&lt;br /&gt;Nachiappan Nagappan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effective Test Suites for Mixed Discrete-Continuous Stateflow Controllers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reza Matinnejad, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Shiva Nejati, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Lionel C. Briand, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Bruckmann, Delphi Automotive Systems&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modeling Readability to Improve Unit Tests&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ermira Daka, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;José Campos, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Gordon Fraser, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Dorn, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;Westley Weimer, University of Virginia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Measure It? Manage It? Ignore It? Software Practitioners and Technical Debt&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neil A. Ernst, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Stephany Bellomo, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ipek Ozkaya, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Robert L. Nord, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ian Gorton, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A User-Guided Approach to Program Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ravi Mangal, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Xin Zhang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Aditya V. Nori, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mayur Naik, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MultiSE: Multi-path Symbolic Execution using Value Summaries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;George Necula, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Liang Gong, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Wontae Choi, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Users Beware: Preference Inconsistencies Ahead&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farnaz Behrang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Myra B. Cohen, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Orso, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Selection and Presentation Practices for Code Example Summarization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Annie Ying &amp;amp; Martin Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Are Mutants a Valid Substitute for Real Faults in Software Testing?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;René Just, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Darioush Jalali, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Laura Inozemtseva, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Michael Ernst, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Reid Holmes, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Gordon Fraser, University of Sheffield&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;AI: A Lightweight System for Tolerating Concurrency Bugs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mingxing Zhang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yongwei Wu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Shan Lu, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Shanxiang Qi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Jinglei Ren, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Weimin Zheng, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Powering the Static Driver Verifier using Corral&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Akash Lal &amp;amp; Shaz Qadeer, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Natural Coding Conventions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Miltiadis Allamanis, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Earl T. Barr, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Christian Bird, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Charles Sutton, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Architecture Challenges for Internal Software Ecosystems: A Large-Scale Industry Case Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Klaus-Benedikt Schultis, Siemens Corporate Technology&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Elsner, Siemens Corporate Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Lohmann, Friedrich-Alexander University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Seeking the Ground Truth: A Retroactive Study on the Evolution and Migration of Software Libraries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bradley Cossette &amp;amp; Robert Walker, University of Calgary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scalable Test Data Generation from Multidimensional Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emina Torlak, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the Value of Branches with What-if Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Bird &amp;amp; Thomas Zimmermann, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proactive Detection of Collaboration Conflicts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuriy Brun, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Reid Holmes, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David Notkin, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Do Fixes Become Bugs?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zuoning Yin, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Ding Yuan, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Yuanyuan Zhou, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Pasupathy, NetApp&lt;br /&gt;Lakshmi Bairavasundaram, NetApp&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proving programs robust&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Swarat Chaudhuri, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Sumit Gulwani, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Roberto Lublinerman, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Sara Navidpour, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Creating and evolving developer documentation: understanding the decisions of open source contributors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barthélémy Dagenais &amp;amp; Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Developer Fluency: Achieving True Mastery in Software Projects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minghui Zhou, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Audris Mockus, Avaya Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Staged Concurrent Program Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nishant Sinha &amp;amp; Chao Wang, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Asserting and checking determinism for multithreaded programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Burnim &amp;amp; Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Darwin: an approach for debugging evolving programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dawei Qi, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Abhik Roychoudhury, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Zhenkai Liang, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Kapil Vaswani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graph-based Mining of Multiple Object Usage Patterns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tung Thanh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Hoan Anh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Nam H. Pham, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Jafar M. Al-Kofahi, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Tien N. Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What makes a good bug report?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Bettenburg, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Sascha Just, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Adrian Schröter, University of Victoria&lt;br /&gt;Cathrin Weiss, University of Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Rahul Premraj, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, University of Calgary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient online monitoring of web-service SLAs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Franco Raimondi, University College London&lt;br /&gt;James Skene, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Wolfgang Emmerich, University College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic consistency assessment for query results in dynamic environments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jamie Payton, University of North Carolina at Charlotte&lt;br /&gt;Christine Julien, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Gruia-Catalin Roman, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Globally distributed software development project performance: an empirical analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Narayan Ramasubbu &amp;amp; Rajesh Krishna Balan, Singapore Management University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mining specifications of malicious behavior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mihai Christodorescu, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Somesh Jha, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Kruegel, Vienna University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object and reference immutability using Java generics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yoav Zibin, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alex Potanin, Victoria University of Wellington&lt;br /&gt;Mahmood Ali, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Shay Artzi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Adam Kieżun, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Controlling factors in evaluating path-sensitive error detection techniques&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew B. Dwyer, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Suzette Person, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Elbaum, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SYNERGY: a new algorithm for property checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bhargav S. Gulavani, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Thomas A. Henzinger, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Yamini Kannan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Aditya V. Nori, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Sriram K. Rajamani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Generation of Suggestions for Program Investigation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CUTE: a concolic unit testing engine for C&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koushik Sen, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Gul Agha, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Context- and path-sensitive memory leak detection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yichen Xie &amp;amp; Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reasoning about partial goal satisfaction for requirements and design engineering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emmanuel Letier &amp;amp; Axel van Lamsweerde, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A classification system and analysis for aspect-oriented programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alexandru Salcianu, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Suhabe Bugrara, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eliminating redundancies with a “composition with adaptation” meta-programming technique&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stan Jarzabek, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Li Shubiao, Xi’an Jiaotong University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Family of Test Adequacy Criteria for Database-Driven Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gregory M. Kapfhammer &amp;amp; Mary Lou Soffa, University of Pittsburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting problems caused by component upgrades&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen McCamant &amp;amp; Michael D. Ernst, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Isolating Cause-Effect Chains from Computer Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andreas Zeller, Saarland University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-FSE/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-FSE/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Software Engineering</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2000-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Classical Verification of Quantum Computation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Urmila Mahadev, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximating Edit Distance Within Constant Factor in Truly Sub-Quadratic Time	Diptarka&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chakraborty, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Debarati Das, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Elazar Goldenberg, The Academic College Of Tel Aviv-Yaffo&lt;br /&gt;Michal Koucký, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Saks, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pseudorandom Sets in Grassmann Graph have Near-Perfect Expansion&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash Khot, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Dor Minzer, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Muli Safra, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A dichotomy theorem for nonuniform CSPs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei A. Bulatov, Simon Fraser University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Matching Problem in General Graphs is in Quasi-NC&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ola Svensson &amp;amp; Jakub Tarnawski, École polytechnique fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Proof of CSP Dichotomy Conjecture&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dmitriy Zhuk, Lomonosov Moscow State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Settling the Complexity of Computing Approximate Two-Player Nash Equilibria&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aviad Rubinstein, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Learning Requires Good Memory: A Time-Space Lower Bound for Parity Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An average-case depth hierarchy theorem for Boolean circuits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benjamin Rossman, National Institute of Informatics&lt;br /&gt;Rocco A. Servedio, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Li-Yang Tan, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Path Finding Methods for Linear Programming: Solving Linear Programs in O(sqrt(rank)) Iterations and Faster Algorithms for Maximum Flow&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yin Tat Lee &amp;amp; Aaron Sidford, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Navigating Central Path with Electrical Flows: from Flows to Matchings, and Back&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aleksander Mądry, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A multi-prover interactive proof for NEXP sound against entangled provers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tsuyoshi Ito, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Vidick, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Polylogarithimic Approximation Algorithm for Edge-Disjoint Paths with Congestion 2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julia Chuzhoy, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Shi Li, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Randomized Rounding Approach to the Traveling Salesman Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shayan Oveis Gharan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Amin Saberi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mohit Singh, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Polylogarithmic-Competitive Algorithm for the k-Server Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nikhil Bansal, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Niv Buchbinder, Open University&lt;br /&gt;Aleksander Mądry, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Naor, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximating Graphic TSP by Matchings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tobia M¨o;mke &amp;amp; Ola Svensson, Royal Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximation Algorithms for the Edge-Disjoint Paths Problem via Raecke Decompositions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Andrews, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subexponential Algorithms for Unique Games and Related Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sanjeev Arora, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Boaz Barak, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;David Steurer, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computational Transition at the Uniqueness Threshold&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Allan Sly, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Two Query PCP with Sub-Constant Error&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dana Moshkovitz &amp;amp; Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Space-Efficient Identity Based Encryption Without Pairings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Boneh, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Craig Gentry, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Hamburg, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Settling the Complexity of 2-Player Nash Equilibrium&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xi Chen, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaotie Deng, City University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Unique Games Conjecture, Integrality Gap for Cut Problems and Embeddability of Negative Type Metrics into L1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash A. Khot, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nisheeth K. Vishnoi, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Correcting Errors Beyond the Guruswami-Sudan Radius in Polynomial Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farzad Parvaresh &amp;amp; Alexander Vardy, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cryptography in NC0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benny Applebaum, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Yuval Ishai, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Eyal Kushilevitz, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hardness of Approximating the Shortest Vector Problem in Lattices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash Khot, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Impossibility of Dimension Reduction in L1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bo Brinkman &amp;amp; Moses Charikar, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Dichotomy Theorem for Constraints on a Three-Element Set&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei A. Bulatov, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minimizing Congestion in General Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Harald Räcke, Paderborn University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constant-Round Coin-Tossing with a Man in the Middle or Realizing the Shared Random String Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Boaz Barak, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-FOCS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-FOCS/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Theory</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2000-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Taskonomy: Disentangling Task Transfer Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amir R. Zamir, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Sax, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;William Shen, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Leonidas Guibas, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jitendra Malik, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Silvio Savarese, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Densely Connected Convolutional Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhuang Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Gao Huang, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Laurens van der Maaten, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Kilian Q. Weinberger, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning from Simulated and Unsupervised Images through Adversarial Training&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ashish Shrivastava, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Tomas Pfister, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Oncel Tuzel, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Josh Susskind, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Wenda Wang, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Russ Webb, Apple Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deep Residual Learning for Image Recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiangyu Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shaoqing Ren, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jian Sun, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DynamicFusion: Reconstruction and Tracking of Non-rigid Scenes in Real-Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Richard A. Newcombe, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Steven M. Seitz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Camera Motion Reveals About Shape with Unknown BRDF&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Manmohan Chandraker, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast, Accurate Detection of 100,000 Object Classes on a Single Machine&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mark A. Ruzon, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mark Segal, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jonathon Shlens, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sudheendra Vijayanarasimhan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jay Yagnik, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Simple Prior-free Method for Non-Rigid Structure-from-Motion Factorization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuchao Dai, Northwestern Polytechnical University&lt;br /&gt;Hongdong Li, Australian National University&lt;br /&gt;Mingyi He, Northwestern Polytechnical University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-time Human Pose Recognition in Parts from Single Depth Images&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jamie Shotton, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mat Cook, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Toby Sharp, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mark Finocchio, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Richard Moore, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alex Kipman, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Blake, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Computation of Robust Low-Rank Matrix Approximations in the Presence of Missing Data using the L1 Norm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anders Eriksson &amp;amp; Anton va den Hendel, University of Adelaide&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Single Image Haze Removal Using Dark Channel Prior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;br /&gt;Jian Sun, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoou Tang, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Global Stereo Reconstruction under Second Order Smoothness Priors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oliver Woodford, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Ian Reid, Oxford Brookes University&lt;br /&gt;Philip Torr, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beyond Sliding Windows: Object Localization by Efficient Subwindow Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chistoph H. Lampert, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Matthew B. Blaschko, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Hodmann, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic 3D Scene Analysis from a Moving Vehicle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bastian Leibe, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Nico Cornelis, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Kurt COrnelis, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Luc Van Gool, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Putting Objects in Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Derek Hoiem, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alexei Efros, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Martial Hebert, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-Time Non-Rigid Surface Detection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julien Pilet, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Lepetit, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Pascal Fua, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Programmable Imaging using a Digital Micromirror Array&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shree K. Nayar, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Vlad Branzoi, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Terry E. Boult, University of Colorado&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object Class Recognition by Unsupervised Scale-Invariant Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rob Fergus, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Pietro Perona, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Morphable 3D models from video&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Brand, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-Time Tracking of Non-Rigid Objects using Mean Shift&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dorin Comaniciu, Siemens Corporate Research&lt;br /&gt;Visvanathan Ramesh, Siemens Corporate Research&lt;br /&gt;Peter Meer, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CVPR/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CVPR/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Computer Vision</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2004-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Relevance estimation with multiple information sources on search engine result pages&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Junqi Zhang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yiqun Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Shaoping Ma, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Qi Tian, University of Texas at San Antonio&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hike: A Hybrid Human-Machine Method for Entity Alignment in Large-Scale Knowledge Bases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yan Zhuang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Guoliang Li, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Zhuojian Zhong, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Jianhua Feng, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vandalism Detection in Wikidata&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefan Heindorf, Paderborn University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Potthast, Bauhaus-Universität Weimar&lt;br /&gt;Benno Stein, Bauhaus-Universität Weimar&lt;br /&gt;Gregor Engels, Paderborn University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the Impact of Syntactic and Semantic Structures for Answer Passages Reranking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kateryna Tymoshenko, University of Trento&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Moschitti, Qatar Computing Research Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cross-Device Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;George Montanez, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ryen White, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiao Huang, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Penguins in Sweaters, or Serendipitous Entity Search on User-generated Content&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ilaria Bordino, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Yelena Mejova, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Mounia Lalmas, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gelling, and Melting, Large Graphs by Edge Manipulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hanghang Tong, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;B. Aditya Prakash, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Tina Eliassi-Rad, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Michalis Faloutsos, University of California Riverside&lt;br /&gt;Christos Faloutsos, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Intent-aware query similarity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jiafeng Guo, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Xueqi Cheng, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Gu Su, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiaofei Zhu, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MENTA: Inducing Multilingual Taxonomies from Wikipedia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gerard de Melo &amp;amp; Gerhard Weikum, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FACeTOR: cost-driven exploration of faceted query results&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abhijith Kashyap, State University of New York at Buffalo&lt;br /&gt;Vagelis Hristidis, Florida International University&lt;br /&gt;Michalis Petropoulos, State University of New York at Buffalo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Feasibility of Multi-Site Web Search Engines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ricardo Baeza-Yates, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Aristides Gionis, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Flavio Junqueira, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Vassilis Plachouras, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Luca Telloli, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning to Link with Wikipedia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Milne &amp;amp; Ian H. Witten, University of Waikato&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Autonomously Semantifying Wikipedia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fei Wu &amp;amp; Daniel S. Weld, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discovering and Exploiting Keyword and Attribute-Value Co-occurrences to Improve P2P Routing Indices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Segabtian Michel, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Matthias Bender, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Nikos Ntarmos, RACTI and University of Patras&lt;br /&gt;Peter Triantafillou, RACTI and University of Patras&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard Weikum, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Christian Zimmer, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards Automatic Association of Relevant Unstructured Content with Structured Query Results&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prasan Roy, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Mukesh Mohania, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Bhuvan Bamba, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Shree Raman, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discovering Frequently Changing Structures from Historical Structural Deltas of Unordered XML&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Qiankun Zhao, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Sourav S Bhowmick, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Mukesh Mohania, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Yahiko Kambayashi, Kyoto University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CIKM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CIKM/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Knowledge Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2005-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Wikipedia With a Broader Lens: Quantifying the Value of Wikipedia’s Relationships with Other Large Scale Online Communities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicholas Vincent, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Isaac Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Brent Hecht, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Keeping a Low Profile? Technology, Risk and Privacy among Undocumented Immigrants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tamy Guberek, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Allison McDonald, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Sylvia Simioni, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Abraham H. Mhaidli, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Kentaro Toyama, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Florian Schaub, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Addressing Age-Related Bias in Sentiment Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Diaz, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Isaac Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Amanda Lazar, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Darren Gergle, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wall++: Room-Scale Interactive and Context-Aware Sensing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yang Zhang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chouchang (Jack) Yang, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alanson Sample, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design for Collaborative Survival: An Inquiry into Human-Fungi Relationships&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jen Liu, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;br /&gt;Daragh Byrne, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Laura Devendorf, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Expressive Time Series Querying with Hand-Drawn Scale-Free Sketches&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Miro Mannino &amp;amp; Azza Abouzied, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pinpointing: Precise Head- and Eye-Based Target Selection for Augmented Reality&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mikko Kytö, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Barrett Ens, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Thammathip Piumsomboon, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Gun A. Lee, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Mark Billinghurst, University of South Australia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Streets for People: Engaging Children in Placemaking Through a Socio-technical Process&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sean Peacock, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Robert Anderson, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Clara Crivellaro, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Let’s Talk About Race: Identity, Chatbots, and AI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ari Schlesinger, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kenton P. O’Hara, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alex S. Taylor, City University of London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“A Stalker’s Paradise”: How Intimate Partner Abusers Exploit Technology&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diana Freed, Cornell Tech&lt;br /&gt;Jackeline Palmer, Hunter College&lt;br /&gt;Diana Minchala, City College of New York&lt;br /&gt;Karen Levy, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Ristenpart, Cornell Tech&lt;br /&gt;Nicola Dell, Cornell Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HARK No More: On the Preregistration of CHI Experiments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Alan Dix, University of Birmingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hoarding and Minimalism: Tendencies in Digital Data Preservation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Francesco Vitale, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Izabelle Janzen, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Joanna McGrenere, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semi-Automated Coding for Qualitative Research: A User-Centered Inquiry and Initial Prototypes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Megh Marathe &amp;amp; Kentaro Toyama, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making as Expression: Informing Design with People with Complex Communication Needs through Art Therapy&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanda Lazar, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Jessica L. Feuston, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Caroline Edasis, Mather LifeWays&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Relevant are Incidental Power Poses for HCI?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yvonne Jansen, Sorbonne Université&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Illustrator: Augmenting Vector Design Tools with Lazy Data Binding for Expressive Visualization Authoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhicheng Liu, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;John Thompson, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alan Wilson, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Mira Dontcheva, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;James Delorey, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Sam Grigg, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Bernard Kerr, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;John Stasko, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Extending Manual Drawing Practices with Artist-Centric Programming Tools&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jennifer, Jacobs Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joel Brandt, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Radomír Mech, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Mitchel Resnick, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Experiencing the Body as Play&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian ‘Floyd’ Mueller, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Richard Byrne, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Josh Andres, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Rakesh Patibanda, RMIT University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gender Recognition or Gender Reductionism?: The Social Implications of Embedded Gender Recognition Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foad Hamidi, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Morgan Klaus Scheuerman, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Stacy M. Branham, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Voice Interfaces in Everyday Life&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Porcheron, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Reeves, The University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Sharples, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Project Zanzibar: A Portable and Flexible Tangible Interaction Platform&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Villar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Cletheroe, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Greg Saul, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Christian Holz, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Tim Regan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Oscar Salandin, Microsoft Researcch&lt;br /&gt;Misha Sra, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hui-Shyong Yeo, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;William Field, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haiyan Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design Within a Patriarchal Society: Opportunities and Challenges in Designing for Rural Women in Bangladesh&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sharifa Sultana, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;François Guimbretière, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Nicola Dell, Cornell Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Agile 3D Sketching with Air Scaffolding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yongkwan Kim, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Sang-Gyun An, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Joon Hyub Lee, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seok-Hyung Bae, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making Core Memory: Design Inquiry into Gendered Legacies of Engineering and Craftwork&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniela K. Rosner, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Samantha Shorey, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brock R. Craft, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Helen Remick, Self-employed&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Illumination Aesthetics: Light as a Creative Material within Computational Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cesar Torres, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jasper O’Leary, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Molly Nicholas, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Eric Paulos, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Organic Primitives: Synthesis and Design of pH-Reactive Materials using Molecular I/O for Sensing Actuation and Interaction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Viirj Kan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Emma Vargo, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Noa Machover, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hiroshi Ishii, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Serena Pan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Weixuan Chen, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Yasuaki Kakehi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ShareVR: Enabling Co-Located Experiences for Virtual Reality between HMD and Non-HMD Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jan Gugenheimer, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Evgeny Stemasov, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Julian Frommel, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Enrico Rukzio, Ulm University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;You Want Me to Work with Who?: Stakeholder Perceptions of Automated Team Formation in Project-based Courses&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farnaz Jahanbakhsh, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Wai-Tat Fu, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Brian Bailey, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stories from Survivors: Privacy &amp;amp; Security Practices when Coping with Intimate Partner Abuse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tara Matthews, Google&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen O’Leary, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Anna Turner, Google&lt;br /&gt;Manya Sleeper, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jill Palzkill Woelfer, Google&lt;br /&gt;Martin Shelton, Google&lt;br /&gt;Cori Manthorne, Community Overcoming Relationship Abuse&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth F. Churchill, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sunny Consolvo, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Critical Lens on Dementia and Design in HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanda Lazar, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Caroline Edasis, Mather LifeWays&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modelling Learning of New Keyboard Layouts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jussi P. P. Jokinen, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Sayan Sarcar, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Chaklam Silpasuwanchai, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Zhenxin Wang, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Xiangshi Ren, Kochi University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Gamified Applications that Make Safe Driving More Engaging&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fabius Steinberger, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ronald Schroeter, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Marcus Foth, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Johnson, Queensland University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;mHealth for Maternal Mental Health: Everyday Wisdom in Ethical Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marguerite Barry, Trinity College Dublin&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Doherty, Trinity College Dublin&lt;br /&gt;Jose Marcano Belisario, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Josip Car, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Cecily Morrison, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Doherty, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Explaining the Gap: Visualizing One’s Predictions Improves Recall and Comprehension of Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yea-Seul Kim, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Katharina Reinecke, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Hullman, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reflective Practicum: A Framework of Sensitising Concepts to Design for Transformative Reflection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Petr Slovák, Vienna University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Frauenberger, Vienna University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Geraldine Fitzpatrick, Vienna University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Can Be Predicted from Six Seconds of Driver Glances?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lex Fridman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Heishiro, Toyoda Toyota Collaborative Safety Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Sean Seaman, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Bobbie Seppelt, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Linda Angell, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Joonbum Lee, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Mehler, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Reimer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Flash Organizations: Crowdsourcing Complex Work by Structuring Crowds As Organizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Melissa A. Valentine, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniela Retelny, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra To, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Negar Rahmati, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Tulsee Doshi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael S. Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design and Evaluation of a Data-Driven Password Meter&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Blase Ur, University of Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Felicia Alfieri, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Maung Aung, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Lujo Bauer, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Nicolas Christin, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Colnago, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Lorrie Faith Cranor, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Henry Dixon, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Pardis Emami Naeini, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hana Habib, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Noah Johnson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;William Melicher, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Public Evaluation: Quantifying Experimenter Intervention&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julie R. Williamson &amp;amp; John Williamson, University of Glasgow&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Is Interaction?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BIGnav: Bayesian Information Gain for Guiding Multiscale Navigation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wanyu Liu, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;br /&gt;Rafael Lucas D’Oliveira, University of Campinas&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Rioul, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Menstrual Tracking to Inform the Design of Personal Informatics Tools&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel A. Epstein, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Nicole B. Lee, Independent Researcher&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer H. Kang, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Elena Agapie, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Schroeder, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Laura R. Pina, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Fogarty, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Julie A. Kientz, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Sean Munson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building a Personalized, Auto-Calibrating Eye Tracker from User Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Xuelin Huang, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Tiffany C.K. Kwok, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Grace Ngai, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen C.F. Chan, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Hong Va Leong, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Email in a Multi-Account, Multi-Device World&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marta E. Cecchinato, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Abigail Sellen, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Milad Shokouhi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Smyth, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Looking at the Vagina through Labella&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Teresa Almeida, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Rob Comber, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Wood, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Dean Saraf, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Madeline Balaam, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enhancing Cross-Device Interaction Scripting with Interactive Illustrations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pei-Yu (Peggy) Chi, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Yang Li, Google&lt;br /&gt;Björn Hartmann, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Empath: Understanding Topic Signals in Large-Scale Text&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan Fast, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Binbin Chen, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Effect of Visual Appearance on the Performance of Continuous Sliders and Visual Analogue Scales&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin Matejka, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Glueck, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HCI Research as Problem-Solving&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RapID: A Framework for Fabricating Low-Latency Interactive Objects with RFID Tags&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Spielberg, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alanson Sample, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Mankoff, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;James McCann, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enabling Designers to Foresee Which Colors Users Cannot See&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Katharina Reinecke, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Brooks, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Movement-based Play With Young People Using Powered Wheelchairs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kathrin Gerling, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Kieran Hicks, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Michael Kalyn, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Adam Evans, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Conor Linehan, University College Cork&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Developing and Validating the User Burden Scale: A Tool for Assessing User Burden in Computing Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hyewon Suh, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Nina Shahriaree, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Eric B. Hekler, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Julie A. Kientz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Momentary Pleasure or Lasting Meaning?: Distinguishing Eudaimonic and Hedonic User Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elisa D. Mekler, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding and Mitigating the Effects of Device and Cloud Service Design Decisions on the Environmental Footprint of Digital Infrastructure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Preist, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Schien, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;Eli Blevis, Indiana University Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haptic Wave: A Cross-Modal Interface for Visually Impaired Audio Producers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Atau Tanaka &amp;amp; Adam Parkinson, Goldsmiths&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“I don’t Want to Wear a Screen”: Probing Perceptions of and Possibilities for Dynamic Displays on Clothing Laura Devendorf&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laura Devendorf, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Joanne Lo, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Noura Howell, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jung Lin Lee, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Nan-Wei Gong, Google&lt;br /&gt;M. Emre Karagozler, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiho Fukuhara, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Eric Paulos, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kimiko Ryokai, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dear Diary: Teens Reflect on Their Weekly Online Risk Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pamela Wisniewski, University of Central Florida&lt;br /&gt;Heng Xu, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Mary Beth Rosson, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel F. Perkins, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;John M. Carroll, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object-Oriented Drawing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haijun Xia, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Araujo, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Wigdor, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foraging Among an Overabundance of Similar Variants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sruti Srinivasa Ragavan, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Sandeep Kaur Kuttal, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Charles Hill, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Anita Sarma, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;David Piorkowski, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Margaret Burnett, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lock n’ LoL: Group-based Limiting Assistance App to Mitigate Smartphone Distractions in Group Activities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minsam Ko, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seungwoo Choi, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Koji Yatani, University of Tokyo&lt;br /&gt;Uichin Lee, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learn Piano with BACh: An Adaptive Learning Interface that Adjusts Task Difficulty Based on Brain State&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beste F. Yuksel, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Kurt B. Oleson, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Lane Harrison, Worcester Polytechnic Institute&lt;br /&gt;Evan M. Peck, Bucknell University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Afergan, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Remco Chang, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Robert JK Jacob, Tufts University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FlexCase: Enhancing Mobile Interaction with a Flexible Sensing and Display Cover&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Rendl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Parzer, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Sean Fanello, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Martin Zirkl, Institute of Surface Technologies and Photonics&lt;br /&gt;Gregor Scheipl, Joanneum Research Forschungsgesellschaft m.b.H&lt;br /&gt;Michael Haller, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Project Jacquard: Interactive Digital Textiles at Scale&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nan-Wei Gong, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiho Fukuhara, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mustafa Emre Karagozler, Google&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Schwesig, Google&lt;br /&gt;Karen E. Robinson, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Smart Touch: Improving Touch Accuracy for People with Motor Impairments with Template Matching&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martez E. Mott, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Radu-Daniel Vatavu, University Stefan cel Mare of Suceava&lt;br /&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;br /&gt;Jacob O. Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Makes Interruptions Disruptive?: A Process-Model Account of the Effects of the Problem State Bottleneck on Task Interruption and Resumption&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jelmer P. Borst, University of Groningen&lt;br /&gt;Niels A. Taatgen, University of Groningen&lt;br /&gt;Hedderik van Rijn, University of Groningen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;VelociTap: Investigating Fast Mobile Text Entry using Sentence-Based Decoding of Touchscreen Keyboard Input&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Keith Vertanen, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Haythem Memmi, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Justin Emge, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Shyam Reyal, University of St Andrews&lt;br /&gt;Per Ola Kristensson, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sharing is Caring: Assistive Technology Designs on Thingiverse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Erin Buehler, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Stacy Branham, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Abdullah Ali, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy J. Chang, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Megan Kelly Hofmann, Colorado State University&lt;br /&gt;Amy Hurst, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tiree Energy Pulse: Exploring Renewable Energy Forecasts on the Edge of the Grid&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Will Simm, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Maria Angela Ferrario, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Adrian Friday, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Newman, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Forshaw, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Mike Hazas, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Alan Dix, Lancaster University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unequal Representation and Gender Stereotypes in Image Search Results for Occupations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Kay, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Cynthia Matuszek, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Sean A. Munson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Resilience Mitigates the Negative Effects of Adolescent Internet Addiction and Online Risk Exposure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pamela Wisniewski, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Haiyan Jia, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Na Wang, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Saijing Zheng, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Heng Xu, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Mary Beth Rosson, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;John Carroll, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Affordance++: Allowing Objects to Communicate Dynamic Use&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pedro Lopes, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrik Jonell, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Political Deliberation Environments to Support Interactions in the Public Sphere&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryan Semaan, Syracuse University&lt;br /&gt;Heather Faucett, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Scott P. Robertson, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;br /&gt;Misa Maruyama, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;br /&gt;Sara Douglas, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ColourID: Improving Colour Identification for People with Impaired Colour Vision&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Alan R. Andrade, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Ross D. Teviotdale, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Dylan L. Knowles, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Craig Stewart, University of Dundee&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fluid Grouping: Quantifying Group Engagement around Interactive Tabletop Exhibits in the Wild&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian Block, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;James Hammerman, TERC&lt;br /&gt;Michael Horn, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Amy Spiegel, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Christiansen, TERC&lt;br /&gt;Brenda Phillips, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Judy Diamond, University of Nebraska State Museum&lt;br /&gt;E. Margaret Evans, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Chia Shen, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sangeet Swara: A Community-Moderated Voice Forum in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aditya Vashistha, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gaetano Borriello, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;William Thies, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Acoustruments: Passive, Acoustically-Driven, Interactive Controls for Handheld Devices	Gierad&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laput, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Brockmeyer, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;iSkin: Flexible, Stretchable and Visually Customizable On-Body Touch Sensors for Mobile Computing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Weigel, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Tong Lu, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Telecom ParisTech&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Carmel Majidi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jürgen Steimle, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patina Engraver: Visualizing Activity Logs as Patina in Fashionable Trackers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Moon-Hwan Lee, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seijin Cha, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Tek-Jin Nam, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BaseLase: An Interactive Focus+Context Laser Floor&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jörg Müller, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Eberle, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Constantin Schmidt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Social Impact of a Robot Co-Worker in Industrial Settings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Allison Sauppé &amp;amp; Bilge Mutlu, University of Wisconsin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“I always assumed that I wasn’t really that close to [her]”: Reasoning about Invisible Algorithms in the News Feed&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Motahhare Eslami, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Aimee Rickman, California State University&lt;br /&gt;Kristen Vaccaro, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Amirhossein Aleyasen, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Andy Vuong, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Hamilton, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Christian Sandvig, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding and Supporting Fathers and Fatherhood on Social Media Sites&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tawfiq Ammari &amp;amp; Sarita Schoenebeck, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lightweight Relief Shearing for Enhanced Terrain Perception on Interactive Maps&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wesley Willett, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Bernhard Jenny, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Tobias Isenberg, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Dragicevic, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From User-Centered to Adoption-Centered Design: A Case Study of an HCI Research Innovation Becoming a Product&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Parmit K. Chilana, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Andrew J. Ko, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Growing Closer on Facebook: Changes in Tie Strength Through Social Network Site Use&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Moira Burke, Facebook&lt;br /&gt;Robert Kraut, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Duet: Exploring Joint Interactions on a Smart Phone and a Smart Watch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiang Anthony Chen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Wigdor, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RetroDepth: 3D Silhouette Sensing for High-Precision Input On and Above Physical Surfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jakub Dostal, University of St Andrews&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Rhemann, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Cem Keskin, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Zach, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jamie Shotton, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Large, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Steven Bathiche, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Matthias Niessner, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;D. Alex Butler, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Sean Fanello, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia&lt;br /&gt;Vivek Pradeep, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Estimating the Social Costs of Friendsourcing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Rzeszotarski &amp;amp; Meredith Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Human Values in Curating a Human Rights Media Archive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abigail Durrant, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Reeves, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emerging Sites of HCI Innovation: Hackerspaces, Hardware Startups &amp;amp; Incubators&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Silvia Lindtner, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Garnet Hertz, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Paul Dourish, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effects of Display Size and Navigation Type on a Classification Task&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Can Liu, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Eric Lecolinet, Telecom ParisTech&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards Accurate and Practical Predictive Models of Active-Vision-Based Visual Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Kieras, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Hornof, University of Oregon&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-time Feedback for Improving Medication Taking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Lee, Philips Research&lt;br /&gt;Anind Dey, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making Sustainability Sustainable: Challenges in the Design of Eco-Interaction Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rayoung Yang, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Mark Newman, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consumed Endurance: A Metric to Quantify Arm Fatigue of Mid-Air Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anders Markussen, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Mikkel Jakobsen, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbaek, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Type-Hover-Swipe in 96 Bytes: A Motion Sensing Mechanical Keyboard&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stuart A Taylor, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Cem Keskin, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Otmar Hilliges, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;John Helmes, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Structured Labeling for Facilitating Concept Evolution in Machine Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Todd Kulesza, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Saleema Amershi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rich Caruana, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Danyel Fisher, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Denis Charles, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MixFab: a Mixed-Reality Environment for Personal Fabrication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Weichel, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Manfred Lau, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Nicolas Villar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hans W Gellersen, Lancaster University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing for Slowness, Anticipation and Re-visitation: A Long Term Field Study of the Photobox&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;William Odom, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Abigail Sellen, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Richard Banks, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Tim Regan, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Mark Selby, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;John Zimmerman, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“Narco” Emotions: Affect and Desensitization in Social Media during the Mexican Drug War&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Munmun De Choudhury, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andres Monroy-Hernandez, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gloria Mark, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Multitasking Through Parallelized Strategy Exploration and Individualized Cognitive Modeling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yunfeng Zhang &amp;amp; Anthony Hornof, University of Oregon&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Labor Dynamics in a Mobile Micro-Task Market&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohamed Musthag &amp;amp; Deepak Ganesan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What is “Critical” About Critical Design?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Bardzell &amp;amp; Shaowen Bardzell, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SPRWeb: Preserving Subjective Responses to Website Colour Schemes through Automatic Recolouring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Katharina Reinecke, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Krzysztof Z. Gajos, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;LaserOrigami: Laser-Cutting 3D Objects	Stefanie Mueller, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bastian Kruck, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mind the Theoretical Gap: Interpreting, Using, and Developing Behavioral Theory in HCI Research&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric B. Hekler, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Predrag Klasnja, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jon Froehlich, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Matthew P. Buman, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Screenfinity: Extending the Perception Area of Content on Very Large Public Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constantin Schmidt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Jörg Müller, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reasons to Question Seven Segment Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Harold Thimbleby, Swansea University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Navigation-Based File Retrieval&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Fitchett, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Dubuque Electricity Portal: Evaluation of a City-Scale Residential Electricity Consumption Feedback System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Erickson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ming Li, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Younghun Kim, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ajay Deshpande, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sambit Sahu, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Tian Chao, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Piyawadee Sukaviriya, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Milind Naphade, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;At Home with Agents: Exploring Attitudes Towards Future Smart Energy Infrastructures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Nadia Pantidi, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Khaled Bachour, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Moran, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Job Opportunities through Entertainment: Virally Spread Speech-Based Services for Low-Literate Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Agha Ali Raza, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Farhan Ul Haq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Zain Tariq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Mansoor Pervaiz, Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;Samia Razaq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Umar Saif, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Roni Rosenfeld, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IllumiRoom: Peripheral Projected Illusions for Interactive Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brett Jones, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Hrvoje Benko, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Eyal Ofek, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew D. Wilson, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Efficacy of Human Post-Editing for Language Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spence Green, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Heer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christopher D. Manning, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Analyzing User-Generated YouTube Videos to Understand Touchscreen Use by People with Motor Impairments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lisa Anthony, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;YooJin Kim, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Leah Findlater, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Turkopticon: Interrupting Worker Invisibility in Amazon Mechanical Turk&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lilly Irani, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;M. Six Silberman, Bureau of Economic Interpretation&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Webzeitgeist: Design Mining the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjitha Kumar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Satyanarayan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Cesar Torres, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Maxine Lim, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Salman Ahmad, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Scott R. Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jerry O. Talton, Intel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weighted Graph Comparison Techniques for Brain Connectivity Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Basak Alper, University of California Santa Barbara&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Bach, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Nathalie Riche, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Tobias Isenberg, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Daniel Fekete, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Many Faces of Facebook: Experiencing Social Media as Performance, Exhibition, and Personal Archive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xuan Zhao, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Niloufar Salehi, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Sasha Naranjit, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Sara Alwaalan, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Voida, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Cosley, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Uncomfortable Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Chris Greenhalgh, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Gabriella Giannachi, University of Exeter&lt;br /&gt;Brendan Walker, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joe Marshall, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ClayVision: The (Elastic) Image of the City&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuichiro Takeuchi, Sony Computer Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Ken Perlin, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Revisiting the Jacquard Loom: Threads of History and Current Patterns in HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ylva Fernaeus, KTH Royal Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Martin Jonssonm, Södertörn University&lt;br /&gt;Jakob Tholanderm, Stockholm University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Personas and Decision Making in the Design Process: An Ethnographic Case Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Erin Friess, University of North Texas&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Error-Related Negativity for Interaction Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chi Vi &amp;amp; Sriram Subramanian, University of Bristol&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Observational and Experimental Investigation of Typing Behaviour using Virtual Keyboards for Mobile Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Niels Henze, University of Oldenburg&lt;br /&gt;Enrico Rukzio, University of Duisburg-Essen&lt;br /&gt;Susanne Boll, University of Oldenburg&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Looking Glass: A Field Study on Noticing Interactivity of Shop Windows&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jörg Müller, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Robert Walter, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Nischt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Florian Alt, University of Stuttgart&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Touché: Enhancing Touch Interaction on Humans, Screens, Liquids, and Everyday Objects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Munehiko Sato, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Affordances in HCI: Toward a Mediated Action Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Victor Kaptelinin, University of Bergen&lt;br /&gt;Bonnie Nardi, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Rhythmic Patterns as an Input Method&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emilien Ghomi, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Guillaume Faure, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Stephane Huot, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Normal Natural Troubles of Driving with GPS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barry Brown, Stockholm University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Laurier, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Communitysourcing: Engaging Local Crowds to Perform Expert Work Via Physical Kiosks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kurtis Heimerl, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Brian Gawalt, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kuang Chen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Tapan S. Parikh, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Björn Hartmann, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Command Selection with CommandMaps&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joey Scarr, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Andrea Bunt, University of Manitoba&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Empathy, Participatory Design and People with Dementia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Lindsay, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Katie Britain, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jackson, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Cassim Ladha, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Karim Ladha, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Olivier, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Usable Gestures for Blind People: Understanding Preference and Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Richard E. Ladner, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effects of Community Size and Contact Rate in Synchronous Social Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryen W. White, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Richardson, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yandong Liu, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Teenagers and Their Virtual Possessions: Design Opportunities and Issues&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;William Odom, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;John Zimmerman, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enhancing Physicality in Touch Interaction with Programmable Friction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Levesque, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Louise Oram, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karon MacLean, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas D. Marchuk, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;J. Edward Colgate, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mid-air Pan-and-Zoom on Wall-sized Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mathieu Nancel, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Julie Wagner, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Emmanuel Pietriga, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bricolage: Example-Based Retargeting for Web Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjitha Kumar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jerry Talton, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Salman Ahmad, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Scott Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Synchronous Interaction Among Hundreds: An Evaluation of a Conference in an Avatar-based Virtual Environment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Erickson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;N. Sadat Shami, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Wendy A. Kellogg, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;David W. Levine, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;In the Shadow of Misperception: Assistive Technology Use and Social Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kristen Shinohara &amp;amp; Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Why is My Internet Slow?: Making Network Speeds Visible&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marshini Chetty, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;David Haslem, Orange Sparkle Ball&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Baird, Amazon&lt;br /&gt;Ugochi Ofoha, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bethany Sumner, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Grinter, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ease of Juggling: Studying the Effects of Manual Multitasking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Antti Oulasvirta &amp;amp; Joanna Bergstrom-Lehtovirta, Aalto University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automics: souvenir generating photoware for theme parks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abigail Durrant, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Duncan Rowland, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Derek McAuley, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Michael A. Peshkin, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Your Noise is My Command: Sensing Gestures Using the Body as an Antenna&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gabe Cohn, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shwetak N. Patel, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Desney Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Review Spotlight: A User Interface for Summarizing User-generated Reviews Using Adjective-Noun Word Pairs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koji Yatani, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Michael Novati, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Trusty, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Khai N. Truong, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lumino: Tangible Blocks for Tabletop Computers Based on Glass Fiber Bundles&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Torsten Becker, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Frederik Rudeck, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mapping the Landscape of Sustainable HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carl DiSalvo, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Hrönn Brynjarsdóttir, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Occlusion-Aware Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Vogel &amp;amp; Ravin Balakrishnan, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Avaaj Otalo — A Field Study of an Interactive Voice Forum for Small Farmers in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neil Patel, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Deepti Chittamuru, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Anupam Jain, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Paresh Dave, Development Support Center&lt;br /&gt;Tapan S. Parikh, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How does search behavior change as search becomes more difficult?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anne Aula, Google&lt;br /&gt;Rehan M. Khan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Zhiwei Guan, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Tower of Babel Meets Web 2.0: User-Generated Content and its Applications in a Multilingual Context&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brent Hecht &amp;amp; Darren Gergle, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Skinput: Appropriating the Body as an Input Surface&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Desney Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Dan Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mobile-izing Health Workers in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Divya Ramachandran, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;John Canny, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Prabhu Dutta Das, Dhirubhai Ambani Institute of Information and Communications Technology&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Design of Eco-Feedback Technology&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jon Froehlich, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Leah Findlater, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Landay, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feminist HCI: Taking Stock and Outlining an Agenda for Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shaowen Bardzell, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prefab: Implementing Advanced Behaviors Using Pixel-Based Reverse Engineering of Interface Structure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Morgan Dixon &amp;amp; James Fogarty, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Useful Junk? The Effects of Visual Embellishment on Comprehension and Memorability of Charts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scott Bateman, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Regan L. Mandryk, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Genest, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;David McDine, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Brooks, University of Saskatchewan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Interaction to Trajectories: Designing Coherent Journeys Through User Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Gabriella Giannachi, University of Exeter&lt;br /&gt;Boriana Koleva, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sizing the Horizon: The Effects of Chart Size and Layering on the Graphical Perception of Time Series Visualization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Heer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Kong, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Maneesh Agrawala, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting Tie Strength With Social Media&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric Gilbert &amp;amp; Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Musink: Composing Music through Augmented Drawing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Theophanis Tsandilas, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Catherine Letondal, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Social Immersive Media: Pursuing Best Practices for Multi-user Interactive Camera/Projector Exhibits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scott S. Snibbe, Sona Research&lt;br /&gt;Hayes S. Raffle, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ephemeral Adaptation: The Use of Gradual Onset to Improve Menu Selection Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Leah Findlater, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karyn Moffatt, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Joanna McGrenere, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Dawson, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Undo and Erase Events as Indicators of Usability Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Akers, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Simpson, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robin Jeffries, Google&lt;br /&gt;Terry Winograd, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;In-Car GPS Navigation: Engagement with and Disengagement from the Environment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gilly Leshed, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Theresa Velden, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Oya Rieger, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Blazej Kot, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving the Performance of Motor-Impaired Users with Automatically-Generated, Ability-Based Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Krzysztof Z. Gajos, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel S. Weld, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Large Scale Analysis of Web Revisitation Patterns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eytan Adar, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jaime Teevan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Susan T. Dumais, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designs on Dignity: Perceptions of Technology Among the Homeless&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher A. Le Dantec &amp;amp; W. Keith Edwards, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Network in the Garden: An Empirical Analysis of Social Media in Rural Life&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric Gilbert, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Christian Sandvig, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multimodal collaborative handwriting training for visually-impaired people&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beryl Plimmer, University of Auckland&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Crossan, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Stephen A. Brewster, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Rachel Blagojevic, University of Auckland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Error Model for Pointing Based on Fitts’ Law&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Susumu Harada, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;I. Scott MacKenzie, York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multiview: improving trust in group video conferencing through spatial faithfulness&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David T. Nguyen &amp;amp; John Canny, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Software or wetware?: discovering when and why people use digital prosthetic memory&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vaiva Kalnikaité &amp;amp; Steve Whittaker, University of Sheffield&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shift: a technique for operating pen-based interfaces using touch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Vogel, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Authoring sensor-based interactions by demonstration with direct manipulation and pattern recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Björn Hartmann, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Leith Abdulla, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Manas Mittal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Scott R. Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sustainable interaction design: invention &amp;amp; disposal, renewal &amp;amp; reuse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eli Blevis, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consuming video on Mobile devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kenton O’Hara, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;April Slayden Mitchell, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Alex Vorbau, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trackball text entry for people with motor impairments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Wobbrock &amp;amp; Brad Myers, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Embedded phenomena: supporting science learning with classroom-sized distributed simulations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Moher, University of Illinois at Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A role for haptics in mobile interaction: initial design using a handheld tactile display prototype&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joseph Luk, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Jérôme Pasquero, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;Shannon Little, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karon MacLean, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Lévesque, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Hayward, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making space for stories: ambiguity in the design of personal communication systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul M. Aoki, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Allison Woodruff, Intel Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Task Engagement in Sensor-Based Statistical Models of Human Interruptibility&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Fogarty, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew J. Ko, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Htet Htet Aung, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Elspeth Golden, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Karen P. Tang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing the spectator experience&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stuart Reeves, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Claire O’Malley, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Mike Fraser, University of Bristol&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The bubble cursor: enhancing target acquisition by dynamic resizing of the cursor’s activation area&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tovi Grossman &amp;amp; Ravin Balakrishnan, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-CHI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-CHI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Human-Computer Interaction</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2001-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding syntax in human encephalography with beam search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Hale, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Dyer, DeepMind&lt;br /&gt;Adhiguna Kuncoro, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan R. Brennan, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Probabilistic Typology: Deep Generative Models of Vowel Inventories&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryan Cotterell &amp;amp; Jason Eisner, Johns Hopkins University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Non-Arbitrary Form-Meaning Systematicity Using String-Metric Learning for Kernel Regression&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;E. Darío Gutiérrez, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Roger Levy, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin K. Bergen, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Evaluation of Machine Translation Quality Estimation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yvette Graham, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Dynamic Feature Selection for Fast Sequential Prediction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emma Strubell, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Luke Vilnis, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Kate Silverstein, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Andrew McCallum, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast and Robust Neural Network Joint Models for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Devlin, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Rabih Zbib, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Zhongqiang Huang, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Lamar, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Richard Schwartz, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;John Makhoul, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Grounded Language Learning from Video Described with Sentences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haonan Yu &amp;amp; Jeffrey Mark Siskind, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;String Re-writing Kernel&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fan Bu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Hang Li, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoyan Zhu, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Symbol-Refined Tree Substitution Grammars for Syntactic Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hiroyuki Shindo, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Yusuke Miyao, National Institute of Informatics&lt;br /&gt;Akinori Fujino, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Masaaki Nagata, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unsupervised Part-of-Speech Tagging with Bilingual Graph-Based Projections&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dipanjan Das, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Slav Petrov, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beyond NomBank: A Study of Implicit Arguments for Nominal Predicates&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Gerber &amp;amp; Joyce Y. Chai, Michigan State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reinforcement Learning for Mapping Instructions to Actions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;S.R.K. Branavan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Harr Chen, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Luke S. Zettlemoyer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Regina Barzilay, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;K-Best A* Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adam Pauls &amp;amp; Dan Klein, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Concise Integer Linear Programming Formulations for Dependency Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;André F.T. Martins, Instituto de Telecomunicações&lt;br /&gt;Noah A. Smith, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Eric P. Xing, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Forest Reranking: Discriminative Parsing with Non-Local Features&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Liang Huang, University of Pennsylvania&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A New String-to-Dependency Machine Translation Algorithm with a Target Dependency Language Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Libin Shen, BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Jinxi Xu, BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Ralph Weischedel, BBN Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning synchronous grammars for semantic parsing with lambda calculus&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuk Wah Wong &amp;amp; Raymond J. Mooney, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semantic taxonomy induction from heterogenous evidence&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rion Snow, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jurafsky, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Y. Ng, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Hierarchical Phrase-Based Model for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Chiang, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Predominant Word Senses in Untagged Text&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diana McCarthy, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;Rob Koeling, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;Julie Weeds, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;John Carroll, University of Sussex&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Accurate Unlexicalized Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Klein &amp;amp; Christopher D. Manning, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards a Model of Face-to-Face Grounding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yukiko I. Nakano, RISTEX&lt;br /&gt;Gabe Reinstein, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Tom Stocky, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Justine Cassell, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discriminative Training and Maximum Entropy Models for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Franz Josef Och &amp;amp; Hermann Ney, RWTH Aachen University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Immediate-Head Parsing for Language Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eugene Charniak, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Decoding and Optimal Decoding for Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ulrich Germann, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Michael Jahr, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Knight, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Marcu, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Kenji Yamada, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-ACL/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-ACL/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Natural Language Processing</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Memory-Augmented Monte Carlo Tree Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chenjun Xiao, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Jincheng Mei, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Martin Müller, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Label-Free Supervision of Neural Networks with Physics and Domain Knowledge&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Russell Stewart &amp;amp; Stefano Ermon, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bidirectional Search That Is Guaranteed to Meet in the Middle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Robert C. Holte, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Ariel Felner, Ben-Gurion University&lt;br /&gt;Guni Sharon, Ben-Gurion University&lt;br /&gt;Nathan R. Sturtevant, University of Denver&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Non-Negative to General Operator Cost Partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian Pommerening, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Malte Helmert, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Gabriele Röger, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Jendrik Seipp, University of Basel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recovering from Selection Bias in Causal and Statistical Inference&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elias Bareinboim, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Jin Tian, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Judea Pearl, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HC-Search: Learning Heuristics and Cost Functions for Structured Prediction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Janardhan Rao Doppa, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Alan Fern, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Prasad Tadepalli, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SMILe: Shufﬂed Multiple-Instance Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gary Doran &amp;amp; Soumya Ray, Case Western Reserve University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning SVM Classifiers with Indefinite Kernels&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Suicheng Gu &amp;amp; Yuhong Guo, Temple University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Document Summarization Based on Data Reconstruction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhanying He, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Chun Chen, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Jiajun Bu, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Can Wang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Lijan Zhang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Deng Cai, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaofei He, Zhejiang University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic Resource Allocation in Conservation Planning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Golovin, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Krause, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Beth Gardner, North Carolina State University&lt;br /&gt;Sarah J. Converse, Patuxent Wildlife Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Steve Morey, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Complexity of and Algorithms for Borda Manipulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jessica Davies, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;George Katsirelos, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Nina Narodytska, University of New South Wales&lt;br /&gt;Toby Walsh, NICTA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Incomplete Is Your Semantic Web Reasoner? Systematic Analysis of the Completeness of Query Answering Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giorgos Stoilos, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Bernardo Cuenca Grau, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Ian Horrocks, Oxford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Novel Transition Based Encoding Scheme for Planning as Satisfiability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ruoyun Huang, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Yixin Chen, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Weixiong Zhang, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Good is Almost Perfect?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Malte Helmert &amp;amp; Gabriele Röger, Albert-Ludwigs-Universität Freiburg&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal False-Name-Proof Voting Rules with Costly Voting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Liad Wagman &amp;amp; Vincent Conitzer, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PLOW: A Collaborative Task Learning Agent&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Allen, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Nathanael Chambers, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;George Ferguson, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Lucian Galescu, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Hyuckchul Jung, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Mary Swift, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;William Taysom, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thresholded Rewards: Acting Optimally in Timed, Zero-Sum Games&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Colin McMillen &amp;amp; Manuela Veloso, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Model Counting: A New Strategy for Obtaining Good Bounds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carla P. Gomes, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Ashish Sabharwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Bart Selman, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards an Axiom System for Default Logic&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gerhard Lakemeyer, RWTH Aachen University&lt;br /&gt;Hector J. Levesque, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Max K- Armed Bandit: A New Model of Exploration Applied to Search Heuristic Selection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent A. Cicirello, Drexel University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen F. Smith, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning and Inferring Transportation Routines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lin Liao, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry Kautz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Computing All Abductive Explanations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Eiter, Technische Universität Wien&lt;br /&gt;Kazuhisa Makino, Osaka University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Game of Hex: An Automatic Theorem-Proving Approach to Game Programming&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vadim V. Anshelevich, Vanshel Consulting&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PROVERB: The Probabilistic Cruciverbalist&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Greg A. Keim, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Noam M. Shazeer, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Michael L. Littman, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Sushant Agarwal, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Catherine M. Cheves, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Fitzgerald, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Jason Grosland, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Fan Jiang, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Shannon Pollard, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Karl Weinmeister, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Evaluation Functions for Global Optimization and Boolean Satisfiability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin A. Boyan &amp;amp; Andrew W. Moore, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Acceleration Methods for Numeric CSPs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yahia Lebbah &amp;amp; Olivier Lhomme, Ecole des Mines de Nantes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Interactive Museum Tour-Guide Robot&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wolfram Burgard, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Armin B. Cremers, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Dirk Hähnel, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard Lakemeyer, Aachen University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Dirk Schulz, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Walter Steiner, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Thrun, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Statistical Parsing with a Context-Free Grammar and Word Statistics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eugene Charniak, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Practical Algorithm for Finding Optimal Triangulations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Krill Shoikhet &amp;amp; Dan Geiger, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Context Switching in Real-Time Propositional Reasoning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;P. Pandurang Nayak &amp;amp; Brian C. Williams, NASA Ames Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building Concept Representations from Reusable Components&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Clark, Boeing&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Porter, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verification of Knowledge Bases Based on Containment Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alon Y. Levy, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Marie-Christine Rousset, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Novel Application of Theory Refinement to Student Modeling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul T. Baffes, SciComp&lt;br /&gt;Raymond J. Mooney, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pushing the Envelope: Planning, Propositional Logic, and Stochastic Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Henry Kautz &amp;amp; Bart Selman, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-AAAI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-AAAI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
