<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PXZHANG</title>
    <description>这里是 @PXZHANG张培歆 的个人网站</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 22:53:46 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 22:53:46 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2003-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Constant-Factor Approximation Algorithm for the Asymmetric Traveling Salesman Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ola Svensson, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Jakub Tarnawski, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;László A. Végh, London School of Economics&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Explicit, Almost Optimal, Epsilon-Balanced Codes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amnon Ta-Shma, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Weighted Linear Matroid Parity Algorithm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Satoru Iwata, University of Tokyo&lt;br /&gt;Yusuke Kobayashi, University of Tsukuba&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deciding Parity Games in Quasipolynomial Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristian S. Calude, University of Auckland&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Jain, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Bakhadyr Khoussainov, University of Auckland&lt;br /&gt;Wei Li, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Frank Stephan, National University of Singapore&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Explicit Two-Source Extractors and Resilient Functions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eshan Chattopadhyay &amp;amp; David Zuckerman, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graph Isomorphism in Quasipolynomial Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;László Babaí, University of Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reed-Muller Codes Achieve Capacity on Erasure Channels&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shrinivas Kudekar, Qualcomm Research&lt;br /&gt;Santhosh Kumar, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Marco Mondelli, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Henry D. Pfister, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Eren Sasoglu, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Rudiger Urbanke, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Exponential Separation of Information and Communication for Boolean Functions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anat Ganor, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;br /&gt;Gillat Kol, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2-Server PIR with sub-polynomial communication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zeev Dvir &amp;amp; Sivakanth Gopi, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lower Bounds on the Size of Semidefinite Programming Relaxations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James R. Lee, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Prasad Raghavendra, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Steurer, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The matching polytope has exponential extension complexity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Rothvoß, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximation Resistance from Pairwise Independent Subgroups&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Siu On Chan, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Low Rank Approximation and Regression in Input Sparsity Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kenneth L. Clarkson &amp;amp; David P. Woodruff, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Linear vs. Semidefinite Extended Formulations: Exponential Separation and Strong Lower Bounds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Samuel Fiorini, Université libre de Bruxelles&lt;br /&gt;Serge Massar, Université libre de Bruxelles&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Pokutta, Universität Erlangen Nürnberg&lt;br /&gt;Hans Tiwary, Université libre de Bruxelles&lt;br /&gt;Ronald de Wolf, Centrum Wiskunde &amp;amp; Informatica&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Cell Probe Complexity of Dynamic Range Counting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kasper Larsen, Aarhus University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Electrical flows, laplacian systems, and faster approximation of maximum flow in undirected graphs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul Christiano, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan A. Kelner, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Aleksander Mądry, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel A. Spielman, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Shang-Hua Teng, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subexponential lower bounds for randomized pivoting rules for the simplex algorithm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oliver Friedmann, University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Dueholm Hansen, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;Uri Zwick, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An improved LP-based approximation for steiner tree&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jaroslaw Byrka, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Fabrizio Grandoni, University of Tor Vergata&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Rothvoß, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Laura Sanità, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;QIP = PSPACE&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rahul Jain, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Zhengfeng Ji, Perimeter Institute for Theoretical Physics&lt;br /&gt;Sarvagya Upadhyay, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;John Watrous, University of Waterloo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A constructive proof of the Lovász local lemma&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Robin A. Moser, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Public-Key Cryptosystems from the Worst-Case Shortest Vector Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Peikert, SRI International&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal algorithms and inapproximability results for every CSP?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prasad Raghavendra, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal hierarchical decompositions for congestion minimization in networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Harald Räcke, University of Warwick&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Faster integer multiplication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Fürer, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards 3-query locally decodable codes of subexponential length&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sergey Yekhanin, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The PCP theorem by gap amplification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Irit Dinur, Hebrew University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Undirected ST-connectivity in log-space&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Omer Reingold, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-linear formulas for permanent and determinant are of super-polynomial size&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Expander flows, geometric embeddings and graph partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sanjeev Arora, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Satish Rao, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Umesh Vazirani, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Derandomizing polynomial identity tests means proving circuit lower bounds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Valentine Kabanets &amp;amp; Russell Impagliazzo, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;New lattice-based cryptographic constructions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oded Regev, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/03/best-paper-awards-STOC/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/03/best-paper-awards-STOC/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Theory</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1997-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DeepXplore: Automated Whitebox Testing of Deep Learning Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kexin Pei, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yinzhi Cao, Lehigh University&lt;br /&gt;Junfeng Yang, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Suman Jana, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Efficient Server Audit Problem, Deduplicated Re-execution, and the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cheng Tan, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Lingfan Yu, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Joshua B. Leners, Two Sigma Investments&lt;br /&gt;Michael Walfish, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pivot Tracing: Dynamic Causal Monitoring for Distributed Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jonathan Mace, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Ryan Roelke, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Rodrigo Fonseca, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Crash Hoare Logic for Certifying the FSCQ File System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haogang Chen, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Ziegler, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Tej Chajed, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Adam Chlipala, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;M. Frans Kaashoek, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nickolai Zeldovich, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Coz: Finding Code that Counts with Causal Profiling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charlie Curtsinger, Grinnell College&lt;br /&gt;Emery Berger, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards optimization-safe systems: analyzing the impact of undefined behavior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xi Wang, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nickolai Zeldovich, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;M. Frans Kaashoek, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Armando Solar-Lezama, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Naiad: A Timely Dataﬂow System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Derek G. Murray, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Frank McSherry, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Isaacs, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Isard, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Paul Barham, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Martíın Abadi, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Scalable Commutativity Rule: Designing Scalable Software for Multicore Processors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Austin T. Clements, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;M. Frans Kaashoek, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nickolai Zeldovich, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Robert T. Morris, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Eddie Kohler, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A File is Not a File: Understanding the I/O Behavior of Apple Desktop Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tyler Harter, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Chris Dragga, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Vaughn, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Andrea C. Arpaci-Dusseau, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Remzi H. Arpaci-Dusseau, University of Wisconsin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cells: A Virtual Mobile Smartphone Architecture&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeremy Andrus, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Christoffer Dall, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Van’t Hof, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Oren Laadan, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Jason Nieh, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FAWN: A Fast Array of Wimpy Nodes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David G. Andersen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jason Franklin, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Kaminsky, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Amar Phanishayee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Lawrence Tan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Vijay Vasudevan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;seL4: Formal Verification of an OS Kernel&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gerwin Klein, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Elphinstone, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Gernot Heiser, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;June Andronick, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;David Cock, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Philip Derrin, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Dhammika Elkaduwe, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Kai Engelhardt, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Rafal Kolanski, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Michael Norrish, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Sewell, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Harvey Tuch, NICTA&lt;br /&gt;Simon Winwood, NICTA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RouteBricks: Exploiting Parallelism to Scale Software Routers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mihai Dobrescu, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Norbert Egi, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Katerina Argyraki, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Byung-Gon Chun, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Fall, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Gianluca Iannaccone, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Allan Knies, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Maziar Manesh, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Sylvia Ratnasamy, Intel Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zyzzyva: speculative byzantine fault tolerance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ramakrishna Kotla, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo Alvisi, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Mike Dahlin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Allen Clement, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Edmund Wong, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sinfonia: a new paradigm for building scalable distributed systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcos K. Aguilera, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Arif Merchant, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Mehul Shah, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Alistair Veitch, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Christos Karamanolis, VMware&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Secure Web Applications via Automatic Partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Chong, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Jed Liu, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Xin Qi, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;K. Vikram, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Lantian Zheng, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Xin Zheng, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Speculative Execution in a Distributed File System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edmund B. Nightingale, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Peter M. Chen, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jason Flinn, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BAR Tolerance for Cooperative Services&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amitanand S. Aiyer, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo Alvisi, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Allen Clement, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Mike Dahlin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Philippe Martin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Carl Porth, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rx: treating bugs as allergies - a safe method to survive software failures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feng Qin, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Tucek, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Jagadeesan Sundaresan, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Yuanyuan Zhou, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vigilante: End-to-End Containment of Internet Worms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Manuel Costa, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Jon Crowcroft, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Miguel Castro, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Antony Rowstron, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Lidong Zhou, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Lintao Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Paul Barham, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Backtracking intrusions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Samuel T. King &amp;amp; Peter M. Chen, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Preserving peer replicas by rate-limited sampled voting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Petros Maniatis, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;David S. H. Rosenthal, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mema Roussopoulos, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mary Baker, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;TJ Giuli, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Yanto Muliadi, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving the Reliability of Commodity Operating Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael M. Swift, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brian N. Bershad, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry M. Levy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BASE: using abstraction to improve fault tolerance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rodrigo Rodrigues, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Miguel Castro, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Barbara Liskov, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Untrusted hosts and confidentiality: secure program partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Zdancewic, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Lantian Zheng, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Nathaniel Nystrom, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cellular Disco: resource management using virtual clusters on shared-memory multiprocessors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kinshuk Govil, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Teodosiu, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Yongqiang Huang, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mendel Rosenblum, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Soft timers: efficient microsecond software timer support for network processing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohit Aron &amp;amp; Peter Druschel, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Click modular router&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Robert Morris, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Eddie Kohler, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;John Jannotti, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;M. Frans Kaashoek, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Manageability, availability and performance in Porcupine: a highly scalable, cluster-based mail service&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yasushi Saito, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brian N. Bershad, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry M. Levy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Continuous profiling: where have all the cycles gone?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jennifer M. Anderson, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Lance M. Berc, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Dean, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Ghemawat, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Monika R. Henzinger, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Shun-Tak A. Leung, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Richard L. Sites, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Mark T. Vandevoorde, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Carl A. Waldspurger, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;William E. Weihl, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Disco: running commodity operating systems on scalable multiprocessors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edouard Bugnion, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Scott Devine, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mendel Rosenblum, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eraser: a dynamic data race detector for multithreaded programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefan Savage, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Michael Burrows, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Greg Nelson, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Sobalvarro, Digital Equipment Corporation&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/03/best-paper-awards-SOSP/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/03/best-paper-awards-SOSP/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Operating Systems</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1997-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Provenance for Natural Language Queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Deutch, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nave Frost, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Amir Gilad, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compressed Linear Algebra for Large-Scale Machine Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ahmed Elgohary, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Matthias Boehm, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Peter Haas, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Fred Reiss, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Berthold Reinwald, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constructing an interactive natural language interface for relational databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fei Li &amp;amp; H. V. Jagadish, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;M4: A Visualization-Oriented Time Series Data Aggregation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Uwe Jugel, SAP&lt;br /&gt;Zbigniew Jerzak, SAP&lt;br /&gt;Gregor Hackenbroich, SAP&lt;br /&gt;Volker Markl, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building Efficient Query Engines in a High-Level Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yannis Klonatos, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Koch, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Tiark Rompf, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Hassan Chaf, Oracle&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On k-Path Covers and their Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefan Funke, University of Stuttgart&lt;br /&gt;André Nusser, University of Stuttgart&lt;br /&gt;Sabine Storandt, University of Stuttgart&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;epiC: an Extensible and Scalable System for Processing Big Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dawei Jiang, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Gang Chen, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Beng Chin Ooi, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Kian-Lee Tan, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Sai Wu, Zhejiang University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Uncracked Pieces in Database Cracking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Felix Martin Schuhknecht, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Alekh Jindal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jens Dittrich, Saarland University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DisC Diversity: Result Diversification based on Dissimilarity and Coverage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marina Drosou &amp;amp; Evaggelia Pitoura, University of Ioannina&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dense Subgraph Maintenance under Streaming Edge Weight Updates for Real-time Story Identification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Albert Angel, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Nick Koudas, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Nikos Sarkas, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Divesh Srivastava, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RemusDB: Transparent High-Availability for Database Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Umar Farooq Minhas, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Shriram Rajagopalan, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Brendan Cully, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Ashraf Aboulnaga, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Ken Salem, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Warfield, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards Certain Fixes with Editing Rules and Master Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shuai Ma, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Wenfei Fan, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Jianzhong Li, Harbin Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Wenyuan Yu, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Nan Tang, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Unified Approach to Ranking in Probabilistic Databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian Li, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Barna Saha, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Amol Deshpande, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Frequent Items in Data Streams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graham Cormode &amp;amp; Marios Hadjieleftheriou, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constrained Physical Design Tuning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Bruno &amp;amp; Surajit Chaudhuri, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scalable Semantic Web Data Management Using Vertical Partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel J. Abadi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marcus, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Samuel R. Madden, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kate Hollenbach, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trustworthy Keyword Search for Regulatory-Compliant Records Retention&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Soumyadeb Mitra, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Windsor W. Hsu, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Marianne Winslett, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cache-conscious Frequent Pattern Mining on a Modern Processor&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amol Ghoting, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Buehrer, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Srinivasan Parthasarathy, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Daehyun Kim, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Anthony D. Nguyen, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Yen-Kuang Chen, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Pradeep Dubey, Intel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Model-Driven Data Acquisition in Sensor Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amol Deshpande, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Guestrin, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Samuel R. Madden, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joseph M. Hellerstein, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Wei Hong, Intel Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weaving Relations for Cache Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anastassia Ailamaki, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;David J. DeWitt, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Mark D. Hill, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Marios Skounakis, University of Wisconsin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Integrating Reliable Memory in Databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wee Teck Ng &amp;amp; Peter M. Chen, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/02/best-paper-awards-VLDB/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/02/best-paper-awards-VLDB/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Databases</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Porta: Profiling Software Tutorials Using Operating-System-Wide Activity Tracing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alok Mysore &amp;amp; Philip J. Guo, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Authoring and Verifying Human-Robot Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Porfirio, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Allison Sauppé, University of Wisconsin-La Crosse&lt;br /&gt;Aws Albarghouthi, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Bilge Mutlu, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RESi: A Highly Flexible, Pressure-Sensitive, Imperceptible Textile Interface Based on Resistive Yarns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patrick Parzer, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Florian Perteneder, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Kathrin Probst, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Christian Rendl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Joanne Leong, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Schuetz, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Anita Vogl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Reinhard Schwoediauer, Johannes Kepler University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Kaltenbrunner, Johannes Kepler University&lt;br /&gt;Siegfried Bauer, Johannes Kepler University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Haller, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Triggering Artwork Swaps for Live Animation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nora S. Willett, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Wilmot Li, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Jovan Popovic, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Adam Finkelstein, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Grabity: A Wearable Haptic Interface for Simulating Weight and Grasping in Virtual Reality&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Inrak Choi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Heather Culbertson, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mark R. Miller, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Olwal, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sean Follmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;AirCode: Unobtrusive Physical Tags for Digital Fabrication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dingzeyu Li, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Avinash S. Nair, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Shree K. Nayar, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Changxi Zheng, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rovables: Miniature On-Body Robots as Mobile Wearables&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Artem Dementyev, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hsin-Liu (Cindy) Kao, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Inrak Choi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Deborah Ajilo, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Maggie Xu, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Paradiso, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Chris Schmandt, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Sean Follmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;proCover: Sensory Augmentation of Prosthetic Limbs Using Smart Textile Covers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joanne Leong, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Parzer, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Florian Perteneder, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Teo Babic, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Christian Rendl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Anita Vogl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Hubert Egger, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Alex Olwal, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michael Haller, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ViBand: High-Fidelity Bio-Acoustic Sensing Using Commodity Smartwatch Accelerometers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gierad Laput, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Robert Xiao, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zooids: Building Blocks for Swarm User Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mathieu Le Goc, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Lawrence H. Kim, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Ali Parsaei, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Daniel Fekete, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Dragicevic, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Sean Follmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Orbits: Gaze Interaction for Smart Watches using Smooth Pursuit Eye Movements&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Augusto Esteves, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Eduardo Velloso, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Bulling, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Hans Gellersen, Lancaster University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Webstrates: Shareable Dynamic Media&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Clemens Klokmose, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;James Eagan, Telecom ParisTech&lt;br /&gt;Siemen Baader, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foldio: Digital Fabrication of Interactive and Shape-Changing Objects With Foldable Printed Electronics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Simon Olberding, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Sergio Soto Ortega, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Klaus Hildebrandt, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Jurgen Steimle, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sensing Techniques for Tablet+Stylus Interaction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ken Hinckley, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michel Pahud, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hrvoje Benko, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Pourang Irani, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Marcel Gavriliu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;François Guimbretière, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiang Anthony Chen, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Fabrice Matulic, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;William Buxton, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Wilson, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PrintScreen: Fabricating Highly Customizable Thin-film Touch-Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Simon Olberding, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Michael Wessely, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Jürgen Steimle, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Expert Crowdsourcing with Flash Teams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniela Retelny, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Sébastien Robaszkiewicz, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra To, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Walter Lasecki, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Jay Patel, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Negar Rahmati, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Tulsee Doshi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Melissa Valentine, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PneUI: Pneumatically Actuated Soft Composite Materials for Shape Changing Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lining Yao, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ryuma Niiyama, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Jifei Ou, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Sean Follmer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Clark Della Silva, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hiroshi Ishii, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Touch &amp;amp; Activate: Adding Interactivity to Existing Objects using Active Acoustic Sensing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Makoto Ono, University of Tsukuba&lt;br /&gt;Buntarou Shizuki, University of Tsukuba&lt;br /&gt;Jiro Tanaka, University of Tsukuba&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fiberio: A Touchscreen that Senses Fingerprints&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Holz &amp;amp; Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CrowdScape: interactively visualizing user behavior and output&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Rzeszotarski &amp;amp; Aniket Kitur, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cliplets: juxtaposing still and dynamic imagery&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neel Joshi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Sisil Mehta, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Steven Drucker, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Eric Stollnitz, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hugues Hoppe, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Matt Uyttendaele, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Michael Cohen, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jamming User Interfaces: Programmable Particle Stiffness and Sensing for Malleable and Shape-Changing Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sean Follmer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Leithinger, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alex Olwal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nadia Cheng, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hiroshi Ishii, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SideBySide: Ad-hoc Multi-user Interaction with Handheld Projectors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Karl D.D. Willis, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Moshe Mahler, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;VizWiz: nearly real-time answers to visual questions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey P. Bigham, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Chandrika Jayant, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Hanjie Ji, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Greg Little, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Miller, University of Central Florida&lt;br /&gt;Robert C. Miller, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Robin Miller, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Aubrey Tatarowicz, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Brandyn White, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Samual White, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Tom Yeh, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mouse 2.0: Multi-touch meets the Mouse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Villar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Dan Rosenfeld, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Hrvoje Benko, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;John Helmes, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Westhues, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Steve Hodges, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Eyal Ofek, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Alex Butler, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiang Cao, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Billy Chen, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bringing Physics to the Surface&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew D. Wilson, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Otmar Hilliges, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Armando Garcia-Mendoza, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ThinSight: Versatile Multi-touch Sensing for Thin Form-factor Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Hodges, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alex Butler, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alban Rrustemi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Bill Buxton, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reflective Physical Prototyping through Integrated Design, Test, and Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Björn Hartmann, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Scott Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Leith Abdulla, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Brandon Burr, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Avi Robinson-Mosher, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Gee, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automation and Customization of Rendered Web Pages&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Bolin, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Webber, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Philip Rha, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Tom Wilson, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Robert C. Miller, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-Finger Gestural Interaction with 3D Volumetric Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tovi Grossman, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Wigdor, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Ravin Balakrishnan, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CrossY: A Crossing-Based Drawing Application&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georg Apitz &amp;amp; François Guimbretière, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Perceptually-Supported Image Editing of Text and Graphics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric Saund, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;br /&gt;David Fleet, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Larner, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;br /&gt;James Mahoney, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Clothing Manipulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Takeo Igarashi, University of Tokyo&lt;br /&gt;John F. Hughes, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Phidgets: Easy Development of Physical Interfaces through Physical Widgets&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Saul Greenberg &amp;amp; Chester Fitchett, University of Calgary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sensing Techniques for Mobile Interaction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ken Hinckley, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Pierce, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mike Sinclair, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Eric Horvitz, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Indigo: A Local Propagation Algorithm for Inequality Constraints&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alan Borning, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Bjorn Freeman-Benson, Object Technology International&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/02/best-paper-awards-UIST/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/02/best-paper-awards-UIST/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>User Interface</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1998-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HighLife: Higher-arity Fact Harvesting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patrick Ernst, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;br /&gt;Amy Siu, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard Weikum, Saarland Informatics CampusSaarbrücken&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Social Networks Under Stress&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Romero, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Brian Uzzi, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HypTrails: A Bayesian Approach for Comparing Hypotheses About Human Trails on the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Philipp Singer, GESIS - Leibniz Institute for the Social Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Denis Helic, Graz University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Hotho, University of Würzburg&lt;br /&gt;Markus Strohmaier, GESIS - Leibniz Institute for the Social Sciences&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Estimation for High Similarities using Odd Sketches&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Mitzenmacher, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Rasmus Pagh, IT University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Ninh Pham, IT University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;No Country for Old Members: User Lifecycle and Linguistic Change in Online Communities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristian Danescu-Niculescu-Mizil, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Robert West, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Jurafsky, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jure Leskovec, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Potts, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Counting Beyond a Yottabyte, or how SPARQL 1.1 Property Paths will Prevent Adoption of the Standard&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcelo Arenas, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Sebastián Conca, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Jorge Pérez, Universidad de Chile&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards a theory model for product search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beibei Li, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Anindya Ghose, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Panagiotis G. Ipeirotis, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Factorizing personalized Markov chains for next-basket recommendation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steffen Rendle, Osaka University&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Freudenthaler, University of Hildesheim&lt;br /&gt;Lars Schmidt-Thieme, University of Hildesheim&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hybrid keyword search auctions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ashish Goel, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kamesh Munagala, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IRLbot: Scaling to 6 billion pages and beyond&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hsin-Tsang Lee, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Derek Leonard, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoming Wang, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;br /&gt;Dmitri Loguinov, Texas A&amp;amp;M University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wherefore art thou r3579x?: anonymized social networks, hidden patterns, and structural steganography&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lars Backstrom, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Cynthia Dwork, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Random Sampling from a Search Engine’s Index&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ziv Bar-Yossef &amp;amp; Maxim Gurevich, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Three-level caching for efficient query processing in large Web search engines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiaohui Long &amp;amp; Torsten Suel, Polytechnic Institute of New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic detection of fragments in dynamically generated web pages&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lakshmish Ramaswamy, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Arun Iyengar, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ling Liu, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Fred Douglis, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scaling personalized web search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Glen Jeh &amp;amp; Jennifer Widom, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SemTag and seeker: bootstrapping the semantic web via automated semantic annotation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Dill, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Nadav Eiron, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;David Gibson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Gruhl, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;R. Guha, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Anant Jhingran, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Tapas Kanungo, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sridhar Rajagopalan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Tomkins, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;John A. Tomlin, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Jason Y. Zien, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abstracting application-level web security&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Scott &amp;amp; Richard Sharp, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Engineering Server Driven Consistency for Large Scale Dynamic Web Services&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian Yin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo Alvisi, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Mike Dahlin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Arun Iyengar, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graph Structure in the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei Broder, AltaVista&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Kumar, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Farzin Maghoul, AltaVista&lt;br /&gt;Prabhakar Raghavan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sridhar Rajagopalan, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Raymie Stata, Compaq Systems Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Tomkins, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Janet Wiener, Compaq Systems Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Focused Crawling: A New Approach to Topic-Specific Web Resource Discovery&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Soumen Chakrabarti, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Martin van den Berg, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;br /&gt;Byron Dom, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Interactive Multimedia Jukebox (IMJ): a new paradigm for the on-demand delivery of audio/video&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin C. Almeroth, University of California Santa Barbara&lt;br /&gt;Mostafa H. Ammar, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-WWW/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-WWW/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>World Wide Web</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1999-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Delayed Impact of Fair Machine Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lydia T. Liu, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Dean, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Esther Rolf, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Max Simchowitz, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Moritz Hardt, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Obfuscated Gradients Give a False Sense of Security: Circumventing Defenses to Adversarial Examples&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anish Athalye, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Carlini, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Wagner, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Black-box Predictions via Influence Functions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pang Wei Koh &amp;amp; Percy Liang, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ensuring Rapid Mixing and Low Bias for Asynchronous Gibbs Sampling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher De Sa, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Re, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kunle Olukotun, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Pixel Recurrent Neural Networks&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Van den Oord, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nal Kalchbrenner, Google&lt;br /&gt;Koray Kavukcuoglu, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dueling Network Architectures for Deep Reinforcement Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ziyu Wang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tom Schaul, Google&lt;br /&gt;Matteo Hessel, Google&lt;br /&gt;Hado van Hasselt, Google&lt;br /&gt;Marc Lanctot, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nando de Freitas, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Nearly-Linear Time Framework for Graph-Structured Sparsity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chinmay Hegde, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Piotr Indyk, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ludwig Schmid, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal and Adaptive Algorithms for Online Boosting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alina Beygelzimer, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Satyen Kale, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Haipeng Luo, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding the Limiting Factors of Topic Modeling via Posterior Contraction Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian Tang, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Zhaoshi Meng, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;XuanLong Nguyen, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Qiaozhu Mei, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ming Zhang, Peking University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vanishing Component Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Roi Livni, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;br /&gt;David Lehavi, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Sagi Schein, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Hila Nachlieli, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Shai Shalev Shwartz, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;br /&gt;Amir Globerson, The Hebrew University of Jerusalum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Semidifferential-based Submodular Function Optimization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rishabh Iyer, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Stefanie Jegelka, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Bilmes, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Posterior Sampling via Stochastic Gradient Fisher Scoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sungjin Ahn, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Anoop Korattikara, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Max Welling, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computational Rationalization: The Inverse Equilibrium Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin Waugh, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Brian Ziebart, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Drew Bagnell, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hilbert Space Embeddings of Hidden Markov Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Le Song, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Byron Boots, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Sajid M. Siddiqi, Google&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey Gordon, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Smola, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Structure preserving embedding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Blake Shaw &amp;amp; Tony Jebara, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SVM Optimization: Inverse Dependence on Training Set Size&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shai Shalev-Shwartz &amp;amp; Nathan Srebro, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Information-theoretic metric learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jason V. Davis, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Brian Kulis, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Prateek Jain, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Suvrit Sra, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Inderjit S. Dhillon, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trading convexity for scalability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ronan Collobert, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Fabian Sinz, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Jason Weston, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Léon Bottou, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A support vector method for multivariate performance measures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thorsten Joachims, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Least-Squares Temporal Difference Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin A. Boyan, NASA Ames Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICML/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICML/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Machine Learning</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1998-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mask R-CNN&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Georgia Gkioxari, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Piotr Dollar, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Ross Girshick, Facebook AI Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deep Neural Decision Forests&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Kontschieder, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Madalina Fiterau, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Antonio Criminisi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Samuel Rota Bulò, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Large Scale Image Categorization to Entry-Level Categories&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vicente Ordonez, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Jia Deng, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Yejin Choi, Stony Brook University&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Berg, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Tamara Berg, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Relative Attributes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Devi Parikh, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Kristen Grauman, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discriminative models for multi-class object layout&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chaitanya Desai, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Deva Ramanan, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Charless Fowlkes, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Population Shape Regression From Random Design Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bradley Davis, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;P. Thomas Fletcher, University of Utah&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Bullitt, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Sarang Joshi, University of Utah&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Globally Optimal Estimates for Geometric Reconstruction Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fredrik Kahl, Lund University&lt;br /&gt;Didier Henrion, LAAS-CNRS&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Pedestrians using Patterns of Motion and Appearance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul Viola, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael J. Jones, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Snow, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Image Parsing: Unifying Segmentation, Detection and Recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhuowen Tu, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Xiangrong Chen, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Alan L. Yuille, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Song-Chun Zhu, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Image-based Rendering using Image-based Priors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Yonatan Wexler, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Probabilistic Tracking with Exemplars in a Metric Space&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kentaro Toyama &amp;amp; Andrew Blake, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Space of All Stereo Images&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steven Seitz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Euclidean Reconstruction and Reprojection up to Subgroups&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yi Ma, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Stefano Soatto, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Jana Kosecka, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Sastry, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Theory of Shape by Space Carving&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kiriakos Kutulakos, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Steven Seitz, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Self-Calibration and Metric Reconstruction in spite of Varying and Unknown Internal Camera Parameters&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marc Pollefeys, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Reinhard Koch, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Luc Van Gool, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Problem of Degeneracy in Structure and Motion Recovery from Uncalibrated Image Sequences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Phil Torr, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICCV/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-ICCV/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Computer Vision</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2002-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adversarial Symbolic Execution for Detecting Concurrency-Related Cache Timing Leaks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shengjian (Daniel) Guo, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Meng Wu, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Chao Wang, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Empirical Study on Crash Recovery Bugs in Large-Scale Distributed Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yu Gao, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Wensheng Dou, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Feng Qin, Ohio State University&lt;br /&gt;Chushu Gao, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Dong Wang, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Jun Wei, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Ruirui Huang, Alibaba Group&lt;br /&gt;Li Zhou, Alibaba Group&lt;br /&gt;Yongming Wu, Alibaba Group&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Race Detection on Compressed Traces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dileep Kini, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Umang Mathur, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Mahesh Viswanathan, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oreo: Detection of Clones in the Twilight Zone&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vaibhav Saini, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Farima Farmahinifarahani, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Yadong Lu, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Baldi, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Crista Lopes, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Impact of Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Practice: An Empirical Study at the Ecosystem Scale&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James C. Davis, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Christy A. Coghlan, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Francisco Servant, Virginia Tech&lt;br /&gt;Dongyoon Lee, Virginia Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Do Android Taint Analysis Tools Keep Their Promises?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Felix Pauck, Paderborn University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Bodden, Paderborn University&lt;br /&gt;Heike Wehrheim, Paderborn University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Power of “Why” and “Why Not”: Enriching Scenario Exploration with Provenance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tim Nelson, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Natasha Danas, Brown University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel J. Dougherty, Worcester Polytechnic Institute&lt;br /&gt;Shriram Krishnamurthi, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cooperative Kernels: GPU Multitasking for Blocking Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tyler Sorensen, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Hugues Evrard, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Alastair F. Donaldson, Imperial College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Misunderstandings in Source Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Gopstein, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Jake Iannacone, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Yu Yan, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Lois DeLong, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Yanyan Zhuang, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Martin K.-C. Yeh, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Justin Cappos, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trade-Offs in Continuous Integration: Assurance, Security, and Flexibility&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Hilton, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Nelson, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Tunnell, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Danny Dig, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discovering Relational Specifications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Calvin Smith, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Gabriel Ferns, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;br /&gt;Aws Albarghouthi, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Diagnosing and Repairing Error Handling Bugs in C&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuchi Tian &amp;amp; Baishakhi Ray, University of Virginia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fairness Testing: Testing Software for Discrimination&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sainyam Galhotra, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Yuriy Brun, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Meliou, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foraging and Navigations Fundamentally: Developers’ Predictions of Value and Cost&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Piorkowski, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Austin Z. Henley, University of Memphis&lt;br /&gt;Tahmid Nabi, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Scott D. Fleming, University of Memphis&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Scaffidi, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Margaret Burnett, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-Representational Security Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eunsuk Kang, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Aleksandar Milicevic, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jackson, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Factors Influencing Code Review Processes in Industry&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tobias Baum, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Olga Liskin, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Kai Niklas, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;br /&gt;Kurt Schneider, Leibniz Universität Hannover&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;API Code Recommendation Using Statistical Learning from Fine-grained Changes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anh Tuan Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Hilton, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Mihai Codoban, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Hoan Anh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Lily Mast, University of Evansville&lt;br /&gt;Eli Rademacher, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Tien N. Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Danny Dig, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proteus: Computing Disjunctive Loop Summary via Path Dependency Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiaofei Xie, Tianjin University&lt;br /&gt;Bihuan Chen, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Yang Liu, Nanyang Technological University&lt;br /&gt;Wei Le, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaohong Li, Tianjin University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Why We Refactor? Confessions of GitHub Contributors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Danilo Silva, Federal University of Minas Gerais&lt;br /&gt;Nikolaos Tsantalis, Concordia University&lt;br /&gt;Marco Tulio Valente, Federal University of Minas Gerais&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Sensitive Data Disclosure via Bi-directional Text Correlation Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jianjun Huang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Xiangyu Zhang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Lin Tan, University of Waterloo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimizing energy consumption of GUIs in Android apps: a multi-objective approach&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mario Linares-Vásquez, College of William and Mary&lt;br /&gt;Gabriele Bavota, Free University of Bolzano&lt;br /&gt;Carlos Eduardo Bernal Cárdenas, College of William and Mary&lt;br /&gt;Rocco Oliveto, University of Molise&lt;br /&gt;Massimiliano Di Penta, University of Sannio&lt;br /&gt;Denys Poshyvanyk, College of William and Mary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Practitioners Perceive the Relevance of Software Engineering Research&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Lo, Singapore Management University&lt;br /&gt;Nachiappan Nagappan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effective Test Suites for Mixed Discrete-Continuous Stateflow Controllers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reza Matinnejad, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Shiva Nejati, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Lionel C. Briand, University of Luxembourg&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Bruckmann, Delphi Automotive Systems&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modeling Readability to Improve Unit Tests&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ermira Daka, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;José Campos, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Gordon Fraser, University of Sheffield&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Dorn, University of Virginia&lt;br /&gt;Westley Weimer, University of Virginia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Measure It? Manage It? Ignore It? Software Practitioners and Technical Debt&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neil A. Ernst, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Stephany Bellomo, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ipek Ozkaya, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Robert L. Nord, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Ian Gorton, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A User-Guided Approach to Program Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ravi Mangal, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Xin Zhang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Aditya V. Nori, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mayur Naik, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MultiSE: Multi-path Symbolic Execution using Value Summaries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;George Necula, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Liang Gong, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Wontae Choi, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Users Beware: Preference Inconsistencies Ahead&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farnaz Behrang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Myra B. Cohen, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Alessandro Orso, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Selection and Presentation Practices for Code Example Summarization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Annie Ying &amp;amp; Martin Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Are Mutants a Valid Substitute for Real Faults in Software Testing?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;René Just, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Darioush Jalali, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Laura Inozemtseva, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Michael Ernst, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Reid Holmes, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Gordon Fraser, University of Sheffield&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;AI: A Lightweight System for Tolerating Concurrency Bugs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mingxing Zhang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yongwei Wu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Shan Lu, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Shanxiang Qi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Jinglei Ren, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Weimin Zheng, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Powering the Static Driver Verifier using Corral&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Akash Lal &amp;amp; Shaz Qadeer, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Natural Coding Conventions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Miltiadis Allamanis, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Earl T. Barr, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Christian Bird, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Charles Sutton, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Architecture Challenges for Internal Software Ecosystems: A Large-Scale Industry Case Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Klaus-Benedikt Schultis, Siemens Corporate Technology&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Elsner, Siemens Corporate Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Lohmann, Friedrich-Alexander University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Seeking the Ground Truth: A Retroactive Study on the Evolution and Migration of Software Libraries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bradley Cossette &amp;amp; Robert Walker, University of Calgary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scalable Test Data Generation from Multidimensional Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emina Torlak, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the Value of Branches with What-if Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Bird &amp;amp; Thomas Zimmermann, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proactive Detection of Collaboration Conflicts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuriy Brun, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Reid Holmes, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David Notkin, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Do Fixes Become Bugs?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zuoning Yin, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Ding Yuan, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Yuanyuan Zhou, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Pasupathy, NetApp&lt;br /&gt;Lakshmi Bairavasundaram, NetApp&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Proving programs robust&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Swarat Chaudhuri, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Sumit Gulwani, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Roberto Lublinerman, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Sara Navidpour, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Creating and evolving developer documentation: understanding the decisions of open source contributors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barthélémy Dagenais &amp;amp; Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Developer Fluency: Achieving True Mastery in Software Projects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minghui Zhou, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Audris Mockus, Avaya Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Staged Concurrent Program Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nishant Sinha &amp;amp; Chao Wang, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Asserting and checking determinism for multithreaded programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Burnim &amp;amp; Koushik Sen, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Darwin: an approach for debugging evolving programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dawei Qi, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Abhik Roychoudhury, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Zhenkai Liang, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Kapil Vaswani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Graph-based Mining of Multiple Object Usage Patterns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tung Thanh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Hoan Anh Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Nam H. Pham, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Jafar M. Al-Kofahi, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Tien N. Nguyen, Iowa State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What makes a good bug report?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Bettenburg, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Sascha Just, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Adrian Schröter, University of Victoria&lt;br /&gt;Cathrin Weiss, University of Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Rahul Premraj, Saarland University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Zimmermann, University of Calgary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient online monitoring of web-service SLAs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Franco Raimondi, University College London&lt;br /&gt;James Skene, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Wolfgang Emmerich, University College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic consistency assessment for query results in dynamic environments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jamie Payton, University of North Carolina at Charlotte&lt;br /&gt;Christine Julien, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Gruia-Catalin Roman, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Globally distributed software development project performance: an empirical analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Narayan Ramasubbu &amp;amp; Rajesh Krishna Balan, Singapore Management University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mining specifications of malicious behavior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mihai Christodorescu, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Somesh Jha, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Kruegel, Vienna University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object and reference immutability using Java generics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yoav Zibin, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alex Potanin, Victoria University of Wellington&lt;br /&gt;Mahmood Ali, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Shay Artzi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Adam Kieżun, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Ernst, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Controlling factors in evaluating path-sensitive error detection techniques&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew B. Dwyer, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Suzette Person, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Elbaum, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SYNERGY: a new algorithm for property checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bhargav S. Gulavani, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Thomas A. Henzinger, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Yamini Kannan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Aditya V. Nori, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Sriram K. Rajamani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Generation of Suggestions for Program Investigation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin P. Robillard, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CUTE: a concolic unit testing engine for C&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koushik Sen, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Gul Agha, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Context- and path-sensitive memory leak detection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yichen Xie &amp;amp; Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reasoning about partial goal satisfaction for requirements and design engineering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emmanuel Letier &amp;amp; Axel van Lamsweerde, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A classification system and analysis for aspect-oriented programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alexandru Salcianu, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Suhabe Bugrara, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eliminating redundancies with a “composition with adaptation” meta-programming technique&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stan Jarzabek, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Li Shubiao, Xi’an Jiaotong University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Family of Test Adequacy Criteria for Database-Driven Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gregory M. Kapfhammer &amp;amp; Mary Lou Soffa, University of Pittsburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting problems caused by component upgrades&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen McCamant &amp;amp; Michael D. Ernst, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Isolating Cause-Effect Chains from Computer Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andreas Zeller, Saarland University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-FSE/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/01/best-paper-awards-FSE/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Software Engineering</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2000-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Classical Verification of Quantum Computation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Urmila Mahadev, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximating Edit Distance Within Constant Factor in Truly Sub-Quadratic Time	Diptarka&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chakraborty, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Debarati Das, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Elazar Goldenberg, The Academic College Of Tel Aviv-Yaffo&lt;br /&gt;Michal Koucký, Computer Science Institute of Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Saks, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pseudorandom Sets in Grassmann Graph have Near-Perfect Expansion&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash Khot, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Dor Minzer, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Muli Safra, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A dichotomy theorem for nonuniform CSPs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei A. Bulatov, Simon Fraser University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Matching Problem in General Graphs is in Quasi-NC&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ola Svensson &amp;amp; Jakub Tarnawski, École polytechnique fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Proof of CSP Dichotomy Conjecture&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dmitriy Zhuk, Lomonosov Moscow State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Settling the Complexity of Computing Approximate Two-Player Nash Equilibria&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aviad Rubinstein, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Learning Requires Good Memory: A Time-Space Lower Bound for Parity Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An average-case depth hierarchy theorem for Boolean circuits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benjamin Rossman, National Institute of Informatics&lt;br /&gt;Rocco A. Servedio, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Li-Yang Tan, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Path Finding Methods for Linear Programming: Solving Linear Programs in O(sqrt(rank)) Iterations and Faster Algorithms for Maximum Flow&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yin Tat Lee &amp;amp; Aaron Sidford, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Navigating Central Path with Electrical Flows: from Flows to Matchings, and Back&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aleksander Mądry, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A multi-prover interactive proof for NEXP sound against entangled provers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tsuyoshi Ito, NEC Labs America&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Vidick, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Polylogarithimic Approximation Algorithm for Edge-Disjoint Paths with Congestion 2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julia Chuzhoy, Toyota Technological Institute at Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Shi Li, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Randomized Rounding Approach to the Traveling Salesman Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shayan Oveis Gharan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Amin Saberi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Mohit Singh, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Polylogarithmic-Competitive Algorithm for the k-Server Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nikhil Bansal, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Niv Buchbinder, Open University&lt;br /&gt;Aleksander Mądry, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Naor, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximating Graphic TSP by Matchings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tobia M¨o;mke &amp;amp; Ola Svensson, Royal Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approximation Algorithms for the Edge-Disjoint Paths Problem via Raecke Decompositions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Andrews, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subexponential Algorithms for Unique Games and Related Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sanjeev Arora, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Boaz Barak, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;David Steurer, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computational Transition at the Uniqueness Threshold&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Allan Sly, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Two Query PCP with Sub-Constant Error&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dana Moshkovitz &amp;amp; Ran Raz, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Space-Efficient Identity Based Encryption Without Pairings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Boneh, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Craig Gentry, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Hamburg, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Settling the Complexity of 2-Player Nash Equilibrium&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xi Chen, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaotie Deng, City University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Unique Games Conjecture, Integrality Gap for Cut Problems and Embeddability of Negative Type Metrics into L1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash A. Khot, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Nisheeth K. Vishnoi, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Correcting Errors Beyond the Guruswami-Sudan Radius in Polynomial Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farzad Parvaresh &amp;amp; Alexander Vardy, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cryptography in NC0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benny Applebaum, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Yuval Ishai, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Eyal Kushilevitz, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hardness of Approximating the Shortest Vector Problem in Lattices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subhash Khot, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Impossibility of Dimension Reduction in L1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bo Brinkman &amp;amp; Moses Charikar, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Dichotomy Theorem for Constraints on a Three-Element Set&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrei A. Bulatov, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minimizing Congestion in General Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Harald Räcke, Paderborn University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constant-Round Coin-Tossing with a Man in the Middle or Realizing the Shared Random String Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Boaz Barak, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-FOCS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-FOCS/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Theory</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2000-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Taskonomy: Disentangling Task Transfer Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amir R. Zamir, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Sax, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;William Shen, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Leonidas Guibas, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jitendra Malik, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Silvio Savarese, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Densely Connected Convolutional Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhuang Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Gao Huang, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Laurens van der Maaten, Facebook AI Research&lt;br /&gt;Kilian Q. Weinberger, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning from Simulated and Unsupervised Images through Adversarial Training&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ashish Shrivastava, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Tomas Pfister, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Oncel Tuzel, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Josh Susskind, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Wenda Wang, Apple Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Russ Webb, Apple Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deep Residual Learning for Image Recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiangyu Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shaoqing Ren, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jian Sun, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DynamicFusion: Reconstruction and Tracking of Non-rigid Scenes in Real-Time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Richard A. Newcombe, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Steven M. Seitz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Camera Motion Reveals About Shape with Unknown BRDF&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Manmohan Chandraker, NEC Labs America&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast, Accurate Detection of 100,000 Object Classes on a Single Machine&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mark A. Ruzon, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mark Segal, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jonathon Shlens, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sudheendra Vijayanarasimhan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jay Yagnik, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Simple Prior-free Method for Non-Rigid Structure-from-Motion Factorization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuchao Dai, Northwestern Polytechnical University&lt;br /&gt;Hongdong Li, Australian National University&lt;br /&gt;Mingyi He, Northwestern Polytechnical University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-time Human Pose Recognition in Parts from Single Depth Images&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jamie Shotton, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mat Cook, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Toby Sharp, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mark Finocchio, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Richard Moore, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alex Kipman, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Blake, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Computation of Robust Low-Rank Matrix Approximations in the Presence of Missing Data using the L1 Norm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anders Eriksson &amp;amp; Anton va den Hendel, University of Adelaide&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Single Image Haze Removal Using Dark Channel Prior&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiming He, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;br /&gt;Jian Sun, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoou Tang, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Global Stereo Reconstruction under Second Order Smoothness Priors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Oliver Woodford, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Ian Reid, Oxford Brookes University&lt;br /&gt;Philip Torr, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fitzgibbon, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beyond Sliding Windows: Object Localization by Efficient Subwindow Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chistoph H. Lampert, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Matthew B. Blaschko, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Hodmann, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic 3D Scene Analysis from a Moving Vehicle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bastian Leibe, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Nico Cornelis, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Kurt COrnelis, Katholieke Universiteit Leuven&lt;br /&gt;Luc Van Gool, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Putting Objects in Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Derek Hoiem, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alexei Efros, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Martial Hebert, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-Time Non-Rigid Surface Detection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julien Pilet, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Lepetit, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Pascal Fua, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Programmable Imaging using a Digital Micromirror Array&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shree K. Nayar, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Vlad Branzoi, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Terry E. Boult, University of Colorado&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object Class Recognition by Unsupervised Scale-Invariant Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rob Fergus, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Pietro Perona, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Zisserman, University of Oxford&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Morphable 3D models from video&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Brand, Mitsubishi Electric Research Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-Time Tracking of Non-Rigid Objects using Mean Shift&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dorin Comaniciu, Siemens Corporate Research&lt;br /&gt;Visvanathan Ramesh, Siemens Corporate Research&lt;br /&gt;Peter Meer, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CVPR/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/31/best-paper-awards-CVPR/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Computer Vision</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
