<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PXZHANG</title>
    <description>这里是 @PXZHANG张培歆 的个人网站</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:31:24 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:31:24 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2005-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Wikipedia With a Broader Lens: Quantifying the Value of Wikipedia’s Relationships with Other Large Scale Online Communities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicholas Vincent, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Isaac Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Brent Hecht, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Keeping a Low Profile? Technology, Risk and Privacy among Undocumented Immigrants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tamy Guberek, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Allison McDonald, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Sylvia Simioni, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Abraham H. Mhaidli, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Kentaro Toyama, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Florian Schaub, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Addressing Age-Related Bias in Sentiment Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Diaz, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Isaac Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Amanda Lazar, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Darren Gergle, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wall++: Room-Scale Interactive and Context-Aware Sensing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yang Zhang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chouchang (Jack) Yang, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alanson Sample, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design for Collaborative Survival: An Inquiry into Human-Fungi Relationships&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jen Liu, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;br /&gt;Daragh Byrne, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Laura Devendorf, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Expressive Time Series Querying with Hand-Drawn Scale-Free Sketches&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Miro Mannino &amp;amp; Azza Abouzied, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pinpointing: Precise Head- and Eye-Based Target Selection for Augmented Reality&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mikko Kytö, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Barrett Ens, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Thammathip Piumsomboon, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Gun A. Lee, University of South Australia&lt;br /&gt;Mark Billinghurst, University of South Australia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Streets for People: Engaging Children in Placemaking Through a Socio-technical Process&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sean Peacock, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Robert Anderson, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Clara Crivellaro, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Let’s Talk About Race: Identity, Chatbots, and AI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ari Schlesinger, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kenton P. O’Hara, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alex S. Taylor, City University of London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“A Stalker’s Paradise”: How Intimate Partner Abusers Exploit Technology&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diana Freed, Cornell Tech&lt;br /&gt;Jackeline Palmer, Hunter College&lt;br /&gt;Diana Minchala, City College of New York&lt;br /&gt;Karen Levy, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Ristenpart, Cornell Tech&lt;br /&gt;Nicola Dell, Cornell Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HARK No More: On the Preregistration of CHI Experiments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Alan Dix, University of Birmingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hoarding and Minimalism: Tendencies in Digital Data Preservation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Francesco Vitale, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Izabelle Janzen, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Joanna McGrenere, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semi-Automated Coding for Qualitative Research: A User-Centered Inquiry and Initial Prototypes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Megh Marathe &amp;amp; Kentaro Toyama, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making as Expression: Informing Design with People with Complex Communication Needs through Art Therapy&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanda Lazar, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Jessica L. Feuston, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Caroline Edasis, Mather LifeWays&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Relevant are Incidental Power Poses for HCI?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yvonne Jansen, Sorbonne Université&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Illustrator: Augmenting Vector Design Tools with Lazy Data Binding for Expressive Visualization Authoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhicheng Liu, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;John Thompson, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alan Wilson, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Mira Dontcheva, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;James Delorey, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Sam Grigg, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Bernard Kerr, Adobe Systems Inc.&lt;br /&gt;John Stasko, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Extending Manual Drawing Practices with Artist-Centric Programming Tools&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jennifer, Jacobs Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Joel Brandt, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Radomír Mech, Adobe Research&lt;br /&gt;Mitchel Resnick, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Experiencing the Body as Play&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian ‘Floyd’ Mueller, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Richard Byrne, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Josh Andres, RMIT University&lt;br /&gt;Rakesh Patibanda, RMIT University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gender Recognition or Gender Reductionism?: The Social Implications of Embedded Gender Recognition Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foad Hamidi, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Morgan Klaus Scheuerman, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Stacy M. Branham, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Voice Interfaces in Everyday Life&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Porcheron, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Reeves, The University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Sharples, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Project Zanzibar: A Portable and Flexible Tangible Interaction Platform&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Villar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Cletheroe, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Greg Saul, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Christian Holz, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Tim Regan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Oscar Salandin, Microsoft Researcch&lt;br /&gt;Misha Sra, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hui-Shyong Yeo, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;William Field, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haiyan Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design Within a Patriarchal Society: Opportunities and Challenges in Designing for Rural Women in Bangladesh&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sharifa Sultana, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;François Guimbretière, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Nicola Dell, Cornell Tech&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Agile 3D Sketching with Air Scaffolding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yongkwan Kim, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Sang-Gyun An, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Joon Hyub Lee, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seok-Hyung Bae, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making Core Memory: Design Inquiry into Gendered Legacies of Engineering and Craftwork&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniela K. Rosner, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Samantha Shorey, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brock R. Craft, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Helen Remick, Self-employed&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Illumination Aesthetics: Light as a Creative Material within Computational Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cesar Torres, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jasper O’Leary, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Molly Nicholas, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Eric Paulos, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Organic Primitives: Synthesis and Design of pH-Reactive Materials using Molecular I/O for Sensing Actuation and Interaction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Viirj Kan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Emma Vargo, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Noa Machover, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hiroshi Ishii, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Serena Pan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Weixuan Chen, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Yasuaki Kakehi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ShareVR: Enabling Co-Located Experiences for Virtual Reality between HMD and Non-HMD Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jan Gugenheimer, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Evgeny Stemasov, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Julian Frommel, Ulm University&lt;br /&gt;Enrico Rukzio, Ulm University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;You Want Me to Work with Who?: Stakeholder Perceptions of Automated Team Formation in Project-based Courses&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Farnaz Jahanbakhsh, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Wai-Tat Fu, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Darko Marinov, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Brian Bailey, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stories from Survivors: Privacy &amp;amp; Security Practices when Coping with Intimate Partner Abuse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tara Matthews, Google&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen O’Leary, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Anna Turner, Google&lt;br /&gt;Manya Sleeper, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jill Palzkill Woelfer, Google&lt;br /&gt;Martin Shelton, Google&lt;br /&gt;Cori Manthorne, Community Overcoming Relationship Abuse&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth F. Churchill, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sunny Consolvo, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Critical Lens on Dementia and Design in HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanda Lazar, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Caroline Edasis, Mather LifeWays&lt;br /&gt;Anne Marie Piper, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modelling Learning of New Keyboard Layouts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jussi P. P. Jokinen, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Sayan Sarcar, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Chaklam Silpasuwanchai, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Zhenxin Wang, Kochi University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Xiangshi Ren, Kochi University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Gamified Applications that Make Safe Driving More Engaging&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fabius Steinberger, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ronald Schroeter, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Marcus Foth, Queensland University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Johnson, Queensland University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;mHealth for Maternal Mental Health: Everyday Wisdom in Ethical Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marguerite Barry, Trinity College Dublin&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Doherty, Trinity College Dublin&lt;br /&gt;Jose Marcano Belisario, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Josip Car, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Cecily Morrison, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Doherty, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Explaining the Gap: Visualizing One’s Predictions Improves Recall and Comprehension of Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yea-Seul Kim, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Katharina Reinecke, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Hullman, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reflective Practicum: A Framework of Sensitising Concepts to Design for Transformative Reflection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Petr Slovák, Vienna University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Frauenberger, Vienna University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Geraldine Fitzpatrick, Vienna University of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Can Be Predicted from Six Seconds of Driver Glances?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lex Fridman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Heishiro, Toyoda Toyota Collaborative Safety Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Sean Seaman, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Bobbie Seppelt, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Linda Angell, Touchstone Evaluations&lt;br /&gt;Joonbum Lee, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Mehler, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Reimer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Flash Organizations: Crowdsourcing Complex Work by Structuring Crowds As Organizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Melissa A. Valentine, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniela Retelny, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alexandra To, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Negar Rahmati, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Tulsee Doshi, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael S. Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design and Evaluation of a Data-Driven Password Meter&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Blase Ur, University of Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Felicia Alfieri, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Maung Aung, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Lujo Bauer, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Nicolas Christin, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Colnago, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Lorrie Faith Cranor, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Henry Dixon, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Pardis Emami Naeini, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hana Habib, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Noah Johnson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;William Melicher, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Public Evaluation: Quantifying Experimenter Intervention&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Julie R. Williamson &amp;amp; John Williamson, University of Glasgow&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Is Interaction?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BIGnav: Bayesian Information Gain for Guiding Multiscale Navigation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wanyu Liu, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;br /&gt;Rafael Lucas D’Oliveira, University of Campinas&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Rioul, Université Paris-Saclay&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Menstrual Tracking to Inform the Design of Personal Informatics Tools&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel A. Epstein, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Nicole B. Lee, Independent Researcher&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer H. Kang, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Elena Agapie, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Schroeder, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Laura R. Pina, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Fogarty, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Julie A. Kientz, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Sean Munson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building a Personalized, Auto-Calibrating Eye Tracker from User Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Xuelin Huang, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Tiffany C.K. Kwok, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Grace Ngai, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen C.F. Chan, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;br /&gt;Hong Va Leong, Hong Kong Polytechnic University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Email in a Multi-Account, Multi-Device World&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marta E. Cecchinato, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Abigail Sellen, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Milad Shokouhi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Smyth, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Looking at the Vagina through Labella&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Teresa Almeida, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Rob Comber, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Gavin Wood, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Dean Saraf, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Madeline Balaam, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enhancing Cross-Device Interaction Scripting with Interactive Illustrations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pei-Yu (Peggy) Chi, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Yang Li, Google&lt;br /&gt;Björn Hartmann, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Empath: Understanding Topic Signals in Large-Scale Text&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan Fast, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Binbin Chen, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Bernstein, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Effect of Visual Appearance on the Performance of Continuous Sliders and Visual Analogue Scales&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin Matejka, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Glueck, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HCI Research as Problem-Solving&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RapID: A Framework for Fabricating Low-Latency Interactive Objects with RFID Tags&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Spielberg, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alanson Sample, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Mankoff, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;James McCann, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enabling Designers to Foresee Which Colors Users Cannot See&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Katharina Reinecke, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Brooks, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Movement-based Play With Young People Using Powered Wheelchairs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kathrin Gerling, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Kieran Hicks, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Michael Kalyn, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Adam Evans, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Conor Linehan, University College Cork&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Developing and Validating the User Burden Scale: A Tool for Assessing User Burden in Computing Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hyewon Suh, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Nina Shahriaree, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Eric B. Hekler, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Julie A. Kientz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Momentary Pleasure or Lasting Meaning?: Distinguishing Eudaimonic and Hedonic User Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elisa D. Mekler, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbæk, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding and Mitigating the Effects of Device and Cloud Service Design Decisions on the Environmental Footprint of Digital Infrastructure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Preist, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Schien, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;Eli Blevis, Indiana University Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haptic Wave: A Cross-Modal Interface for Visually Impaired Audio Producers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Atau Tanaka &amp;amp; Adam Parkinson, Goldsmiths&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“I don’t Want to Wear a Screen”: Probing Perceptions of and Possibilities for Dynamic Displays on Clothing Laura Devendorf&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laura Devendorf, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Joanne Lo, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Noura Howell, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Jung Lin Lee, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Nan-Wei Gong, Google&lt;br /&gt;M. Emre Karagozler, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiho Fukuhara, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Eric Paulos, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kimiko Ryokai, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dear Diary: Teens Reflect on Their Weekly Online Risk Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pamela Wisniewski, University of Central Florida&lt;br /&gt;Heng Xu, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Mary Beth Rosson, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel F. Perkins, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;John M. Carroll, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Object-Oriented Drawing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haijun Xia, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Araujo, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Wigdor, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Foraging Among an Overabundance of Similar Variants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sruti Srinivasa Ragavan, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Sandeep Kaur Kuttal, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Charles Hill, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Anita Sarma, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;David Piorkowski, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Margaret Burnett, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lock n’ LoL: Group-based Limiting Assistance App to Mitigate Smartphone Distractions in Group Activities&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minsam Ko, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seungwoo Choi, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Koji Yatani, University of Tokyo&lt;br /&gt;Uichin Lee, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learn Piano with BACh: An Adaptive Learning Interface that Adjusts Task Difficulty Based on Brain State&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beste F. Yuksel, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Kurt B. Oleson, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Lane Harrison, Worcester Polytechnic Institute&lt;br /&gt;Evan M. Peck, Bucknell University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Afergan, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Remco Chang, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Robert JK Jacob, Tufts University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FlexCase: Enhancing Mobile Interaction with a Flexible Sensing and Display Cover&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Rendl, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Parzer, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Sean Fanello, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Martin Zirkl, Institute of Surface Technologies and Photonics&lt;br /&gt;Gregor Scheipl, Joanneum Research Forschungsgesellschaft m.b.H&lt;br /&gt;Michael Haller, University of Applied Sciences Upper Austria&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Project Jacquard: Interactive Digital Textiles at Scale&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nan-Wei Gong, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiho Fukuhara, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mustafa Emre Karagozler, Google&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Schwesig, Google&lt;br /&gt;Karen E. Robinson, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Smart Touch: Improving Touch Accuracy for People with Motor Impairments with Template Matching&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martez E. Mott, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Radu-Daniel Vatavu, University Stefan cel Mare of Suceava&lt;br /&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Colorado Boulder&lt;br /&gt;Jacob O. Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What Makes Interruptions Disruptive?: A Process-Model Account of the Effects of the Problem State Bottleneck on Task Interruption and Resumption&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jelmer P. Borst, University of Groningen&lt;br /&gt;Niels A. Taatgen, University of Groningen&lt;br /&gt;Hedderik van Rijn, University of Groningen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;VelociTap: Investigating Fast Mobile Text Entry using Sentence-Based Decoding of Touchscreen Keyboard Input&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Keith Vertanen, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Haythem Memmi, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Justin Emge, Montana Tech&lt;br /&gt;Shyam Reyal, University of St Andrews&lt;br /&gt;Per Ola Kristensson, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sharing is Caring: Assistive Technology Designs on Thingiverse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Erin Buehler, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Stacy Branham, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Abdullah Ali, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy J. Chang, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Megan Kelly Hofmann, Colorado State University&lt;br /&gt;Amy Hurst, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tiree Energy Pulse: Exploring Renewable Energy Forecasts on the Edge of the Grid&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Will Simm, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Maria Angela Ferrario, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Adrian Friday, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Newman, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Forshaw, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Mike Hazas, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Alan Dix, Lancaster University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unequal Representation and Gender Stereotypes in Image Search Results for Occupations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Kay, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Cynthia Matuszek, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;Sean A. Munson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Resilience Mitigates the Negative Effects of Adolescent Internet Addiction and Online Risk Exposure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pamela Wisniewski, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Haiyan Jia, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Na Wang, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Saijing Zheng, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Heng Xu, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;Mary Beth Rosson, Pennsylvania State University&lt;br /&gt;John Carroll, Pennsylvania State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Affordance++: Allowing Objects to Communicate Dynamic Use&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pedro Lopes, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrik Jonell, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Political Deliberation Environments to Support Interactions in the Public Sphere&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryan Semaan, Syracuse University&lt;br /&gt;Heather Faucett, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Scott P. Robertson, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;br /&gt;Misa Maruyama, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;br /&gt;Sara Douglas, University of Hawaii at Manoa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ColourID: Improving Colour Identification for People with Impaired Colour Vision&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Alan R. Andrade, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Ross D. Teviotdale, University of Dundee&lt;br /&gt;Dylan L. Knowles, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Craig Stewart, University of Dundee&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fluid Grouping: Quantifying Group Engagement around Interactive Tabletop Exhibits in the Wild&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian Block, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;James Hammerman, TERC&lt;br /&gt;Michael Horn, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Amy Spiegel, University of Nebraska-Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Christiansen, TERC&lt;br /&gt;Brenda Phillips, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Judy Diamond, University of Nebraska State Museum&lt;br /&gt;E. Margaret Evans, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Chia Shen, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sangeet Swara: A Community-Moderated Voice Forum in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aditya Vashistha, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gaetano Borriello, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;William Thies, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Acoustruments: Passive, Acoustically-Driven, Interactive Controls for Handheld Devices	Gierad&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laput, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Brockmeyer, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;iSkin: Flexible, Stretchable and Visually Customizable On-Body Touch Sensors for Mobile Computing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Weigel, Max Planck Institut&lt;br /&gt;Tong Lu, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Telecom ParisTech&lt;br /&gt;Antti Oulasvirta, Aalto University&lt;br /&gt;Carmel Majidi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jürgen Steimle, Max Planck Institut&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patina Engraver: Visualizing Activity Logs as Patina in Fashionable Trackers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Moon-Hwan Lee, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Seijin Cha, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Tek-Jin Nam, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BaseLase: An Interactive Focus+Context Laser Floor&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jörg Müller, Aarhus University&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Eberle, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Constantin Schmidt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Social Impact of a Robot Co-Worker in Industrial Settings&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Allison Sauppé &amp;amp; Bilge Mutlu, University of Wisconsin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“I always assumed that I wasn’t really that close to [her]”: Reasoning about Invisible Algorithms in the News Feed&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Motahhare Eslami, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Aimee Rickman, California State University&lt;br /&gt;Kristen Vaccaro, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Amirhossein Aleyasen, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Andy Vuong, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Hamilton, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Christian Sandvig, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding and Supporting Fathers and Fatherhood on Social Media Sites&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tawfiq Ammari &amp;amp; Sarita Schoenebeck, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lightweight Relief Shearing for Enhanced Terrain Perception on Interactive Maps&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wesley Willett, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Bernhard Jenny, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Tobias Isenberg, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Dragicevic, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From User-Centered to Adoption-Centered Design: A Case Study of an HCI Research Innovation Becoming a Product&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Parmit K. Chilana, University of Waterloo&lt;br /&gt;Andrew J. Ko, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Growing Closer on Facebook: Changes in Tie Strength Through Social Network Site Use&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Moira Burke, Facebook&lt;br /&gt;Robert Kraut, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Duet: Exploring Joint Interactions on a Smart Phone and a Smart Watch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiang Anthony Chen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Tovi Grossman, Autodesk Research&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Wigdor, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RetroDepth: 3D Silhouette Sensing for High-Precision Input On and Above Physical Surfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jakub Dostal, University of St Andrews&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Rhemann, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Cem Keskin, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Zach, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jamie Shotton, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Large, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Steven Bathiche, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Matthias Niessner, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;D. Alex Butler, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Sean Fanello, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia&lt;br /&gt;Vivek Pradeep, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Estimating the Social Costs of Friendsourcing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Rzeszotarski &amp;amp; Meredith Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Human Values in Curating a Human Rights Media Archive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abigail Durrant, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Reeves, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emerging Sites of HCI Innovation: Hackerspaces, Hardware Startups &amp;amp; Incubators&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Silvia Lindtner, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Garnet Hertz, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Paul Dourish, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effects of Display Size and Navigation Type on a Classification Task&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Can Liu, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Eric Lecolinet, Telecom ParisTech&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;George Fitzmaurice, Autodesk Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards Accurate and Practical Predictive Models of Active-Vision-Based Visual Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Kieras, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Hornof, University of Oregon&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Real-time Feedback for Improving Medication Taking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Lee, Philips Research&lt;br /&gt;Anind Dey, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making Sustainability Sustainable: Challenges in the Design of Eco-Interaction Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rayoung Yang, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Mark Newman, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consumed Endurance: A Metric to Quantify Arm Fatigue of Mid-Air Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anders Markussen, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Mikkel Jakobsen, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Kasper Hornbaek, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Type-Hover-Swipe in 96 Bytes: A Motion Sensing Mechanical Keyboard&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stuart A Taylor, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Cem Keskin, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Otmar Hilliges, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Shahram Izadi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;John Helmes, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Structured Labeling for Facilitating Concept Evolution in Machine Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Todd Kulesza, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Saleema Amershi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rich Caruana, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Danyel Fisher, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Denis Charles, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;MixFab: a Mixed-Reality Environment for Personal Fabrication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christian Weichel, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;Manfred Lau, Lancaster University&lt;br /&gt;David Kim, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Nicolas Villar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Hans W Gellersen, Lancaster University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing for Slowness, Anticipation and Re-visitation: A Long Term Field Study of the Photobox&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;William Odom, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Abigail Sellen, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Richard Banks, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Tim Regan, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Mark Selby, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;John Zimmerman, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;“Narco” Emotions: Affect and Desensitization in Social Media during the Mexican Drug War&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Munmun De Choudhury, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andres Monroy-Hernandez, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Gloria Mark, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Multitasking Through Parallelized Strategy Exploration and Individualized Cognitive Modeling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yunfeng Zhang &amp;amp; Anthony Hornof, University of Oregon&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Labor Dynamics in a Mobile Micro-Task Market&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohamed Musthag &amp;amp; Deepak Ganesan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;What is “Critical” About Critical Design?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Bardzell &amp;amp; Shaowen Bardzell, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SPRWeb: Preserving Subjective Responses to Website Colour Schemes through Automatic Recolouring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David R. Flatla, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Katharina Reinecke, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Krzysztof Z. Gajos, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;LaserOrigami: Laser-Cutting 3D Objects	Stefanie Mueller, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bastian Kruck, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mind the Theoretical Gap: Interpreting, Using, and Developing Behavioral Theory in HCI Research&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric B. Hekler, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Predrag Klasnja, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jon Froehlich, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Matthew P. Buman, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Screenfinity: Extending the Perception Area of Content on Very Large Public Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Constantin Schmidt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Jörg Müller, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reasons to Question Seven Segment Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Harold Thimbleby, Swansea University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Navigation-Based File Retrieval&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Fitchett, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Dubuque Electricity Portal: Evaluation of a City-Scale Residential Electricity Consumption Feedback System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Erickson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ming Li, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Younghun Kim, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ajay Deshpande, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Sambit Sahu, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Tian Chao, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Piyawadee Sukaviriya, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Milind Naphade, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;At Home with Agents: Exploring Attitudes Towards Future Smart Energy Infrastructures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Nadia Pantidi, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Khaled Bachour, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Stuart Moran, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Job Opportunities through Entertainment: Virally Spread Speech-Based Services for Low-Literate Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Agha Ali Raza, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Farhan Ul Haq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Zain Tariq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Mansoor Pervaiz, Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;Samia Razaq, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Umar Saif, Lahore University of Management Sciences&lt;br /&gt;Roni Rosenfeld, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IllumiRoom: Peripheral Projected Illusions for Interactive Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brett Jones, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Hrvoje Benko, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Eyal Ofek, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Andrew D. Wilson, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Efficacy of Human Post-Editing for Language Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spence Green, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Heer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christopher D. Manning, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Analyzing User-Generated YouTube Videos to Understand Touchscreen Use by People with Motor Impairments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lisa Anthony, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;br /&gt;YooJin Kim, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Leah Findlater, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Turkopticon: Interrupting Worker Invisibility in Amazon Mechanical Turk&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lilly Irani, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;M. Six Silberman, Bureau of Economic Interpretation&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Webzeitgeist: Design Mining the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjitha Kumar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Satyanarayan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Cesar Torres, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Maxine Lim, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Salman Ahmad, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Scott R. Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jerry O. Talton, Intel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weighted Graph Comparison Techniques for Brain Connectivity Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Basak Alper, University of California Santa Barbara&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Bach, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Nathalie Riche, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Tobias Isenberg, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Daniel Fekete, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Many Faces of Facebook: Experiencing Social Media as Performance, Exhibition, and Personal Archive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xuan Zhao, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Niloufar Salehi, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Sasha Naranjit, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Sara Alwaalan, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Voida, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Cosley, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Uncomfortable Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Chris Greenhalgh, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Gabriella Giannachi, University of Exeter&lt;br /&gt;Brendan Walker, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joe Marshall, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ClayVision: The (Elastic) Image of the City&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuichiro Takeuchi, Sony Computer Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Ken Perlin, New York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Revisiting the Jacquard Loom: Threads of History and Current Patterns in HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ylva Fernaeus, KTH Royal Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Martin Jonssonm, Södertörn University&lt;br /&gt;Jakob Tholanderm, Stockholm University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Personas and Decision Making in the Design Process: An Ethnographic Case Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Erin Friess, University of North Texas&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting Error-Related Negativity for Interaction Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chi Vi &amp;amp; Sriram Subramanian, University of Bristol&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Observational and Experimental Investigation of Typing Behaviour using Virtual Keyboards for Mobile Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Niels Henze, University of Oldenburg&lt;br /&gt;Enrico Rukzio, University of Duisburg-Essen&lt;br /&gt;Susanne Boll, University of Oldenburg&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Looking Glass: A Field Study on Noticing Interactivity of Shop Windows&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jörg Müller, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Robert Walter, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Gilles Bailly, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Nischt, Technische Universität Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Florian Alt, University of Stuttgart&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Touché: Enhancing Touch Interaction on Humans, Screens, Liquids, and Everyday Objects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Munehiko Sato, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Ivan Poupyrev, Disney Research&lt;br /&gt;Chris Harrison, Disney Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Affordances in HCI: Toward a Mediated Action Perspective&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Victor Kaptelinin, University of Bergen&lt;br /&gt;Bonnie Nardi, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Rhythmic Patterns as an Input Method&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emilien Ghomi, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Guillaume Faure, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Stephane Huot, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Michel Beaudouin-Lafon, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Normal Natural Troubles of Driving with GPS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barry Brown, Stockholm University&lt;br /&gt;Eric Laurier, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Communitysourcing: Engaging Local Crowds to Perform Expert Work Via Physical Kiosks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kurtis Heimerl, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Brian Gawalt, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kuang Chen, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Tapan S. Parikh, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Björn Hartmann, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Command Selection with CommandMaps&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joey Scarr, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Andrea Bunt, University of Manitoba&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Empathy, Participatory Design and People with Dementia&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stephen Lindsay, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Katie Britain, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jackson, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Cassim Ladha, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Karim Ladha, Newcastle University&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Olivier, Newcastle University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Usable Gestures for Blind People: Understanding Preference and Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shaun K. Kane, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Richard E. Ladner, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Effects of Community Size and Contact Rate in Synchronous Social Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryen W. White, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Richardson, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yandong Liu, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Teenagers and Their Virtual Possessions: Design Opportunities and Issues&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;William Odom, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;John Zimmerman, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jodi Forlizzi, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Enhancing Physicality in Touch Interaction with Programmable Friction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Levesque, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Louise Oram, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karon MacLean, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Andy Cockburn, University of Canterbury&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas D. Marchuk, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Johnson, Northwestern University&lt;br /&gt;J. Edward Colgate, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mid-air Pan-and-Zoom on Wall-sized Displays&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mathieu Nancel, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Julie Wagner, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Emmanuel Pietriga, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Chapuis, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bricolage: Example-Based Retargeting for Web Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjitha Kumar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jerry Talton, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Salman Ahmad, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Scott Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Synchronous Interaction Among Hundreds: An Evaluation of a Conference in an Avatar-based Virtual Environment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Erickson, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;N. Sadat Shami, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Wendy A. Kellogg, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;David W. Levine, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;In the Shadow of Misperception: Assistive Technology Use and Social Interactions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kristen Shinohara &amp;amp; Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Why is My Internet Slow?: Making Network Speeds Visible&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marshini Chetty, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;David Haslem, Orange Sparkle Ball&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Baird, Amazon&lt;br /&gt;Ugochi Ofoha, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Bethany Sumner, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Grinter, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ease of Juggling: Studying the Effects of Manual Multitasking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Antti Oulasvirta &amp;amp; Joanna Bergstrom-Lehtovirta, Aalto University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automics: souvenir generating photoware for theme parks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Abigail Durrant, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Duncan Rowland, University of Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;David Kirk, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Joel E. Fischer, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Derek McAuley, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Michael A. Peshkin, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Your Noise is My Command: Sensing Gestures Using the Body as an Antenna&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gabe Cohn, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Shwetak N. Patel, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Desney Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Review Spotlight: A User Interface for Summarizing User-generated Reviews Using Adjective-Noun Word Pairs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Koji Yatani, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Michael Novati, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Trusty, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Khai N. Truong, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lumino: Tangible Blocks for Tabletop Computers Based on Glass Fiber Bundles&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Torsten Becker, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;br /&gt;Frederik Rudeck, Hasso Plattner Institute&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mapping the Landscape of Sustainable HCI&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carl DiSalvo, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Hrönn Brynjarsdóttir, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Occlusion-Aware Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Vogel &amp;amp; Ravin Balakrishnan, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Avaaj Otalo — A Field Study of an Interactive Voice Forum for Small Farmers in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neil Patel, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Deepti Chittamuru, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Anupam Jain, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Paresh Dave, Development Support Center&lt;br /&gt;Tapan S. Parikh, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How does search behavior change as search becomes more difficult?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Anne Aula, Google&lt;br /&gt;Rehan M. Khan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Zhiwei Guan, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Tower of Babel Meets Web 2.0: User-Generated Content and its Applications in a Multilingual Context&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brent Hecht &amp;amp; Darren Gergle, Northwestern University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Skinput: Appropriating the Body as an Input Surface&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Harrison, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Desney Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Dan Morris, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mobile-izing Health Workers in Rural India&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Divya Ramachandran, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;John Canny, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Prabhu Dutta Das, Dhirubhai Ambani Institute of Information and Communications Technology&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Design of Eco-Feedback Technology&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jon Froehlich, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Leah Findlater, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Landay, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feminist HCI: Taking Stock and Outlining an Agenda for Design&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shaowen Bardzell, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Prefab: Implementing Advanced Behaviors Using Pixel-Based Reverse Engineering of Interface Structure&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Morgan Dixon &amp;amp; James Fogarty, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Useful Junk? The Effects of Visual Embellishment on Comprehension and Memorability of Charts&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scott Bateman, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Regan L. Mandryk, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Carl Gutwin, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Genest, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;David McDine, University of Saskatchewan&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Brooks, University of Saskatchewan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Interaction to Trajectories: Designing Coherent Journeys Through User Experiences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Gabriella Giannachi, University of Exeter&lt;br /&gt;Boriana Koleva, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Tom Rodden, University of Nottingham&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sizing the Horizon: The Effects of Chart Size and Layering on the Graphical Perception of Time Series Visualization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeffrey Heer, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Kong, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Maneesh Agrawala, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Predicting Tie Strength With Social Media&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric Gilbert &amp;amp; Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Musink: Composing Music through Augmented Drawing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Theophanis Tsandilas, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Catherine Letondal, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Mackay, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Social Immersive Media: Pursuing Best Practices for Multi-user Interactive Camera/Projector Exhibits&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scott S. Snibbe, Sona Research&lt;br /&gt;Hayes S. Raffle, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ephemeral Adaptation: The Use of Gradual Onset to Improve Menu Selection Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Leah Findlater, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karyn Moffatt, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Joanna McGrenere, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Jessica Dawson, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Undo and Erase Events as Indicators of Usability Problems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Akers, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Simpson, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robin Jeffries, Google&lt;br /&gt;Terry Winograd, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;In-Car GPS Navigation: Engagement with and Disengagement from the Environment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gilly Leshed, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Theresa Velden, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Oya Rieger, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Blazej Kot, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Phoebe Sengers, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving the Performance of Motor-Impaired Users with Automatically-Generated, Ability-Based Interfaces&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Krzysztof Z. Gajos, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel S. Weld, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Large Scale Analysis of Web Revisitation Patterns&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eytan Adar, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jaime Teevan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Susan T. Dumais, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designs on Dignity: Perceptions of Technology Among the Homeless&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher A. Le Dantec &amp;amp; W. Keith Edwards, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Network in the Garden: An Empirical Analysis of Social Media in Rural Life&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eric Gilbert, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Karrie Karahalios, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Christian Sandvig, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multimodal collaborative handwriting training for visually-impaired people&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beryl Plimmer, University of Auckland&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Crossan, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Stephen A. Brewster, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Rachel Blagojevic, University of Auckland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Error Model for Pointing Based on Fitts’ Law&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Wobbrock, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Edward Cutrell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Susumu Harada, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;I. Scott MacKenzie, York University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multiview: improving trust in group video conferencing through spatial faithfulness&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David T. Nguyen &amp;amp; John Canny, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Software or wetware?: discovering when and why people use digital prosthetic memory&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vaiva Kalnikaité &amp;amp; Steve Whittaker, University of Sheffield&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shift: a technique for operating pen-based interfaces using touch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Vogel, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Baudisch, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Authoring sensor-based interactions by demonstration with direct manipulation and pattern recognition&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Björn Hartmann, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Leith Abdulla, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Manas Mittal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Scott R. Klemmer, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sustainable interaction design: invention &amp;amp; disposal, renewal &amp;amp; reuse&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eli Blevis, Indiana University at Bloomington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consuming video on Mobile devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kenton O’Hara, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;April Slayden Mitchell, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Alex Vorbau, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trackball text entry for people with motor impairments&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Wobbrock &amp;amp; Brad Myers, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Embedded phenomena: supporting science learning with classroom-sized distributed simulations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom Moher, University of Illinois at Chicago&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A role for haptics in mobile interaction: initial design using a handheld tactile display prototype&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Joseph Luk, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Jérôme Pasquero, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;Shannon Little, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Karon MacLean, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Lévesque, McGill University&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Hayward, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Making space for stories: ambiguity in the design of personal communication systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul M. Aoki, Palo Alto Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Allison Woodruff, Intel Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Examining Task Engagement in Sensor-Based Statistical Models of Human Interruptibility&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Fogarty, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew J. Ko, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Htet Htet Aung, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Elspeth Golden, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Karen P. Tang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Scott E. Hudson, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing the spectator experience&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stuart Reeves, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Steve Benford, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Claire O’Malley, University of Nottingham&lt;br /&gt;Mike Fraser, University of Bristol&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The bubble cursor: enhancing target acquisition by dynamic resizing of the cursor’s activation area&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tovi Grossman &amp;amp; Ravin Balakrishnan, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-CHI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-CHI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Human-Computer Interaction</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2001-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding syntax in human encephalography with beam search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Hale, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Chris Dyer, DeepMind&lt;br /&gt;Adhiguna Kuncoro, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan R. Brennan, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Probabilistic Typology: Deep Generative Models of Vowel Inventories&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryan Cotterell &amp;amp; Jason Eisner, Johns Hopkins University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Non-Arbitrary Form-Meaning Systematicity Using String-Metric Learning for Kernel Regression&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;E. Darío Gutiérrez, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Roger Levy, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin K. Bergen, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving Evaluation of Machine Translation Quality Estimation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yvette Graham, Trinity College Dublin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Dynamic Feature Selection for Fast Sequential Prediction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Emma Strubell, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Luke Vilnis, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Kate Silverstein, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Andrew McCallum, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast and Robust Neural Network Joint Models for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jacob Devlin, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Rabih Zbib, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Zhongqiang Huang, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Lamar, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Richard Schwartz, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;John Makhoul, Raytheon BBN Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Grounded Language Learning from Video Described with Sentences&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Haonan Yu &amp;amp; Jeffrey Mark Siskind, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;String Re-writing Kernel&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fan Bu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Hang Li, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xiaoyan Zhu, Tsinghua University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bayesian Symbol-Refined Tree Substitution Grammars for Syntactic Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hiroyuki Shindo, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Yusuke Miyao, National Institute of Informatics&lt;br /&gt;Akinori Fujino, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Masaaki Nagata, NTT Communication Science Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Unsupervised Part-of-Speech Tagging with Bilingual Graph-Based Projections&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dipanjan Das, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Slav Petrov, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beyond NomBank: A Study of Implicit Arguments for Nominal Predicates&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew Gerber &amp;amp; Joyce Y. Chai, Michigan State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reinforcement Learning for Mapping Instructions to Actions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;S.R.K. Branavan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Harr Chen, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Luke S. Zettlemoyer, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Regina Barzilay, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;K-Best A* Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adam Pauls &amp;amp; Dan Klein, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Concise Integer Linear Programming Formulations for Dependency Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;André F.T. Martins, Instituto de Telecomunicações&lt;br /&gt;Noah A. Smith, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Eric P. Xing, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Forest Reranking: Discriminative Parsing with Non-Local Features&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Liang Huang, University of Pennsylvania&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A New String-to-Dependency Machine Translation Algorithm with a Target Dependency Language Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Libin Shen, BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Jinxi Xu, BBN Technologies&lt;br /&gt;Ralph Weischedel, BBN Technologies&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning synchronous grammars for semantic parsing with lambda calculus&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuk Wah Wong &amp;amp; Raymond J. Mooney, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Semantic taxonomy induction from heterogenous evidence&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rion Snow, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Jurafsky, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Y. Ng, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Hierarchical Phrase-Based Model for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Chiang, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Finding Predominant Word Senses in Untagged Text&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diana McCarthy, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;Rob Koeling, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;Julie Weeds, University of Sussex&lt;br /&gt;John Carroll, University of Sussex&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Accurate Unlexicalized Parsing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan Klein &amp;amp; Christopher D. Manning, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards a Model of Face-to-Face Grounding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yukiko I. Nakano, RISTEX&lt;br /&gt;Gabe Reinstein, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Tom Stocky, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Justine Cassell, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Discriminative Training and Maximum Entropy Models for Statistical Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Franz Josef Och &amp;amp; Hermann Ney, RWTH Aachen University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Immediate-Head Parsing for Language Models&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eugene Charniak, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Decoding and Optimal Decoding for Machine Translation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ulrich Germann, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Michael Jahr, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Knight, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Marcu, University of Southern California&lt;br /&gt;Kenji Yamada, University of Southern California&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-ACL/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-ACL/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Natural Language Processing</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Memory-Augmented Monte Carlo Tree Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chenjun Xiao, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Jincheng Mei, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Martin Müller, University of Alberta&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Label-Free Supervision of Neural Networks with Physics and Domain Knowledge&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Russell Stewart &amp;amp; Stefano Ermon, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bidirectional Search That Is Guaranteed to Meet in the Middle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Robert C. Holte, University of Alberta&lt;br /&gt;Ariel Felner, Ben-Gurion University&lt;br /&gt;Guni Sharon, Ben-Gurion University&lt;br /&gt;Nathan R. Sturtevant, University of Denver&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;From Non-Negative to General Operator Cost Partitioning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Florian Pommerening, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Malte Helmert, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Gabriele Röger, University of Basel&lt;br /&gt;Jendrik Seipp, University of Basel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recovering from Selection Bias in Causal and Statistical Inference&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elias Bareinboim, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Jin Tian, Iowa State University&lt;br /&gt;Judea Pearl, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;HC-Search: Learning Heuristics and Cost Functions for Structured Prediction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Janardhan Rao Doppa, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Alan Fern, Oregon State University&lt;br /&gt;Prasad Tadepalli, Oregon State University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SMILe: Shufﬂed Multiple-Instance Learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gary Doran &amp;amp; Soumya Ray, Case Western Reserve University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning SVM Classifiers with Indefinite Kernels&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Suicheng Gu &amp;amp; Yuhong Guo, Temple University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Document Summarization Based on Data Reconstruction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Zhanying He, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Chun Chen, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Jiajun Bu, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Can Wang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Lijan Zhang, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Deng Cai, Zhejiang University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaofei He, Zhejiang University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic Resource Allocation in Conservation Planning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Golovin, California Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Krause, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Beth Gardner, North Carolina State University&lt;br /&gt;Sarah J. Converse, Patuxent Wildlife Research Center&lt;br /&gt;Steve Morey, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Complexity of and Algorithms for Borda Manipulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jessica Davies, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;George Katsirelos, Université Paris-Sud&lt;br /&gt;Nina Narodytska, University of New South Wales&lt;br /&gt;Toby Walsh, NICTA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Incomplete Is Your Semantic Web Reasoner? Systematic Analysis of the Completeness of Query Answering Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giorgos Stoilos, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Bernardo Cuenca Grau, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Ian Horrocks, Oxford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Novel Transition Based Encoding Scheme for Planning as Satisfiability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ruoyun Huang, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Yixin Chen, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;br /&gt;Weixiong Zhang, Washington University in St. Louis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;How Good is Almost Perfect?&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Malte Helmert &amp;amp; Gabriele Röger, Albert-Ludwigs-Universität Freiburg&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal False-Name-Proof Voting Rules with Costly Voting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Liad Wagman &amp;amp; Vincent Conitzer, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PLOW: A Collaborative Task Learning Agent&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Allen, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Nathanael Chambers, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;George Ferguson, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;Lucian Galescu, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Hyuckchul Jung, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;br /&gt;Mary Swift, University of Rochester&lt;br /&gt;William Taysom, Institute for Human and Machine Cognition&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thresholded Rewards: Acting Optimally in Timed, Zero-Sum Games&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Colin McMillen &amp;amp; Manuela Veloso, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Model Counting: A New Strategy for Obtaining Good Bounds&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carla P. Gomes, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Ashish Sabharwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Bart Selman, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Towards an Axiom System for Default Logic&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gerhard Lakemeyer, RWTH Aachen University&lt;br /&gt;Hector J. Levesque, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Max K- Armed Bandit: A New Model of Exploration Applied to Search Heuristic Selection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent A. Cicirello, Drexel University&lt;br /&gt;Stephen F. Smith, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning and Inferring Transportation Routines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Lin Liao, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry Kautz, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Computing All Abductive Explanations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Eiter, Technische Universität Wien&lt;br /&gt;Kazuhisa Makino, Osaka University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Game of Hex: An Automatic Theorem-Proving Approach to Game Programming&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vadim V. Anshelevich, Vanshel Consulting&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;PROVERB: The Probabilistic Cruciverbalist&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Greg A. Keim, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Noam M. Shazeer, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Michael L. Littman, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Sushant Agarwal, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Catherine M. Cheves, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Fitzgerald, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Jason Grosland, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Fan Jiang, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Shannon Pollard, Duke University&lt;br /&gt;Karl Weinmeister, Duke University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning Evaluation Functions for Global Optimization and Boolean Satisfiability&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Justin A. Boyan &amp;amp; Andrew W. Moore, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Acceleration Methods for Numeric CSPs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yahia Lebbah &amp;amp; Olivier Lhomme, Ecole des Mines de Nantes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Interactive Museum Tour-Guide Robot&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wolfram Burgard, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Armin B. Cremers, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Dieter Fox, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Dirk Hähnel, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Gerhard Lakemeyer, Aachen University of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Dirk Schulz, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Walter Steiner, University of Bonn&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Thrun, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Statistical Parsing with a Context-Free Grammar and Word Statistics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eugene Charniak, Brown University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Practical Algorithm for Finding Optimal Triangulations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Krill Shoikhet &amp;amp; Dan Geiger, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast Context Switching in Real-Time Propositional Reasoning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;P. Pandurang Nayak &amp;amp; Brian C. Williams, NASA Ames Research Center&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Building Concept Representations from Reusable Components&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Clark, Boeing&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Porter, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verification of Knowledge Bases Based on Containment Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alon Y. Levy, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Marie-Christine Rousset, Université Paris-Sud&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Novel Application of Theory Refinement to Student Modeling&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul T. Baffes, SciComp&lt;br /&gt;Raymond J. Mooney, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pushing the Envelope: Planning, Propositional Logic, and Stochastic Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Henry Kautz &amp;amp; Bart Selman, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-AAAI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/12/30/best-paper-awards-AAAI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Concolic Testing 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;这篇博客的核心内容来源于本人发表于软件工程顶级会议ICSE2018并获得“ACM SIGSOFT Distinguished Paper Award”的&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/icse2018.pdf&quot;&gt;同名论文&lt;/a&gt;，在后面的内容中，若未做特殊说明，本文将使用以下抽象语法树作为例子：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;抽象语法树&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;研究问题&quot;&gt;研究问题&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;给定程序的最优动态符号执行测试策略是什么？&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;能不能有效的得到最优策略?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;现有算法是否很好的逼近最优策略?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;是否能设计一个可用算法来逼近最优策略?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;如果4的回答是肯定的，那么该算法与现有算法的相比如何?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;程序抽象&quot;&gt;程序抽象&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;程序是带标签的转移系统P=(C,init,V,φ,T)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C是控制节点的有限集合&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;init ∈ C是唯一入口&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;V是变量的有限集合&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;φ是捕获V初始取值集合的断言&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;T : C × GC → C是转移函数&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;P的一条程序路径就是一个转移序列π = ⟨(c1, gc1, c2), (c2, gc2, c3), · · · , (ck, gck, ck+1)⟩&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;马尔可夫链抽象&quot;&gt;马尔可夫链抽象&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本文将使用马尔可夫决策过程来求解最优策略，首先需要形式化的说明P能够转换为对应的马尔可夫链，由于这是显而易见的，所以这里对原作中相关定义不做翻译，截图如下：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/13.png&quot; alt=&quot;定义3.2&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/14.png&quot; alt=&quot;定义3.3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;最优策略&quot;&gt;最优策略&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;问题可以被定义为：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;测试用例生成方法的搜索空间是{𝑅𝑇}∪{𝑆𝐸(P)|P ∈ 𝑝𝑎𝑡ℎ(𝑃)}&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;一个策略是一个测试用例生成方法的序列&amp;lt;t1, t2, t3, …&amp;gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;使用测试用例生成方法t的代价是cost(t)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;找到达到100%覆盖率并具有最小总代价的策略&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;这里通过举例来说明最优策略的选择，首先作如下假设：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;随机测试的cost是1&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;求解n边路径的代价为10n&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;那么有就会有以下策略：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;完全随机测试：期望cost: 5*(2^32)/4 = 5368709120&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;完全符号执行：对&amp;lt;1,2,3,4&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;1,3,5,6,7,8&amp;gt;执行符号执行，相关Cost：30+50=80&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;最优策略：对&amp;lt;1,2&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;1,3,5,6&amp;gt;执行符号执行，其余执行随机测试，相关Cost：10+30+5=45&lt;br /&gt;
注意：随机测试的期望数目决定于具有最小到达概率的节点!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;事实上，寻找最优策略的问题可以简化为基于带代价的马尔可夫决策过程的模型检测问题，比如说下面这个极其简单的程序的相关抽象：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/4.png&quot; alt=&quot;程序&quot; /&gt;
其抽象语法树为：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/5.png&quot; alt=&quot;抽象语法树&quot; /&gt;
相对应的马尔可夫决策过程为：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/6.png&quot; alt=&quot;马尔可夫决策过程&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;显然，根据带代价的马尔可夫决策过程可以很轻松地回答研究问题1和2：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;最优策略是具有最小期望成本的策略&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;其求解复杂性随着P中的控制节点数量指数级增长&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;模拟实验&quot;&gt;模拟实验&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该部分实验主要是为了验证现有算法（相关算法的理论可以参考&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang.cn/2018/09/29/concolic-testing-1/&quot;&gt;前一篇&lt;/a&gt;)的性能，实验基于随机生成的马尔可夫链，而非现有程序，实验设置如下：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;随机生成抽象表示程序的DTMC模型（分支密度50%；低概率分支密度0.2（10，15，20），0.8（5），低概率程度1.0E-4）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;随机生成表示每条分支符号执行代价的cost（不超过1000）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;每种情况有50个模型，每个方法运行1000次&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;相应的实验结果如下：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt; &lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;5 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;10 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;15 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;20 states&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RT&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;138.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11.3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;44.2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;114.7&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RCN&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1.7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;14.4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;15.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;12.7&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RSS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;12.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50.7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;64.0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;68.1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;RPS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;12.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50.6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;63.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;68.5&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DFS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;7.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;27.4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;18.6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DART&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;12.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.0&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;GS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CGS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;12.6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;13.8&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SGS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11.2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;32.4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;29.4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;25.5&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;说明：这里RCN对应前文中的Coverage-Optimized Search&lt;br /&gt; 
显然，现在可以回答研究问题3：&lt;em&gt;现有算法还有很大的改进空间&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;贪婪算法&quot;&gt;贪婪算法&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;算法的核心想法为根据单位时间(cost)所能覆盖的期望节点数(reward)选择局部最优策略和路径&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;离散时间马尔可夫链估计&quot;&gt;离散时间马尔可夫链估计&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;使用拉普拉斯估计方法来估计离散时间马尔可夫链&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;如果在P中从s到t是不可能的，置Pr(s, t)=0&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;否则，置Pr(s,t) = (#(s, t)+1) / (#s+n)&lt;br /&gt;
举例说明：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/7.png&quot; alt=&quot;拉普拉斯估计方法&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cost估计&quot;&gt;cost估计&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;使用函数拟合来估计cost：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设cost是基础操作的加权和&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;根据收集的cost来估计权值&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;给定一个约束，利用其所有基础操作的加权和来估计cost&lt;br /&gt;
举例说明： 约束c是a * b &amp;gt; 0，所以SC(c) = WC(*) + WC(&amp;gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;算法&quot;&gt;算法&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;首先，根据实证研究做如下假设：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;求解一个线性（不）等式及其结合的cost是4&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;求解一个非线性（不）等式的cost是10&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;求解一个非线性（不）等式的布尔组合的cost是50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;具体相关步骤如下：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;根据下图公式计算每个节点的reward
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/8.png&quot; alt=&quot;reward计算&quot; /&gt;
比如对于下面这种情况：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/9.png&quot; alt=&quot;reward例子&quot; /&gt;
可以获得以下方程组：
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅1 = 1/3*𝑅2+2/3*𝑅3&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅2 = 1+𝑅3&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅3 = 1/3*𝑅4+2/3*𝑅5&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅4 = 1&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅5 = 1/3*𝑅6+2/3*𝑅8&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅6 = 1+1/2*𝑅7+1/2*𝑅8&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅7 = 1+𝑅8&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅8 = 0&lt;br /&gt;
相应的部分解为：&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅1 = 1&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅2 = 5/3&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅4 = 1&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;𝑅6 = 1.5&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;随机测试的期望收益：∑𝑠∈𝑆 {𝜇(𝑠)×𝑅𝑠}
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;随机测试：cost 1, reward 1&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;选择只有结束节点未被覆盖的路径&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SE(π)的期望收益：𝑅𝑠，如果last(π)是s
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;路径&amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;：cost 4, reward 5/3&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;：cost 50, reward 1&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6&amp;gt;：cost 50, reward 3/2&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;选择其中最大的reward/cost&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;更新离散时间马尔可夫链&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;模拟实验结果&quot;&gt;模拟实验结果&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该部分实验仍使用上文中提到的模拟马尔可夫链，结果如下：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt; &lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;5 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;10 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;15 states&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;20 states&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;G&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4.8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4.8&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;显然，现在可以回答研究问题4：&lt;em&gt;这里提出的贪婪算法更接近最优策略&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;klee实验&quot;&gt;KLEE实验&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该部分实验针对的是实际程序，而非之前的模拟马尔可夫链，实验设置如下：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;测试平台：KLEE&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;测试对象：GNU科学库中的程序集&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;测试目标：测量不同策略实现的覆盖率随时间的变化
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/10.png&quot; alt=&quot;程序集&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;实验结果如下:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;时间&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;G&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;RCN&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;RSS&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;RPS&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;DFS&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;RT&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5 min (%)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;72.6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;28.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;22.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;29.7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;17.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;65.5&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;15 min (%)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;73.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;30.1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;24.3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;34.3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21.0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;72.7&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;30 min (%)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;76.9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;32.6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;25.0&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;36.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;22.3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;74.0&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;更直观的折线图如下：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/11.png&quot; alt=&quot;折线图&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以及对于每个程序，实际执行的SE以及RT的次数统计如下：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/12.png&quot; alt=&quot;测试方法统计&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;贡献&quot;&gt;贡献&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;定义了基于程序行为概率抽象的最优动态符号执行测试策略&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;将确定最优策略的问题简化为基于带代价的马尔可夫决策过程的模型检测问题&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;使用模拟实验验证了现有算法并揭示它们还有很大的改进空间&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;提出了一种接近最优策略的贪婪算法&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;未来工作&quot;&gt;未来工作&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;研究其它用于估算概率以及求解代价的方法&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;把该框架扩展到其它的测试用例生成方法中（注意到有人工智能系统分析与测试方向的论文引用了本文）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/08/concolic-testing-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/10/08/concolic-testing-2/</guid>
        
        <category>Software Engineering</category>
        
        <category>Concolic Testing</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Concolic Testing 1</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;随机测试random-testing&quot;&gt;随机测试（Random Testing）&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;使用随机生成的测试输入执行程序，然后观察是否会出现错误状态&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对于高可能性的错误，随机测试的代价很低，反之很高&lt;br /&gt;
比如说下面的第3行判断语句，对于随机测试来说，几乎不可能覆盖到其True分支
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;public static void example(int x, int y) {
  int[] array = new int[10];
  if (y == 42342531) {
      array[x] = y; 
  }
}
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;符号执行symbolic-execution&quot;&gt;符号执行（Symbolic Execution）&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;利用符号变量来代替输入执行程序，然后使用约束求解器求解路径约束从而获得测试输入&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;符号执行的代价很高，但是可以“保证”到达给定节点&lt;br /&gt;
同样是上面那个程序，我们可以通过求解下面的路径约束：
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;y == 42342531 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (x&amp;lt;0 || x &amp;gt;= 10)
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;生成一个特定的测试输入来覆盖我们指定的路径，比如：&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;x == 10 and y == 42342531
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;但是目前符号执行面临两个问题，第一：由于需要利用符号变量来构建路径约束，所以显然其比随机测试需要更多的时间；第二：目前最常见的约束求解器（如Z3等）的求解能力仍十分有限，对于稍复杂的路径约束就束手无策。&lt;br /&gt;
常见的符号执行策略有：&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Random State Search&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Random Path Selection&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Depth First Search&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Subpath-Guided Search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;所以自动化测试领域提出了concolic testing，我翻译为动态符号执行测试，也可以翻译为具体符号执行，因为concolic是concrete和symbolic的合成词。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;动态符号执行测试concolic-testing&quot;&gt;动态符号执行测试（Concolic Testing）&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;集成了具体执行和符号执行两种策略&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;决定选择随机测试还是符号执行&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;如果选择符号执行，决定选择的程序执行路径&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;常见的动态符号执行测试工具：Microsoft SAGE和JDart等&lt;br /&gt;
比如说如下程序：
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9
10
11
12
13
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;int h(int x, int y) {
  if (x != y) { 
      if (2*x == x + 10) { 
          abort(); /*error*/
      }
      else {
          return 2x+y; 
      }
  }
  else{
      return 2x;
  } 
}
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;其抽象语法树为：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;抽象语法树&quot; /&gt;
如上图所示，黑色箭头表示随机测试，蓝色箭头表示符号执行.&lt;br /&gt;
常见的动态符号执行策略有：&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Directed Automated Random Testing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coverage-Optimized Search&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Generational Search&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Context-Guided Search&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;部分常见测试策略&quot;&gt;部分常见测试策略&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;事实上，绝大多数动态符号执行测试策略仅执行一遍随机测试，更多的是关注随后符号执行路径的调度，这导致相关算法性能距离&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang.cn/2018/10/08/concolic-testing-2/&quot;&gt;最优调度策略&lt;/a&gt;有极大的差距。我将使用以下函数作为例子简单阐述几种常见动态符号执行以及符号执行策略。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9
10
11
12
13
14
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;void myfunc(int x, int y){
1.    if(x==y){
2.        x++;
       }
3.    if ((x*x)%10==9){
4.        return;
       }
5.    if (x*y+3*y-5*x==15){  
6.        if (x%2==1 ||y%2==1){
7.           x = x-y;
           } 
       }
8.    return;
}
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其抽象语法树为：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;抽象语法树&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;subpath-guided-search&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/oopsla13-pgse.pdf&quot;&gt;Subpath-Guided Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该方法是符号执行测试调度策略，首先给出两个关键的定义：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Length-n子路径：给定一条路径&amp;lt;s1, s2,…, sk&amp;gt;，那么其length-n 子路径就是&amp;lt;sk-n+1, sk-n+2, …, sk&amp;gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;统计分析结构：结构e = (π, f) 用于统计分析，其中π是length-n 子路径，f是π被探索过的频率&lt;br /&gt;
基于以上定义，该调度策略可以总结为以下步骤：
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;初始化 
  结构e的优先队列
重复 
  1.随机选择一个具有最低子路径计数的节点继续
  2.如果下一个节点是终节点，求解路径条件获得测试用例
  3.用下一个节点来更新优先队列
直到 所有节点被覆盖 
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;用一个案例来进一步说明该算法（优先队列中带*结构表示有包含相应子路径的未终结状态）：&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;步骤&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;候选路径&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;优先队列&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;生成用例&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1:1t&lt;br /&gt;2:1f&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(*1t, 0), (*1f, 0)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1:1t&lt;br /&gt;2:1f3t&lt;br /&gt;3:1f3f&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(*1t, 0), (*3t, 0), (*3f, 0), (1f, 1)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1f3t4&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1:1t&lt;br /&gt;2:1f3f&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;(*1t, 0), (*3f, 0), (3t, 1), (1f, 1)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;…&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;…&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;…&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;…&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;directed-automated-random-testing&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/pldi2005.pdf&quot;&gt;Directed Automated Random Testing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该方法是动态符号执行测试调度策略，也是目前广泛使用的JAVA自动化测试工具JDart的算法基础。该调度策略可以总结为以下步骤：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;初始化 
	一个具体执行的测试用例
重复 
	1.执行该测试用例
	2.深度优先搜索获取未覆盖的分支
	3.求解访问未覆盖分支的路径条件获得测试用例
直到 所有节点被覆盖 
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;用一个案例来进一步说明该算法：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设第一个测试用例是x = 0, y = 100,其访问了节点1, 3, 5, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6&amp;gt;通过求解下面的条件 x!=y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (x&lt;em&gt;x)%10!=9 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; x&lt;/em&gt;y+3y-5x==15执行符号执行&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设测试用例是x=4, y = 5 ,其访问了节点1, 3, 5, 6, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6, 7&amp;gt;执行符号执行&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;coverage-optimized-search&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/klee-osdi-08.pdf&quot;&gt;Coverage-Optimized Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该方法是动态符号执行测试调度策略,也是目前广泛使用的C/C++自动化测试工具KLEE的算法基础。该调度策略可以总结为以下步骤：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;初始化
	一个具体执行的测试用例
重复
	1.执行该测试用例
	2.计算未覆盖节点与已覆盖节点间的最小距离
	3.从最小距离中随机选择一条路径
	4.求解该路径条件获得一个测试用例
直到 所有节点被覆盖
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;用一个案例来进一步说明该算法：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设第一个测试用例是x = 0, y = 100,其访问了节点1, 3, 5, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对于 &amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6&amp;gt;最小距离是1, &amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6, 7&amp;gt;是2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;从&amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6&amp;gt;随机选择一条路径,假设是&amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;执行符号执行&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;generational-search&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/FuzzTesting.pdf&quot;&gt;Generational Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该方法是动态符号执行测试调度策略。该调度策略可以总结为以下步骤：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;初始化
	带有一个测试用例的测试套件
重复
	1.执行该测试用例
	2.给定该测试用例的路径，其上所有分支条件系统地用未被访问的另一分支替换
	3.求解每个约束获得相应的测试用例
直到 所有节点被覆盖
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;用一个案例来进一步说明该算法：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设第一个测试用例是x = 0, y = 100,其访问了节点1, 3, 5, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;1,3,4&amp;gt;和&amp;lt;1,3,5,6&amp;gt;的路径条件求解并将相应的测试用例添加到测试套件中&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;选择路径&amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;的测试用例&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;选择路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;的测试用例&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;选择路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 5, 6&amp;gt;的测试用例&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;….. 
下图来源于原论文，较为清晰的阐述了该算法调度顺序：
&lt;img src=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/img/posts/concolic_testing/3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Generational Search&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;context-guided-search&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://pxzhang94.github.io/paper/concolic_testing/seo-fse2014.pdf&quot;&gt;Context-Guided Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;该方法是动态符号执行测试调度策略。首先给出一个关键的定义&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;K-Context：定义分支b的k-context为一条执行路径上之前k个分支的序列
比如路径&amp;lt;1,2,3,5,8&amp;gt;包含分支(1,3,5)，那么：&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5的1-context为(5)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5的2-context为(3,5)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5的3-context为(1,3,5)
该调度策略可以总结为以下步骤：
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;rouge-table&quot;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-gutter gl&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;lineno&quot;&gt;1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&quot;rouge-code&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;初始化
  一个具体执行的测试用例和k = 1
重复
  1.重复广度优先搜索
      a.检查在执行树上给定深度的每个节点的k-context是否是新的
      b.求解访问未覆盖分支的路径条件获得测试用例
      c.用测试用例更新执行树
  2.递增k
直到 所有节点被覆盖
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;用一个案例来进一步说明该算法：&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设第一个测试用例是x = 0, y = 100,其访问了节点1, 3, 5, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 2&amp;gt;执行符号测试&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;假设测试用例是x=0, y=0,其访问了节点1, 2, 3, 5, 8&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;对路径&amp;lt;1, 3, 4&amp;gt;执行符号测试&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/09/29/concolic-testing-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/09/29/concolic-testing-1/</guid>
        
        <category>Software Engineering</category>
        
        <category>Concolic Testing</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
