<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PXZHANG</title>
    <description>这里是 @PXZHANG张培歆 的个人网站</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:01:17 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:01:17 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1999-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Program synthesis using conflict-driven learning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yu Feng, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Ruben Martins, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Osbert Bastani, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Isil Dillig, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The semantics of transactions and weak memory in x86, Power, ARM, and C++&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nathan Chong, ARM&lt;br /&gt;Tyler Sorensen, Imperial College London&lt;br /&gt;John Wickerson, Imperial College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A data-driven CHC solver&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;He Zhu, Galois&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Magill, Galois&lt;br /&gt;Suresh Jagannathan, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Low Overhead Dynamic Binary Translation on ARM&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amanieu D’Antras, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Cosmin Gorgovan, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Jim Garside, University of Manchester&lt;br /&gt;Mikel Luján, University of Manchester&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Repairing sequential consistency in C/C++11&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ori Lahav, MPI-SWS&lt;br /&gt;Viktor Vafeiadis, MPI-SWS&lt;br /&gt;Jeehoon Kang, Seoul National University&lt;br /&gt;Chung-Kil Hur, Seoul National University&lt;br /&gt;Derek Dreyer, MPI-SWS&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bringing the web up to speed with WebAssembly&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andreas Haas, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andreas Rossberg, Google&lt;br /&gt;Derek L. Schuff, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ben L. Titzer, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michael Holman, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Dan Gohman, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;Luke Wagner, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;Alon Zakai, Mozilla&lt;br /&gt;JF Bastien, Apple&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compiling without continuations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Luke Maurer, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Paul Downen, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Zena M. Ariola, University of Oregon&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peyton Jones, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the limits of program-specific garbage collection performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicholas Jacek, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Meng-Chieh Chiu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Marlin, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Eliot Moss, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Into the Depths of C: Elaborating the De Facto Standards&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kayvan Memarian, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Justus Matthiesen, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;James Lingard, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Kyndylan Nienhuis, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;David Chisnall, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Robert N. M. Watson, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Peter Sewell, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Transactional Data Structure Libraries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alexander Spiegelman, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Guy Golan-Gueta, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Idit Keidar, Technion&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Types from data: Making structured data first-class citizens in F#&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tomas Petricek, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Gustavo Guerra, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Don Syme, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Provably Correct Peephole Optimizations with Alive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nuno P. Lopes, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;David Menendez, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;Santosh Nagarakatte, Rutgers University&lt;br /&gt;John Regehr, University of Utah&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diagnosing Type Errors with Class&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Danfeng Zhang, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Dimitrios Vytiniotis, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peyton-Jones, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Improving Accuracy for Floating Point Expressions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pavel Panchekha, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Alex Sanchez-Stern, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James R. Wilcox, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Zachary Tatlock, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Improving JavaScript Performance by Deconstructing the Type System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wonsun Ahn, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Jiho Choi, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Shull, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;María Garzarín, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Josep Torrellas, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compiler validation via equivalence modulo inputs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vu Le, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Mehrdad Afshari, University of California Davis&lt;br /&gt;Zhendong Su, University of California Davis&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Abstraction Refinement for Program Analyses in Datalog&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xin Zhang, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ravi Mangal, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Radu Grigore, Oxford University&lt;br /&gt;Mayur Naik, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Hongseok Yang, Oxford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Static Analysis for Probabilistic Programs: Inferring Whole Program Properties from Finitely Many Path&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sriram Sankaranarayanan, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Aleksandar Chakarov, University of Colorado&lt;br /&gt;Sumit Gulwani, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A General Constraint-centric Scheduling Framework for Spatial Architectures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tony Nowatzki, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Sartin-Tarm, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo De Carli, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Karthikeyan Sankaralingam, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Cristian Estan, Broadcom&lt;br /&gt;Behnam Robatmili, Qualcomm Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reconciling Exhaustive Pattern Matching with Objects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chinawat Isradisaikul &amp;amp; Andrew C. Myers, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CLAP: Recording Local Executions to Reproduce Concurrency Failures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeff Huang, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Charles Zhang, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Julian Dolby, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Concurrent Data Representation Synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Hawkins, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen Fisher, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Mooly Sagiv, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Representation Synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Peter Hawkins, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Alex Aiken, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Kathleen Fisher, Tufts University&lt;br /&gt;Martin Rinard, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Mooly Sagiv, Tel-Aviv University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Safe to the Last Instruction: Automated Verification of a Type-Safe Operating System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jean Yang, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Chris Hawblitzel, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Binary Analysis for Measurement and Attribution of Program Performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nathan Tallent, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;John Mellor-Crummey, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Fagan, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fault-tolerant Typed Assembly Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Frances Perry, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Lester Mackey, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;George A. Reis, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Jay Ligatti, University of South Florida&lt;br /&gt;David I. August, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;David Walker, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Ant and the Grasshopper: Fast and Accurate Pointer Analysis for Millions of Lines of Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ben Hardekopf &amp;amp; Calvin Lin, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Pool Allocation: Improving Performance by Controlling Data Structure Layout in the Heap&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chris Lattner &amp;amp; Vikram Adve, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Programming by Sketching for Bit-Streaming Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Armando Solar-Lezama, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Rodric Rabbah, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rastislav Bodik, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Kemal Ebcioğlu, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cloning-Based Context-Sensitive Pointer Alias Analysis Using Binary Decision Diagrams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Whaley &amp;amp; Monica S. Lam, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatically Proving the Correctness of Compiler Optimizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sorin Lerner, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Todd Millstein, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Craig Chambers, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamo: a transparent dynamic optimization system&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vasanth Bala, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Duesterwald, Hewlett-Packard Labs&lt;br /&gt;Sanjeev Banerjia, InCert&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Whole program paths&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James R. Larus, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-PLDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-PLDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Programming Languages</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;REPT: Reverse Debugging of Failures in Deployed Software&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weidong Cui, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Xinyang Ge, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Baris Kasikci, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ben Niu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Upamanyu Sharma, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Ruoyu Wang, Arizona State University&lt;br /&gt;Insu Yun, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Orca: Differential Bug Localization in Large-Scale Services&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ranjita Bhagwan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rahul Kumar, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Chandra Sekhar Maddila, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Adithya Abraham Philip, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;LegoOS: A Disseminated, Distributed OS for Hardware Resource Disaggregation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yizhou Shan, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yutong Huang, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yilun Chen, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Yiying Zhang, Purdue University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryoan: A Distributed Sandbox for Untrusted Computation on Secret Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tyler Hunt, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Zhiting Zhu, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Yuanzhong Xu, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Simon Peter, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Emmett Witchel, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Push-Button Verification of File Systems via Crash Refinement&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Helgi Sigurbjarnarson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;James Bornholt, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Emina Torlak, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Xi Wang, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Early Detection of Configuration Errors to Reduce Failure Damage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tianyin Xu, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Xinxin Jin, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Peng Huang, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Yuanyuan Zhou, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shan Lu, University of Chicago&lt;br /&gt;Long Jin, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Shankar Pasupathy, NetApp&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shielding Applications from an Untrusted Cloud with Haven&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Baumann, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Marcus Peinado, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Galen Hunt, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IX: A Protected Dataplane Operating System for High Throughput and Low Latency&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Adam Belay, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;George Prekas, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Ana Klimovic, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Samuel Grossman, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Christos Kozyrakis, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Edouard Bugnion, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Arrakis: The Operating System is the Control Plane&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Simon Peter, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jialin Li, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Irene Zhang, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Dan Ports, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Doug Woos, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Timothy Roscoe, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spanner: Google’s Globally-Distributed Database&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James C. Corbett, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michael Epstein, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fikes, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Frost, Google&lt;br /&gt;JJ Furman, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Ghemawat, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrey Gubarev, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Heiser, Google&lt;br /&gt;Peter Hochschild, Google&lt;br /&gt;Wilson Hsieh, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sebastian Kanthak, Google&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Kogan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Hongyi Li, Google&lt;br /&gt;Alexander Lloyd, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sergey Melnik, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Mwaura, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Nagle, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sean Quinlan, Google&lt;br /&gt;Rajesh Rao, Google&lt;br /&gt;Lindsay Rolig, Google&lt;br /&gt;Yasushi Saito, Google&lt;br /&gt;Michal Szymaniak, Google&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Taylor, Google&lt;br /&gt;Ruth Wang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Dale Woodford, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient System-Enforced Deterministic Parallelism&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Amittai Aviram, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Shu-Chun Weng, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Sen Hu, Yale University&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Ford, Yale University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Turtles Project: Design and Implementation of Nested Virtualization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Muli Ben-Yehuda, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael D. Day, IBM&lt;br /&gt;Zvi Dubitzky, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Factor, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Nadav Har’El, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Abel Gordon, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Anthony Liguori, IBM&lt;br /&gt;Orit Wasserman, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Ben-Ami Yassour, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;KLEE: Unassisted and Automatic Generation of High-Coverage Tests for Complex Systems Programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cristian Cadar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Dunbar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Difference Engine: Harnessing Memory Redundancy in Virtual Machines&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Diwaker Gupta, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Sangmin Lee, University of Texas at Austin&lt;br /&gt;Michael Vrable, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Stefan Savage, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Alex C. Snoeren, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;George Varghese, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey M. Voelker, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DryadLINQ: A System for General-Purpose Distributed Data-Parallel Computing Using a High-Level Language&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuan Yu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Michael Isard, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Dennis Fetterly, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mihai Budiu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Úlfar Erlingsson, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Pradeep Kumar Gunda, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Currey, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bigtable: A Distributed Storage System for Structured Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fay Chang, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey Dean, Google&lt;br /&gt;Sanjay Ghemawat, Google&lt;br /&gt;Wilson C. Hsieh, Google&lt;br /&gt;Deborah A. Wallach, Google&lt;br /&gt;Mike Burrows, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tushar Chandra, Google&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Fikes, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robert E. Gruber, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rethink the Sync&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Edmund B. Nightingale, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Kaushik Veeraraghavan, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Peter M. Chen, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Jason Flinn, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Using Model Checking to Find Serious File System Errors	Junfeng Yang, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paul Twohey, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Madanlal Musuvathi, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Recovering Device Drivers&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael M. Swift, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Muthukaruppan Annamalai, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Brian N. Bershad, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Henry M. Levy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Memory Resource Management in VMware ESX Server&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Carl A. Waldspurger, VMware&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Checking System Rules Using System-Specific, Programmer-Written Compiler Extensions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dawson Engler, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Chelf, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Andy Chou, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Seth Hallem, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IO-Lite: A Unified I/O Buffering and Caching System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vivek S. Pai, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Druschel, Rice University&lt;br /&gt;Willy Zwaenepoel, Rice University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Automatic Compiler-Inserted I/O Prefetching for Out-of-Core Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Todd C. Mowry, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Angela K. Demke, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Orran Krieger, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Safe Kernel Extensions Without Run-Time Checking&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;George C. Necula &amp;amp; Peter Lee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-OSDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-OSDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Operating Systems</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2004-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;NetChain: Scale-Free Sub-RTT Coordination&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xin Jin, Johns Hopkins University&lt;br /&gt;Xiaozhou Li, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Haoyu Zhang, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Nate Foster, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Jeongkeun Lee, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Robert Soulé, Università della Svizzera italiana&lt;br /&gt;Changhoon Kim, Barefoot Networks&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;mOS: A Reusable Networking Stack for Flow Monitoring Middleboxes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Muhammad Asim Jamshed, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;YoungGyoun Moon, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Donghwi Kim, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;Dongsu Han, KAIST&lt;br /&gt;KyoungSoo Park, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Passive Wi-Fi: Bringing Low Power to Wi-Fi Transmissions&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryce Kellogg, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua R. Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Queues Don’t Matter When You Can JUMP Them!&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matthew P. Grosvenor, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Malte Schwarzkopf, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Ionel Gog, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Robert N. M. Watson, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Andrew W. Moore, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Steven Hand, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Jon Crowcroft, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Designing Distributed Systems Using Approximate Synchrony in Data Center Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dan R. K. Ports, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Jialin Li, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Naveen Kr. Sharma, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Design and Implementation of Open vSwitch&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ben Pfaff, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Justin Pettit, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Teemu Koponen, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Ethan J. Jackson, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Andy Zhou, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jarno Rajahalme, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jesse Gross, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Alex Wang, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Stringer, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Pravin Shelar, VMware&lt;br /&gt;Keith Amidon, Awake Networks&lt;br /&gt;Martín Casado, VMware&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Software Dataplane Verification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mihai Dobrescu &amp;amp; Katerina Argyraki, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Embassies: Radically Refactoring the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jon Howell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Parno, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;John R. Douceur, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Fault-Tolerant Engineered Network&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Halperin, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Resilient Distributed Datasets: A Fault-Tolerant Abstraction for In-Memory Cluster Computing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Matei Zaharia, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Mosharaf Chowdhury, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Tathagata Das, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ankur Dave, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Justin Ma, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Murphy McCauley, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Michael J. Franklin, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Design, Implementation and Evaluation of Congestion Control for Multipath TCP&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Damon Wischik, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Costin Raiciu, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Adam Greenhalgh, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Mark Handley, University College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ServerSwitch: A Programmable and High Performance Platform for Data Center Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Guohan Lu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Chuanxiong Guo, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yulong Li, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Zhiqiang Zhou, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Tong Yuan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haitao Wu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yongqiang Xiong, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rui Gao, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Yongguang Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Reverse traceroute&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ethan Katz-Bassett, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Harsha V. Madhyastha, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Vijay Kumar Adhikari, University of Minnesota&lt;br /&gt;Colin Scott, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Justine Sherry, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Peter van Wesep, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sora: High Performance Software Radio Using General Purpose Multi-core Processors&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kun Tan, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jiansong Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Ji Fang, Beijing Jiaotong University&lt;br /&gt;He Liu, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yusheng Ye, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Shen Wang, Tsinghua University&lt;br /&gt;Yongguang Zhang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Haitao Wu, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Wei Wang, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey M. Voelker, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;TrInc: Small Trusted Hardware for Large Distributed Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dave Levin, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;John R. Douceur, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jacob R. Lorch, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Moscibroda, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Remus: High Availability via Asynchronous Virtual Machine Replication&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Brendan Cully, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey Lefebvre, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Dutch Meyer, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Mike Feeley, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Norm Hutchinson, University of British Columbia&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Warfield, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Consensus Routing: The Internet as a Distributed System&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John P. John, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Ethan Katz-Bassett, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arvind Krishnamurthy, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Anderson, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Arun Venkataramani, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Life, Death, and the Critical Transition: Finding Liveness Bugs in Systems Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charles Killian, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;James W. Anderson, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Ranjit Jhala, University of California San Diego&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, University of California San Diego&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Experience with an Object Reputation System for Peer-to-Peer Filesharing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kevin Walsh &amp;amp; Emin Gün Sirer, Cornell University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Replay Debugging for Distributed Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dennis Geels, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Gautam Altekar, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Detecting BGP Configuration Faults with Static Analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nick Feamster &amp;amp; Hari Balakrishnan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Trickle: A Self-Regulating Algorithm for Code Propagation and Maintenance in Wireless Sensor Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Philip Levis, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Neil Patel, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;David Culler, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Scott Shenker, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-NSDI/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/09/best-paper-awards-NSDI/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Networking</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2008-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Inferring Persistent Interdomain Congestion&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Saksham Agarwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Shijin Rajakrishnan, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Akshay Narayan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Rachit Agarwal, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;David Shmoys, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Amin Vahdat, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Re-architecting datacenter networks and stacks for low latency and high performance&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Handley, University College London&lt;br /&gt;Costin Raiciu, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Alexandru Agache, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Andrei Voinescu, University Politehnica of Bucharest&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Moore, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Gianni Antichi, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Marcin Wójcik, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Language-directed hardware design for network performance monitoring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Srinivas Narayana, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Anirudh Sivaraman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Vikram Nathan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Prateesh Goyal, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Venkat Arun, IIT Guwahati&lt;br /&gt;Mohammad Alizadeh, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Vimalkumar Jeyakumar, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Changhoon Kim, Barefoot Networks&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eliminating Channel Feedback in Next-Generation Cellular Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Deepak Vasisht, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Swarun Kumar, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hariharan Rahul, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Inter-Technology Backscatter: Towards Internet Connectivity for Implanted Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vikram Iyer, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Bryce Kellogg, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Don’t Mind the Gap: Bridging Network-wide Objectives and Device-level Configurations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryan Beckett, Princeton University&lt;br /&gt;Ratul Mahajan, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Todd Millstein, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Jitendra Padhye, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;David Walker, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Central Control Over Distributed Routing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefano Vissicchio, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;br /&gt;Olivier Tilmans, Université catholique de Louvain&lt;br /&gt;Laurent Vanbever, ETH Zurich&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer Rexford, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Balancing Accountability and Privacy in the Network&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Naylor, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Matthew K. Mukerjee, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Peter Steenkiste, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;CONGA: Distributed Congestion-Aware Load Balancing for Datacenters&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohammad Alizadeh, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Tom Edsall, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Sarang Dharmapurikar, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Ramanan Vaidyanathan, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Chu, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Andy Fingerhut, Google&lt;br /&gt;Terry Lam, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Francis Matus, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Rong Pan, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Navindra Yadav, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;George Varghese, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ambient Backscatter: Wireless Communication Out of Thin Air&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Liu, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Parks, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Vamsi Talla, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;David Wetherall, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Joshua R. Smith, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Multi-Resource Fair Queueing for Packet Processing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ali Ghodsi, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Vyas Sekar, Intel Research&lt;br /&gt;Matei Zaharia, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Ion Stoica, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;They Can Hear Your Heartbeats: Non-Invasive Security for Implanted Medical Devices&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Haitham Hassanieh, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Ransford, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Fu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient Error Estimating Coding: Feasibility and Applications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Binbin Chen, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Ziling Chou, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Yuda Zhao, National University of Singapore&lt;br /&gt;Haifeng Yu, National University of Singapore&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;White Space Networking with Wi-Fi like Connectivity&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Paramvir Bahl, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Ranveer Chandra, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Moscibroda, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rohan Murty, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Matt Welsh, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;ZigZag Decoding: Combating Hidden Terminals in Wireless Networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shyamnath Gollakota &amp;amp; Dina Katabi, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-SIGCOMM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-SIGCOMM/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Networking</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2008-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DEEPSEC: Deciding Equivalence Properties in Security Protocols – Theory and Practice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vincent Cheval, Inria&lt;br /&gt;Steve Kremer, Inria&lt;br /&gt;Itsaka Rakotonirina, Inria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On Enforcing the Digital Immunity of a Large Humanitarian Organization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stevens Le Blond, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Alejandro Cuevas, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Juan Ramón Troncoso-Pastoriza, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Philipp Jovanovic, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Ford, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Pierre Hubaux, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verified Models and Reference Implementations for the TLS 1.3 Standard Candidate&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Karthikeyan Bhargavan, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Blanchet, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Nadim Kobeissi, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A2: Analog Malicious Hardware&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kaiyuan Yang, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Hicks, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Qing Dong, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Todd Austin, University of Michigan&lt;br /&gt;Dennis Sylvester, University of Michigan&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Riposte: An Anonymous Messaging System Handling Millions of Users&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Henry Corrigan-Gibbs, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Dan Boneh, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;David Mazières, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Messy State of the Union: Taming the Composite State Machines of TLS&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benjamin Beurdouche, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Karthikeyan Bhargavan, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Antoine Delignat-Lavaud, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Cédric Fournet, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Markulf Kohlweiss, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Alfredo Pironti, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Pierre-Yves Strub, IMDEA&lt;br /&gt;Jean Karim Zinzindohoue, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Secure Multiparty Computations on BitCoin&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcin Andrychowicz, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Stefan Dziembowski, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Malinowski, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Łukasz Mazurek, University of Warsaw&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bootstrapping Privacy Compliance in Big Data Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shayak Sen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Saikat Guha, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Anupam Datta, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Sriram K. Rajamani, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Janice Tsai, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jeannette M. Wing, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pinocchio: Nearly Practical Verifiable Computation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bryan Parno, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Craig Gentry, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Jon Howell, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mariana Raykova, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Don’t Trust Satellite Phones: A Security Analysis of Two Satphone Standards&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Benedikt Driessen, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Ralf Hund, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Willems, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Christof Paar, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;br /&gt;Thorsten Holz, Ruhr-Universität Bochum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Phonotactic Reconstruction of Encrypted VoIP Conversations: Hookt on fon-iks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew M. White, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Austin Matthews, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Snow, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Fabian Monrose, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SCiFI - A System for Secure Face Identification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Margarita Osadchy, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Benny Pinkas, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Ayman Jarrous, University of Haifa&lt;br /&gt;Boaz Moskovich, University of Haifa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Native Client: A Sandbox for Portable, Untrusted x86 Native Code&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bennet Yee, Google&lt;br /&gt;David Sehr, Google&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Dardyk, Google&lt;br /&gt;Bradley Chen, Google&lt;br /&gt;Robert Muth, Google&lt;br /&gt;Tavis Ormandy, Google&lt;br /&gt;Shiki Okasaka, Google&lt;br /&gt;Neha Narula, Google&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Fullagar, Google&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pacemakers and Implantable Cardiac Defibrillators: Software Radio Attacks and Zero-Power Defenses&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel Halperin, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;Thomas S. Heydt-Benjamin, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin Ransford, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Shane S. Clark, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Benessa Defend, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Will Morgan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Fu, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Tadayoshi Kohno, University of Washington&lt;br /&gt;William H. Maisel, Harvard University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-S&P/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-S&P/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Security and Privacy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1997-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Entity Matching with Active Monotone Classification&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yufei Tao, Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dichotomies in Ontology-Mediated Querying with the Guarded Fragment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;André Hernich, University of Liverpool&lt;br /&gt;Carsten Lutz, University of Bremen&lt;br /&gt;Fabio Papacchini, University of Liverpool&lt;br /&gt;Frank Wolter, University of Liverpool&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FAQ: Questions Asked Frequently&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mahmoud Abo Khamis, University at Buffalo&lt;br /&gt;Hung Q. Ngo, University at Buffalo&lt;br /&gt;Atri Rudra, University at Buffalo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Parallel-Correctness and Transferability for Conjunctive Queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom J. Ameloot, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Gaetano Geck, Universität Dortmund&lt;br /&gt;Bas Ketsman, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Frank Neven, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Schwentick, Universität Dortmund&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Weaker Forms of Monotonicity for Declarative Networking: A More Fine-Grained Answer to the CALM-Conjecture&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tom J. Ameloot, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Bas Ketsman, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Frank Neven, Hasselt University&lt;br /&gt;Daniel Zinn, LogicBlox&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Verification of database-driven systems via amalgamation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mikołaj Bojańczyk, University of Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Luc Segouﬁn, INRIA&lt;br /&gt;Szymon Toruńczyk, University of Warsaw&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Worst-case Optimal Join Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hung Q. Ngo, University at Buffalo&lt;br /&gt;Ely Porat, Bar-Ilan University&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Ré, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Atri Rudra, University at Buffalo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Data Exchange Beyond Complete Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcelo Arenas, Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Jorge Pérez, Universidad de Chile&lt;br /&gt;Juan Reutter, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Optimal Algorithm for the Distinct Elements Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Daniel M. Kane, Harvard University&lt;br /&gt;Jelani Nelson, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;David P. Woodruff, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Size and Treewidth Bounds for Conjunctive Queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georg Gottlob, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Stephanie Lee, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Valient, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Estimating PageRank on Graph Streams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Atish Das Sarma, Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Sreenivas Gollapudi, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Rina Panigrahy, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Generalized Hypertree Decompositions: NP-Hardness and Tractable Variants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georg Gottlob, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Zoltan Miklos, University of Oxford&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Schwentick, Universität Dortmund&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Two-variable logic on data trees and XML reasoning&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mikolaj Bojanczyk, Warsaw University&lt;br /&gt;Claire David, Université Paris&lt;br /&gt;Anca Muscholl, Université Paris&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Schwentick, Universität Dortmund&lt;br /&gt;Luc Segoufin, Université Paris&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the complexity of division and set joins in the relational algebra&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dirk Leinders &amp;amp; Jan Van den Bussche, Limburgs Universitair Centrum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;XML data exchange: consistency and query answering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcelo Arenas &amp;amp; Leonid Libkin, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Conditional XPath, the first order complete XPath dialect&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maarten Marx, University of Amsterdam&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Information-Theoretic Approach to Normal Forms for Relational and XML Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Marcelo Arenas &amp;amp; Leonid Libkin, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Monadic Datalog and the Expressive Power of Languages for Web Information Extraction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Georg Gottlob &amp;amp; Christoph Koch, Technische Universität Wien&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Optimal aggregation algorithms for middleware&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ronald Fagin, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Amnon Lotem, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Moni Naor, Weizmann Institute of Science&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Auditing Boolean attributes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jon Kleinberg, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Christos Papadimitriou, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Prabhakar Raghavan, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Exact and approximate aggregation in constraint query languages&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael Benefikt &amp;amp; Leonid Libkin, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A lower bound theorem for indexing schemes and its application to multidimensional range queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vasilis Samoladas &amp;amp; Daniel P. Miranker, University of Texas at Austin&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Expressiveness of structured document query languages based on attribute grammars&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Frank Neven &amp;amp; Jan Van den Bussche, Limburgs Universitair Centrum&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Complexity of Database Queries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christos H. Papadimitriou, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Mihalis Yannakakis, Bell Labs&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-PODS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/08/best-paper-awards-PODS/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Databases</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (2009-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Approaching 3/2 for the s-t-path TSP&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Vera Traub &amp;amp; Jens Vygen, Universität Bonn&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Online Bipartite Matching with Amortized O(log2 N)Replacements&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Aaron Bernstein, Technical University of Berlin&lt;br /&gt;Jacob Holm, University of Copenhagen&lt;br /&gt;Eva Rotenberg, Technical University of Denmark&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Subquadratic Algorithms for the Diameter and the Sum of Pairwise Distances in Planar Graphs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sergio Cabello, University of Ljubljana&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A (2 + Є) Approximation for Maximum Weight Matching in the Semi-Streaming Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ami Paz, IRIF&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Schwartzman, National Institute of Informatics&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Improved Distributed Algorithm for Maximal Independent Set&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mohsen Ghaffari, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Near-Optimal Light Spanners&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Shiri Chechik, Tel-Aviv University&lt;br /&gt;Christian Wulff-Nilsen, University of Copenhagen&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Parameterized Complexity of k-Biclique&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bingkai Lin, University of Tokyo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Polynomiality for Bin Packing with a Constant Number of Item Types&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michel X. Goemans &amp;amp; Thomas Rothvoß, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Almost-Linear-Time Algorithm for Approximate Max Flow in Undirected Graphs, and its Multicommodity Generalizations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jonathan A. Kelner, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Yin Tat Lee, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Lorenzo Orecchia, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Sidford, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Simple Algorithm for the Graph Minor Decomposition - Logic meets Structural Graph Theory&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Grohe, RWTH Aachen University&lt;br /&gt;Ken-ichi Kawarabayashi, National Institute of Informatics&lt;br /&gt;Bruce Reed, McGill University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Dynamic graph connectivity in polylogarithmic worst case time&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bruce M. Kapron, University of Victoria&lt;br /&gt;Valerie King, University of Victoria&lt;br /&gt;Ben Mountjoy, University of Victoria&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Computing all maps into a sphere&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Martin Čadek, Masaryk University&amp;lt;brMarek Krčál, Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Jiří Matoušel, Charles University&lt;br /&gt;Francis Sergeraert, Université Joseph Fourier&lt;br /&gt;Lukáš Vokřínel, Masaryk University&lt;br /&gt;Uli Wagner, ETH Zurich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An Almost Optimal Unrestricted Fast Johnson-Lindenstrauss Transform&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nir Ailon, Technion&lt;br /&gt;Edo Liberty, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;An O(log n/log log n)-approximation Algorithm for the Asymmetric Traveling Salesman Problem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Arash Asadpour, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Michel X. Goemans, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Aleksander Mądry, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Shayan Oveis Gharan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Amin Saberi, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Natural Algorithms&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bernard Chazelle, Princeton University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SODA/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SODA/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Theory</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;SuRF:Practical Range Query Filtering with Fast Succinct Tries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Huanchen Zhang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Hyeontaek Lim, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Viktor Leis, TU München&lt;br /&gt;David G. Andersen, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Michael Kaminsky, Intel Labs&lt;br /&gt;Kimberly Keeton, Hewlett Packard Enterprise&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Pavlo, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Parallelizing Sequential Graph Computations&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wenfei Fan, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Jingbo Xu, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Yinghui Wu, Washington State University&lt;br /&gt;Wenyuan Yu, Beihang University&lt;br /&gt;Jiaxin Jiang, Hong Kong Baptist University&lt;br /&gt;Zeyu Zheng, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Bohan Zhang, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;Yang Cao, University of Edinburgh&lt;br /&gt;Chao Tian, University of Edinburgh&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wander Join: Online Aggregation via Random Walks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feifei Li, University of Utah&lt;br /&gt;Bin Wu, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Ke Yi, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology&lt;br /&gt;Zhuoyue Zhao, Shanghai Jiao Tong University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DBSCAN Revisited: Mis-Claim, Un-Fixability, and Approximation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Junhao Gan &amp;amp; Yufei Tao, Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Materialization Optimizations for Feature Selection Workloads&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ce Zhang, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Arun Kumar, University of Wisconsin&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Ré, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Massive Graph Triangulation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Xiaocheng Hu, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;br /&gt;Yufei Tao, The Chinese University of Hong Kong&lt;br /&gt;Chin-Wan Chung, KAIST&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;High-Performance Complex Event Processing over XML Streams&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Barzan Mozafari, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Kai Zeng, University of California Los Angeles&lt;br /&gt;Carlo Zaniolo, University of California Los Angeles&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Entangled Queries: Enabling Declarative Data-Driven Coordination&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nitin Gupta, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Lucja Kot, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Sudip Roy, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Gabriel Bender, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Johannes Gehrke, Cornell University&lt;br /&gt;Christoph Koch, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;FAST: fast architecture sensitive tree search on modern CPUs and GPUs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Changkyu Kim, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Jatin Chhugani, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Nadathur Satish, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Eric Sedlar, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Anthony D. Nguyen, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Tim Kaldewey, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Victor W. Lee, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Scott A. Brandt, University of California Santa Cruz&lt;br /&gt;Pradeep Dubey, Intel&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Generating example data for dataflow programs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher Olston, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Shubham Chopra, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Utkarsh Srivastava, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Serializable isolation for snapshot databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael J. Cahill, University of Sydney&lt;br /&gt;Uwe Röhm, University of Sydney&lt;br /&gt;Alan D. Fekete, University of Sydney&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scalable Network Distance Browsing in Spatial Databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hanan Samet, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Jagan Sankaranarayanan, University of Maryland&lt;br /&gt;Houman Alborzi, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Compiling mappings to bridge applications and databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sergey Melnik, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Atul Adya, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Philip A. Bernstein, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Scalable Approximate Query Processing with the DBO Engine&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Christopher Jermaine, University of Florida&lt;br /&gt;Subramanian Arumugam, University of Florida&lt;br /&gt;Abhijit Pol, University of Florida&lt;br /&gt;Alin Dobra, University of Florida&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;To search or to crawl?: towards a query optimizer for text-centric tasks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Panagiotis G. Ipeirotis, New York University&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Agichtein, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Pranay Jain, Columbia University&lt;br /&gt;Luis Gravano, Columbia University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Indexing spatio-temporal trajectories with Chebyshev polynomials&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yuhan Cai &amp;amp; Raymond T. Ng, University of British Columbia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spreadsheets in RDBMS for OLAP&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Andrew Witkowski, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Srikanth Bellakonda, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Tolga Bozkaya, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Dorman, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Nathan Folkert, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Abhinav Gupta, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Lei Shen, Oracle&lt;br /&gt;Sankar Subramanian, Oracle&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Locally adaptive dimensionality reduction for indexing large time series databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eamonn Keogh, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Kaushik Chakrabarti, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Michael Pazzani, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Sharad Mehrotra, University of California Irvine&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;XMill: an efficient compressor for XML data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hartmut Liefke, University of Pennsylvania&lt;br /&gt;Dan Suciu, AT&amp;amp;T Laboratories&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;DynaMat: a dynamic view management system for data warehouses&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yannis Kotidis &amp;amp; Nick Roussopoulos, University of Maryland&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Efficient transparent application recovery in client-server information systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;David Lomet &amp;amp; Gerhard Weikum, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Integrating association rule mining with relational database systems: alternatives and implications&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sunita Sarawagi, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Shiby Thomas, University of Florida&lt;br /&gt;Rakesh Agrawal, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Fast parallel similarity search in multimedia databases&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Stefan Berchtold, University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Christian Böml, University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Bernhard Braunmüller, University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Daniel A. Keim, University of Munich&lt;br /&gt;Hans-Peter Kriegel, University of Munich&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Implementing data cubes efficiently&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Venky Harinarayan, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Anand Rajaraman, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey D. Ullman, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGMOD/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGMOD/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Databases</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Refined Mean Field Approximation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nicolas Gast, Inria&lt;br /&gt;Benny Van Houdt, University of Antwerp&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Accelerating Performance Inference over Closed Systems by Asymptotic Methods&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giuliano Casale, Imperial College London&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On the Duration and Intensity of Competitions in Nonlinear Pólya Urn Processes with Fitness&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bo Jiang, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Daniel R. Figueiredo, Federal University of Rio de Janeiro&lt;br /&gt;Bruno Ribeiro, Purdue University&lt;br /&gt;Don Towsley, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Spy vs. Spy: Rumor Source Obfuscation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giulia Fanti, University of California Berkeley&lt;br /&gt;Peter Kairouz, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Sewoong Oh, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Pramod Viswanath, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Concave switching in single and multihop networks&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Neil Walton, University of Amsterdam&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Queueing System Topologies with Limited Flexibility&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;John Tsitsiklis &amp;amp; Kuang Xu, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Temperature management in data centers: why some (might) like it hot&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Nosayba El-Sayed, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Ioan Stefanovici, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;George Amvrosiadis, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Andy A. Hwang, University of Toronto&lt;br /&gt;Bianca Schroeder, University of Toronto&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Topology Discovery of Sparse Random Graphs With Few Participants&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Animashree Anandkumar, University of California Irvine&lt;br /&gt;Avinatan Hassidim, Google&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Kelner, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Load balancing via random local search in closed and open systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ayalvadi Ganesh, University of Bristol&lt;br /&gt;Sarah Lilienthal, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;D. Manjunath, Indian Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Alexandre Proutière, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Florian Simatos, INRIA&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The Age of Gossip: Spatial Mean Field Regime&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Augustin Chaintreau, Technicolor&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Yves Le Boudec, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;br /&gt;Nikodin Ristanovic, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Counter Braids: A Novel Counter Architecture for Per-Flow Measurement&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yi Lu, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Andrea Montanari, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Balaji Prabhakar, Stanford University&lt;br /&gt;Sarang Dharmapurikar, Cisco Systems&lt;br /&gt;Abdul Kabbani, Stanford University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Modeling the Relative Fitness of Storage&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Michael P. Mesnier, Intel&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Wachs, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Raja R. Sambasivan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Alice X. Zheng, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Gregory R. Ganger, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maximizing throughput in wireless networks via gossiping&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Eytan Modiano, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Devavrat Shah, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;Gil Zussman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Coupon replication systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Laurent Massoulié &amp;amp; Milan Vojnović, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;On performance bounds for the integration of elastic and adaptive streaming flows&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thomas Bonald &amp;amp; Alexandre Proutiere, France Telecom&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Supporting stored video: reducing rate variability and end-to-end resource requirements through optimal smoothing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James D. Salehi, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Zhi-Li Zhang, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;James F. Kurose, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Don Towsley, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Exploiting process lifetime distributions for dynamic load balancing&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mor Harchol-Balter &amp;amp; Allen B. Downey, University of California Berkeley&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGMETRICS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGMETRICS/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Performance</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Paper Awards (1996-2018)</title>
        <description>&lt;style&gt;
.table {
	font-size:12px;
}
table td {
	vertical-align: middle;
}
table th:nth-of-type(2) {
    width: 240px;
}

&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Authors&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2018&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Should I Follow the Crowd? A Probabilistic Analysis of the Effectiveness of Popularity in Recommender Systems&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Rocío Cañamares &amp;amp; Pablo Castells, Universidad Autónoma de Madrid&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2017&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;BitFunnel: Revisiting Signatures for Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bob Goodwin, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Michael Hopcroft, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Dan Luu, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Alex Clemmer, Heptio&lt;br /&gt;Mihaela Curmei, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Sameh Elnikety, Microsoft&lt;br /&gt;Yuxiong He, Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2016&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Understanding Information Need: An fMRI Study&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yashar Moshfeghi, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Peter Triantafillou, University of Glasgow&lt;br /&gt;Frank E. Pollick, University of Glasgow&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2015&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;QuickScorer: A Fast Algorithm to Rank Documents with Additive Ensembles of Regression Trees&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Claudio Lucchese, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;br /&gt;Franco Maria Nardini, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;br /&gt;Salvatore Orlando, Università di Venezia&lt;br /&gt;Raffaele Perego, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;br /&gt;Nicola Tonellotto, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;br /&gt;Rossano Venturini, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2014&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Partitioned Elias-Fano Indexes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Giuseppe Ottaviano, Istituto di Scienza e Tecnologie dell’Informazione&lt;br /&gt;Rossano Venturini, Università di Pisa&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2013&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Beliefs and Biases in Web Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryen W. White, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2012&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Time-Based Calibration of Effectiveness Measures&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mark Smucker &amp;amp; Charles Clarke, University of Waterloo&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2011&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Find It If You Can: A Game for Modeling Different Types of Web Search Success Using Interaction Data&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mikhail Ageev, Moscow State University&lt;br /&gt;Qi Guo, Emory University&lt;br /&gt;Dmitry Lagun, Emory University&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Agichtein, Emory University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2010&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Assessing the Scenic Route: Measuring the Value of Search Trails in Web Logs&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryen W. White, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Huang, University of Washington&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2009&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Sources of evidence for vertical selection&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jaime Arguello, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Fernando Diaz, Yahoo! Research&lt;br /&gt;Jamie Callan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Francois Crespo, Yahoo! Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2008&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Algorithmic Mediation for Collaborative Exploratory Search&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jeremy Pickens, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;br /&gt;Gene Golovchinsky, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;br /&gt;Chirag Shah, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill&lt;br /&gt;Pernilla Qvarfordt, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;br /&gt;Maribeth Back, FX Palo Alto Lab&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2007&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Studying the Use of Popular Destinations to Enhance Web Search Interaction&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ryen W. White, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Mikhail Bilenko, Microsoft Research&lt;br /&gt;Silviu Cucerzan, Microsoft Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2006&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Minimal Test Collections for Retrieval Evaluation&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ben Carterette, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;James Allan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Ramesh Sitaraman, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Learning to estimate query difficulty: including applications to missing content detection and distributed information retrieval&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Elad Yom-Tov, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Shai Fine, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;David Carmel, IBM Research&lt;br /&gt;Adam Darlow, IBM Research&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2004&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A Formal Study of Information Retrieval Heuristics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hui Fang, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;Tao Tao, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;br /&gt;ChengXiang Zhai, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Re-examining the potential effectiveness of interactive query expansion&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Ian Ruthven, University of Strathclyde&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2002&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Novelty and redundancy detection in adaptive filtering&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yi Zhang, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Jamie Callan, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Minka, Carnegie Mellon University&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2001&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Temporal summaries of new topics&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;James Allan, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Rahul Gupta, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;br /&gt;Vikas Khandelwal, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IR evaluation methods for retrieving highly relevant documents&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Kalervo Järvelin &amp;amp; Jaana Kekäläinen, University of Tampere&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1999&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Cross-language information retrieval based on parallel texts and automatic mining of parallel texts from the Web&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Jian-Yun Nie, Université de Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Michel Simard, Université de Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Pierre Isabelle, Université de Montréal&lt;br /&gt;Richard Durand, Université de Montréal&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;A theory of term weighting based on exploratory data analysis&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Warren R. Greiff, University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1997&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Feature selection, perceptron learning, and a usability case study for text categorization&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hwee Tou Ng, DSO National Laboratories&lt;br /&gt;Wei Boon Goh, Ministry of Defence&lt;br /&gt;Kok Leong Low, Ministry of Defence&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1996&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Retrieving spoken documents by combining multiple index sources&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Gareth Jones, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Foote, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Karen Spärck Jones, University of Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Steve Young, University of Cambridge&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGIR/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/01/04/best-paper-awards-SIGIR/</guid>
        
        <category>Best Paper</category>
        
        <category>Information Retrieval</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
